<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<!--    <string name="facebook_key_banner" translatable="false">188105218261916_188108168261621</string>-->
<!--    <string name="facebook_key_interstial" translatable="false">188105218261916_188108261594945</string>-->

    <string name="facebook_app_id" translatable="false">2416765975233198</string>

    <string name="admob_key_banner" translatable="false">ca-app-pub-1033168981021068/2839092635</string>
    <string name="admob_key_interstitial" translatable="false">ca-app-pub-1033168981021068/2243663430</string>
    <string name="admob_key_native" translatable="false">ca-app-pub-1033168981021068/8364305486</string>

    <string name="admob_app_id" translatable="false">ca-app-pub-1033168981021068~1362359431</string>
    <string name="ad_unit_id" translatable="false">ca-app-pub-1033168981021068/8364305486</string>

    <string name="soma_ID_APP" translatable="false">1100030699</string>

    <string name="soma_key_banner_phone" translatable="false">130236221</string>
    <string name="soma_key_banner_tab" translatable="false">130239147</string>

    <string name="soma_key_interst_phone" translatable="false">130236222</string>
    <string name="soma_key_interst_tab" translatable="false">130236223</string>

    <string name="app_name">PRO Fitness</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>

    <drawable name="focused">#ff5500</drawable>
    <drawable name="selected">#FF00FF</drawable>

    <string name="buffering">buffering</string>


    <string name="app_id" translatable="false">1457812561100616</string>
<!--    <string name="facebook_app_id" translatable="false">921446537903472</string>-->
    <string name="title_1">Exercises</string>
    <string name="title_2">Workouts</string>
    <string name="title_3">Custom</string>
    <string name="title_4">Log</string>
    <string name="title_5">More</string>
    <string name="title_6">Reminder</string>
    <string name="title_7">Units: kg</string>
    <string name="title_8">Units: lbs</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="titles">Title:  </string>
    <string name="downl_vid">Downloading video</string>
    <string name="please_wait">Please wait...</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="work">My Workout</string>
    <string name="create_plus">To create new workout press +</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="workout_name">Workout Name:</string>
    <string name="days_title">Days Number:</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="work_title">Workout Title:</string>
    <string name="options">Options:</string>
    <string name="camera">Camera/Gallery</string>
    <string name="ex_phot_title">Exercise’s Photos</string>
    <string name="name_desc">Name, Description</string>
    <string name="ex_name">Exercise Name:</string>
    <string name="desc">Description:</string>
    <string name="auto">Auto</string>
    <string name="on">On</string>
    <string name="off">Off</string>
    <string name="retake">Retake</string>
    <string name="preview">Preview</string>
    <string name="use">Use</string>
    <string name="erorr">Error!</string>
    <string name="blanck">Please fill up the text field!</string>
    <string name="okey">Ok</string>
    <string name="realy_cancel">Do you really want to cancel the download process? All downloaded videos will be lost!</string>
    <string name="download_all">Download All Videos</string>
    <string name="unzip">Unziping Files</string>
    <string name="files">Files</string>
    <string name="dow_video">Downloading Videos</string>
    <string name="video_saved">All videos were saved succesfully!</string>
    <string name="conn">Please check your wi-fi or cellular internet connection!</string>
    <string name="stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="pause">Pause</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="status">Status</string>
    <string name="empty_message">00:00</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="weight">Weight(kg)</string>
    <string name="repetitions">Repetitions</string>
    <string name="set_s">Set seconds</string>
    <string name="wei">Weight</string>
    <string name="rep">Repetitions</string>
    <string name="wei_rep">Performance</string>
    <string name="no_history">No exercises have been done yet</string>
    <string name="no_exercise">You have no exercises yet.\nGo on and create your first one.</string>
    <string name="last_val">Last values</string>
    <string name="send_f">Send Feedback</string>
    <string name="rep_bug">Report a Bug</string>
    <string name="tel_fr">Tell a Friend</string>
    <string name="rate_us">Rate us</string>
    <string name="ad">Add</string>

    <string name="exit">Are you sure ?</string>
    <string name="sdcard">No SDCard!</string>
    <string name="post_to">Post to wall</string>
    <string name="not_loged">Not Logged</string>
    <string name="log_fail">Login Failed</string>
    <string name="posting">Posting </string>
    <string name="posting_succes">Posted Successfully</string>
    <string name="email_sent">Email Sent</string>
    <string name="email_notsent">Email Not Sent</string>
    <string name="change_db">Wait...Changing DB</string>

    <string name="s1">4 sets and 15 reps</string>
    <string name="s2">4 sets and 12/10/8/6 reps</string>
    <string name="s3">5 sets and 3/3/3/2/1 reps</string>

    <string name="rek1">My GoFitness</string>
    <string name="rek2">6 Pack Abs</string>
    <string name="rek3">Go Fitness</string>

    <string name="info">Alege categoria la care se refera la moment corpul tau</string>
    <string name="dialog_future">You can\'t input data for future dates.</string>

    <string name="ex_guide_1">Back and Chest</string>
    <string name="ex_guide_2">Legs and Forearms</string>
    <string name="ex_guide_3">Shoulders, Triceps and Biceps</string>
    <string name="ex_guide_4">Back and Triceps</string>
    <string name="ex_guide_5">Chest and Biceps</string>
    <string name="ex_guide_6">Legs and Shoulders</string>
    <string name="ex_guide_7">Cycle 1</string>
    <string name="ex_guide_8">Cycle 2</string>
    <string name="ex_guide_9">Cycle 3</string>
    <string name="ex_guide_10">Biceps and Triceps</string>
    <string name="ex_guide_11">Legs</string>
    <string name="ex_guide_12">Back</string>
    <string name="ex_guide_13">Biceps</string>
    <string name="ex_guide_14">Chest</string>
    <string name="ex_guide_15">Shoulders</string>
    <string name="ex_guide_16">Triceps</string>

    <string name="ex_name_1">Bicycle Crunch</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_1">Instructions \n1. Lay supine in a relaxed position with your arms behind your head and legs straight. \n2. Exhale as you raise one knee towards your face while driving the opposite elbow to the knee. \n3. Once your abs are fully contracted, slowly lower yourself back to the starting position and repeat on the opposite side. \n4. Complete for the assigned number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Exhale hard like you\’re blowing out candles on a cake and hold the contraction for a second in order to improve mind muscle connection. \n2. If your lower back bothers you during this exercise, choose more anti extension and anti rotation based movements. \n3. Avoid putting the hands behind the head as this can lead to excess strain upon the neck.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_2">Hanging Leg Raise</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_2">Instructions \n1. The hanging leg raise is an awesome exercise for building the lower abs. All you need for this exercise is somewhere to hang from. It could be a chin-up bar or it could be a tree. \n2. Once you\'re hanging, tense up the mid section. While keeping your legs straight, raise your them up slowly. You should raise your legs are high as possible. \n3. Pause for a second, and slowly lower your legs back to the starting position. \n4. Repeat for desired reps. \n\nTips: \n1. Speed is so important with the hanging leg raise. If you swing your legs, you\'re using momentum and your abs will not benefit much from the exercise. \n2. Do not allow your body to swing. Keep your torso as still and controlled as possible. \n3. Advanced lifters can add weight by holding a dumbbell between the feet.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_3">Roman Chair Knee Raise</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_3">Instructions \n1. The Roman chair knee raise hits your lower abdominal muscles. Get into the chair so that your forearms are resting on the pads, back on the back pad, and hands grasping the handles. \n2. Take your feet off the rests so they are hanging straight down. \n3. Slowly raise your knees up as high as possible. \n4. Pause, then lower back to the starting position. \n5. Repeat for desired reps. \n\nTips: \n1. You must do the Roman chair leg raise slowly. Using speed and momentum throughout the exercise takes the emphasis off your abs. \n2. You can also do this exercise weighted, holding a dumbbell between your feet.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_4">Deadlift</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_4">Instructions \n1. Position the bar over the top of your shoelaces and assume a hip width stance. \n2. Push your hips back and hinge forward until your torso is nearly parallel with the floor. \n3. Reach down and grasp the bar using a shoulder width, double overhand grip. \n4. Inhale and pull up slightly on the bar while allowing your hips to drop in a seesaw fashion. This phenomenon is commonly referred to as \"pulling the slack out of the bar\". \n5. As you drop the hips and pull up on the bar, set the lats (imagine you’re trying to squeeze oranges in your armpits) and ensure your armpits are positioned directly over the bar. \n6. Drive through the whole foot and focus on pushing the floor away. \n7. Ensure the bar tracks in a straight line as you extend the knees and hips. \n8. Once you have locked out the hips, reverse the movement by pushing the hips back and hinging forward. \n9. Return the bar to the floor, reset, and repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. You MUST keep the crease of the armpit over the bar and the midfoot in order to allow the bar to travel linearly. \n2. The deadlift is a hinge, not a squat. If you set the hips too low you will put yourself in a disadvantageous position biomechanically and limit your potential for pulling maximal weights.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_5">Bent Over Barbell Row</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_5">Instructions \n 1. Assume a standing position while holding the bar using a double overhand grip. \n 2. Hinge forward until your torso is roughly parallel with the floor (or slightly above) and then begin the movement by driving the elbows behind the body while retracting the shoulder blades. \n 3. Pull the bar towards your belly button until it touches your body and then slowly lower the bar back to the starting position under control. \n 4. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Experiment with head position and see which option (looking forward vs. packing the neck) works better for you. \n2. Keep some tone through your abdominals as you pull the bar into your body to ensure you don’t arch excessively through your spine. \n3. Don’t allow momentum to dictate the movement, control the bar throughout the entirety of each rep.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_6">Bent Over Two Dumbbell Row</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_6">Instructions \n1. Assume a standing position while holding a dumbbell in each hand with a neutral grip. \n2. Hinge forward until your torso is roughly parallel with the floor (or slightly above) and then begin the movement by driving the elbows behind the body while retracting the shoulder blades. \n3. Pull the dumbbells towards your body until the elbows are at (or just past) the midline and then slowly lower the dumbbells back to the starting position under control. \n4. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Experiment with head position and see which option (looking forward vs. packing the neck) works better for you. \n2. Keep some tone through your abdominals as you pull the dumbbells into your body to ensure you don’t arch excessively through your spine. \n3. Don’t allow momentum to dictate the movement, control the dumbbells throughout the entirety of each rep.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_7">Wide Grip Pull Up</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_7">Instructions \n1. Using a pronated grip, grasp the pull bar with a wider than shoulder width grip. \n2. Take a deep breath, squeeze your glutes and brace your abs. Depress the shoulder blades and then drive the elbows straight down to the floor while activating the lats. \n3. Pull your chin towards the bar until the lats are fully contracted, then slowly lower yourself back to the start position and repeat for the assigned number of repetitions. \n\n Tips \n1. To decrease bicep involvement, use a false (thumbless grip). \n2. Try to keep a neutral head position (looking straight ahead or slightly up) as hyperextending the neck can lead to compensations throughout the spine. \n3. If the bar is high enough, keep the legs straight and in front of the body in a hollow body position.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_8">One Arm Dumbbell Row</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_8">Instructions \n1. Place your left knee and left hand on a flat bench with your right leg set firmly on the floor. \n2. Hold a dumbbell in the opposite hand with a neutral grip. \n3. Begin the movement by driving the elbow behind the body while retracting the shoulder blade. \n4. Pull the dumbbell towards your body until the elbow is at (or just past) the midline and then slowly lower the dumbbells back to the starting position under control. \n5. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions on both sides. \n\nTips \n1. Experiment with head position and see which option (looking forward vs. packing the neck) works better for you. \n2. Keep some tone through your abdominals as you pull the bar into your body to ensure you don’t arch excessively through your spine. \n3. Don’t allow momentum to dictate the movement, control the dumbbells throughout the entirety of each rep. \n4. If you feel your biceps being overused and your back remaining under active, consider utilizing a false grip.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_9">Reverse Grip Bent Over Rows</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_9">Instructions \n1. Grab a barbell, load some weight on, and place the barbell down in front of you. \n2. Stand with your feet at around shoulder width, bend at the knees, squat down to grip the bar with a reverse grip (thumbs at the top of the bar) and your hands wider than shoulder width apart. \n3. Keeping your back straight, stand straight up so you\'re holding the bar in front of you against your waist. To get into the starting position bend you knees slightly, and while keeping your back straight let the barbell slide down your thighs until it drops just below knee level. This is the stance that should not change throughout the set. \n4. Now pull the bar up to just below your chest. \n5. Squeeze your shoulder blades together at the top of the movement. \n6. Then slowly lower the bar back to the starting position. Repeat for desired reps. \n\nTips \n1. Pause at the top of the exercise and squeeze your shoulder blades together. \n2. Don\'t let the weight drop down quickly - keep it slow. \n3. Keep your back straight throughout the entire set. \n4. Keep your head up and your eyes looking forward throughout the whole movement. \n5. The bent over row can cause back injuries, so make sure your technique is perfected before loading on the weight.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_10">Seated Cable Rows</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_10">Instructions \n1. Set the appropriate weight on the weight stack and attach a close grip bar or V–bar to the seated row machine. \n2. Grasp the bar with a neutral grip (palms facing in). \n3. Keeping your legs slightly bent and your back straight, pull the weight up slightly off the stack. You should be sitting straight upright with your shoulders back. This is the starting position. \n4. Keeping your body in position, pull the handle into your stomach. \n5. Pull your shoulder blades back, squeeze, pause, and then slowly lower the weight back to the starting position. \n6. Repeat for desired reps. \n\nTips \n1. Your back must remain straight at all times. Your torso should be kept still throughout the entire set. \n2. Don\'t let your shoulders hunch over when your arms are extended. \n3. Use the back muscles to move the weight - do not lean forward and use momentum to swing the weight back. \n4. Pausing and squeezing at the top of the movement for a 1-2 count will increase intensity and results.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_11">Reverse Grip Lat Cable Pull Down</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_11">Instructions \n1. Attach a wide grip handle to the lat pulldown machine and assume a seated position. \n2. Grasp the handle with a supinated grip (double underhand) just inside of shoulder width. \n3. Initiate the movement by depressing the shoulder blades and then flexing the elbow while extending the shoulder. \n4. Pull the handle towards your body until the elbows are in line with your torso and then slowly lower the handle back to the starting position under control. \n5. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Keep some tone through your abdominals as you pull the bar into your body to ensure you don’t arch excessively through the spine. \n2. Don’t allow momentum to dictate the movement, control the weight throughout the entirety of each rep. \n3. If you feel your biceps being overused and your back remaining under active, consider utilizing a false grip.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_12">V - Bar Pull Down</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_12">Instructions \n1. Attach a V-bar to the lat pulldown machine and assume a seated position. \n2. Grasp the handle with a neutral grip and initiate the movement by depressing the shoulder blades and then flexing the elbow while extending the shoulder. \n3. Pull the handle towards your body until the elbows are in line with your torso and then slowly lower the handle back to the starting position under control. \n4. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Keep some tone through your abdominals as you pull the bar into your body to ensure you don’t arch excessively through the spine. \n2. Don’t allow momentum to dictate the movement, control the dumbbells throughout the entirety of each rep. \n3. If you feel your biceps being overused and your back remaining under active, consider utilizing a false grip</string>

    <string name="ex_name_13">Wide Grip Lat Pulldown</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_13">Instructions \n1. Attach a wide grip handle to the lat pulldown machine and assume a seated position. \n2. Grasp the handle with a pronated grip (double overhand) and initiate the movement by depressing the shoulder blade and then flexing the elbow while extending the shoulder. \n3. Pull the handle towards your body until the elbows are in line with your torso and then slowly lower the handle back to the starting position under control. \n4. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Keep some tone through your abdominals as you pull the bar into your body to ensure you don’t arch excessively through the spine. \n2. Don’t allow momentum to dictate the movement, control the dumbbells throughout the entirety of each rep. \n3. If you feel your biceps being overused and your back remaining under active, consider utilizing a false grip</string>

    <string name="ex_name_14">Standing Barbell Reverse Curl</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_14">Instructions \n1. Select the desired weight and assume a shoulder width stance. \n2. Using a pronated (palms down) grip, take a deep breath and curl the barbell towards your shoulders. \n3. Once the biceps are fully shortened, slowly lower the weight back to the starting position. \n4. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Don’t allow the elbows to shift behind the body. Similarly, make sure the shoulder doesn’t shift forward in the socket as you lower the weight. \n2. Maintain a slight bend in the elbow at the bottom of the movement in order to keep tension through the biceps. \n3. Rotate the forearms slowly, excessive velocity may cause issues within the elbows or wrists. \n4. Using a slow eccentric (lowering portion) of the exercise can help to improve tension and mind muscle connection.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_15">Standing Barbell Curl</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_15">Instructions \n1. The standing barbell curl is the cornerstone of many bicep building routines. Grasp a barbell or Olympic bar at around shoulder width apart using an underhand grip (palms facing up). \n2. Stand straight up, feet together (you may be more comfortable putting one foot back for stability), back straight, and with your arms fully extended. \n3. The bar should not be touching your body. \n4. Keeping your eyes facing forwards, elbows tucked in at your sides, and your body completely still, slowly curl the bar up. \n5. Squeeze your biceps hard at the top of the movement, and then slowly lower it back to the starting position. \n6. Repeat for desired reps. \n\nTips: \n1. The single biggest mistake lifters make on this exercise is swinging the body back to assist in moving the weight up. This is cheating! Your body should remain fixed and only your biceps should be used to move the weight. \n2. Another mistake is not keeping the elbows fixed and in at the sides. You should not let your elbows come forward when moving the weight up. \n3. And finally, you need to control the weight throughout the set. This means not letting it drop quickly!</string>

    <string name="ex_name_16">EZ Bar Curl</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_16">Instructions \n1. The standing EZ bar curl is a variation of the barbell curl, but using an EZ bar. Grasp an EZ bar at around shoulder width apart using a underhand grip (palms facing up). \n2. Stand straight up, feet together (you may be more comfortable taking one foot back for stability), back straight, and with your arms fully extended. The bar should not be touching your body. \n3. Keeping your eyes facing forwards, elbows tucked in at your sides, and your body completely still, slowly curl the bar up. \n4. Squeeze your biceps hard at the top of the movement, and then slowly lower it back to the starting position. \n5. Repeat for desired reps. \n\nTips: \n1. Use the EZ bar curl when you have had wrist injuries or if you feel pain in the wrists when doing barbell curls. \n2. Do not swing back when you curl the bar up. This is cheating. \n3. Keep your body fixed and elbows in at your sides throughout the movement.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_17">EZ Bar Preacher Curl</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_17">Instructions \n1. The EZ bar preacher curl is a great exercise to isolate the biceps, while minimizing the strain on your wrists. Adjust the seat on the preacher bench so that your upper arms sit comfortably on the padding when seated. \n2. Load the desired weight on the barbell. \n3. Sit on the preacher bench and grip the EZ bar with your hands shoulder width apart using an underhand (palms facing up) grip. (note: You can use a wide or narrow grip on this exercise) \n4. Keeping your back straight and eyes facing forward, take the weight off the rack so that you\'re supporting it with your arms slightly bent. This is the starting position. \n5. Slowly bring the weight up until your forearms are at a right angle to the floor. \n6. Squeeze the bicep at the top of the movement, and then slowly lower it back to the starting position. \n7. Repeat for desired reps. \n\nTips: \n1. Keep the motion slow and controlled throughout the set. \n2. Don\'t \"rest\" at the top of the movement. \n3. Squeeze the biceps as hard as possible as your get the weight to the top. \n4. Use a wide grip to work the inner biceps and a close grip to work the outer biceps.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_18">EZ Bar Cable Curl</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_18">Instructions \n1. Set up for the cable curl by attaching a EZ bar to the low pulley cable and selecting the weight you want to use on the stack. \n2. Stand facing the cable machine with your legs shoulder width apart. \n3. Grasp the bar with an underhand grip (palms facing up), and your hands about shoulder width apart. \n4. Keeping your elbows tucked in by your sides, slowly curl the bar up as far as possible. \n5. Squeeze the biceps at the top of the movement, and then slowly lower it back to starting position. \n6. Do not pause, but go straight into the next rep! \n\nTips: \n1. Keep your elbows tucked in by your sides and don\'t allow them to come forward as you curl the weight up. \n2. Don\'t \"rest\" at the bottom of the movement. When you complete a rep move straight into the next rep! \n3. Keep the rep timing slow and control the weight as you lower it.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_19">Machine Preacher Curls</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_19">Instructions \n1. Sit down on the Preacher Curl Machine and select the weight. \n2. Place the back of your upper arms (your triceps) on the preacher pad provided and grab the handles using an underhand grip (palms facing up). Tip: Make sure that when you place the arms on the pad you keep the elbows in. This will be your starting position. \n3. Now lift the handles as you exhale and you contract the biceps. At the top of the position make sure that you hold the contraction for a second. Tip: Only the forearms should move. The upper arms should remain stationary and on the pad at all times. \n4. Lower the handles slowly back to the starting position as you inhale. \n5. Repeat for the recommended amount of repetitions. \n\nTips: \n1. Make sure you use a full range of motion by allowing the weight to go as far as possible without hitting the stack. \n2. Keep the rep timing slow, and control the weight. \n3. If you have a training partner, the bicep machine is good for heavy negative curls. \n\nVariations: \nYou can use free weights (barbells and dumbbells) to perform this exercise on a preacher bench. Alternatively, you can use the pulley machine as well in conjunction with a preacher bench.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_20">Standing Hammer Curl </string>
    <string name="ex_desc_20">Instructions \n1. The hammer curl is a great exercise for the biceps and forearms. Set up by grasping a set of dumbbells and standing straight up with the dumbbells by your sides. \n2. You should be using a neutral grip, meaning your palms are facing your body. \n3. Bend your arms slightly to take tension into the biceps. \n4. Keeping your body fixed and elbows in at your sides, slowly curl the dumbbells up as far as possible. \n5. Squeeze the biceps at the top of the movement, and then slowly lower the weight back to the starting position. \n6. Repeat for desired reps. \n\nTips: \n1. Do not lean back as you move the weight - this is cheating! \n2. Keep your elbows locked in by your sides throughout the set. Don\'t allow them to come forward as you curl the weight up. Focus on only allowing your forearms to move. \n3. Squeeze and hold at the top of the movement for maximum results. \n4. Keep the rep timing slow and control the weight for the whole set.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_21">Alternate Seated Dumbbell Curl</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_21">Instructions \n1. Set up for the alternate seated dumbbell curl by grabbing a flat bench or adjustable bench and placing a set of dumbbells at one end. If you\'re using an adjustable bench, adjust the back to a 90 degree angle. \n2. Sit on the end of the bench with your feet out in front of you and your knees together. \n3. Pick up the dumbbells from the floor and let them hang by your sides with your palms facing up. \n4. Bend the arms slightly to take the tension into the biceps. This is the starting position for the exercise. \n5. Keeping your back straight and your elbows tucked in at your sides, slowly curl up the dumbbell in your weakest arm (for most people this is their left) up as far as possible. \n6. Squeeze the bicep hard, then slowly lower the weight back to the starting position. \n7. Repeat for the other arm, and then repeat for desired reps. \n\nTips: \n1. Keep your body fixed throughout the set. Do not lean back when curling the dumbbells up. \n2. Keep your elbows tucked in at your sides. \n3. Keep the tension on the bicep throughout the set, even in the arm that is not curling the weight. </string>

    <string name="ex_name_22">Incline Dumbbell Curl</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_22">Instructions \n1. Position an incline bench at roughly 55-65 degrees, select the desired weight from the rack, and sit upright with your back flat against the pad. \n2. Using a supinated (palms up) grip, take a deep breath and curl both dumbbells towards your shoulders. \n3. Once the biceps are fully shortened, slowly lower the weights back to the starting position. \n4. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Don’t allow the elbows to shift behind the body. Similarly, make sure the shoulder doesn\’t shift forward in the socket as you lower the weight. \n2. Maintain a slight bend in the elbow at the bottom of the movement in order to keep tension through the biceps. \n3. Using a slow eccentric (lowering portion) of the exercise can help to improve tension and mind muscle connection. </string>

    <string name="ex_name_23">Alternating Standing Dumbbell Curl</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_23">Instructions \n1. The standing dumbbell curl is a good way to correct any strength and size imbalances in the biceps as it works each muscle individually. Set up for the exercise by grasping a set of dumbbells and standing straight up with the dumbbells by your side. \n2. Your palms should be facing up, and the dumbbells not touching your body. \n3. Before starting the set, take up the slack by lifting up the weight slightly so the tension is on your bicep muscles. \n4. Starting with your weakest arm (usually the left), curl the dumbbell up as far as possible. \n5. Squeeze the bicep at the top of the exercise, and then slowly lower the weight down without it touching your body or taking the tension off your bicep. \n6. Repeat for the other arm. \n7. That\'s one rep. Now repeat for the desired amount of reps to complete the set. \n\nTips: \n1. Keep the tension on both of your biceps throughout the set. Do not rest the weights on your body or let them hang down. \n2. Keep your body fixed throughout the set. No swinging back as you raise the weight! \n3. Always start with your weakest arm - for most people that will be their left. As a general rule you should always hit your weakest side/body part first.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_24">Seated Calf Raise</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_24">Instructions \n1. Take a seat on the machine and place the balls of your feet on the platform with your toes pointed forward - your heels will naturally hang off. Position the base of quads under the knee pad and allow your hands to rest on top. \n2. Extend your ankles and release the safety bar. \n3. Lower the heels by dorsiflexing the ankles until the calves are fully stretched. \n4. Extend the ankles and exhale as you flex the calves. \n5. Repeat for the assigned number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Keep the repetitions slow and controlled. Limit momentum and pause at the top to emphasize the contraction. \n2. Limit depth of the heels if you feel any sort of stretch through the bottom of the foot during the exercise. \n3. Try to move through the ball of the foot rather than the base of the toes.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_25">Seated Smith Machine Calf Raise</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_25">Instructions \n1. Set up for the smith machine seated calf raise by placing a flat bench in the smith machine and putting a step or calf Block or step under the bar. \n2. Lower the bar and add the weight you want to use. \n3. Sit on the end of the bench with your feet and knees together and balls of your feet on the edge of the block. \n4. Take the bar off the rack and rest it on your thighs. \n5. Allow your heels to drop as far as possible without touching the floor. This is the starting position. \n6. Execute the movement by raising your heels up as far as possible. \n7. Squeeze the calf muscles, and then slowly lower your heals back to the starting position. \n8. Repeat for desired reps. \n\nTips: \n1. This exercise is a great alternative to the seated calf raise machine. \n2. Make sure the balls of your feet are on the edge of the block/step. t let them come forward as this makes the exercise less challenging. \n3. Keep the rep timing slow and controlled, lowering the weight slowly. \n4. Pause at the top of the movement (heels up) for a count of 2-3 to add intensity.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_26">Standing Dumbbell Calf Raise</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_26">Instructions \n1. Stand with your torso upright holding two dumbbells in your hands by your sides. Place the ball of the foot on a sturdy and stable wooden board (that is around 2-3 inches tall) while your heels extend off and touch the floor. This will be your starting position. \n2. With the toes pointing either straight (to hit all parts equally), inwards (for emphasis on the outer head) or outwards (for emphasis on the inner head), raise the heels off the floor as you exhale by contracting the calves. Hold the top contraction for a second. \n3. As you inhale, go back to the starting position by slowly lowering the heels. \n4. Repeat for the recommended amount of times. \n\nTips \n1. Keep the balls of your feet on the edge of the step. Don\'t let your feet come forward as this makes the exercise less challenging. \n2. Keep the rep timing slow and controlled - don\'t \"bounce\". \n3. To help keep your balance, keep your eyes facing forward at all times. \n\nNote: As you become stronger you may need to use wrist wraps to avoid having the dumbbells slip out of your hands.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_27">Standing Smith Machine Calf Raise</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_27">Instructions \n1. The smith machine is a good alternative if your gym does not have a standing calf raise machine. Set the bar on the smith machine to around shoulder height and rack up the weight you want to use. \n2. Grab a step or calf block and put it below the bar. \n3. Step up on the block and position the balls of your feet on the edge. \n4. Grasp the smith bar with a wide grip and position it across the top of your back muscles (not across the back of your neck!). \n5. Push up to take the weight off the rack and slowly let your heels drop down as far as possible. This is the starting position. \n6. Slowly raise your heels as far as you can off the floor. \n7. Squeeze the calf muscles, and then slowly lower your heels back to the starting position. \n8. Repeat for desired reps. \n\nTips \n1. Don\'t let your heels touch the floor throughout the set. \n2. The balls of your feet should be right on the edge of the block. Do not allow them to come forward as it makes the exercise less challenging. \n3. Use the maximum range of motion by allowing your heels to drop as far as possible and then raising them as high as possible. \n4. Focus on Not allowing your knees to bend.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_28">Barbell Bench Press</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_28">Instructions \n1. Lie flat on a bench and set your hands just outside of shoulder width. \n2. Set your shoulder blades by pinching them together and driving them into the bench. \n3. Take a deep breath and allow your spotter to help you with the lift off in order to maintain tightness through your upper back. \n4. Let the weight settle and ensure your upper back remains tight after lift off. \n5. Inhale and allow the bar to descend slowly by unlocking the elbows. \n6. Lower the bar in a straight line to the base of the sternum (breastbone) and touch the chest. \n7. Push the bar back up in a straight line by pressing yourself into the bench, driving your feet into the floor for leg drive, and extending the elbows. \n8. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Technique first, weight second - no one cares how much you bench if you get injured. \n2. Keep the bar in line with your wrist and elbows and ensure it travels in a straight line. In order to keep the wrist straight, try to position the bar as low in the palm as possible while still being able to wrap the thumb. \n3. If you want to keep more tension through the triceps and chest, stop each repetition just short of lockout at the top. \n4. Don’t worry about tucking the elbows excessively, much of this advice is from geared lifters using suits. A slight tuck on the way down may be advisable for some lifters but other lifters can use an excellent cue from Greg Nuckols that will accomplish the same thing: \"Flare and push\".</string>

    <string name="ex_name_29">Decline Dumbbell Bench Press</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_29">Instructions \n1. Pick up the dumbbells off the floor using a neutral grip (palms facing in). Position the ends of the dumbbells in your hip crease, and sit down on the edge of an decline bench. \n2. To get into position, lay back and keep the weights close to your chest. Once you are in position, take a deep breath, and press the dumbbells to lockout at the top. \n3. Slowly lower the dumbbells under control as far as comfortably possible (the handles should be about level with your chest). \n4. Contract the chest and push the dumbbells back up to the starting position. \n5. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n**Dropping the dumbbells to the side is discouraged unless you are experienced with the technique or using excessively heavy weights. \n**Ideally you should twist the dumbbells back to neutral (palms facing each other), bring your knees up so the ends of the dumbbells are touching your thighs, then use the weight of the dumbbells to rock back to an upright, seated position. \n\nTips \n1. Maintain more tension through the pecs by not locking out the elbows entirely. \n2. Keep the weights slightly tilted at a 45 degree angle in order to keep the elbows in a neutral position. \n3. Don’t allow the dumbbells to collide at the top of each rep - bouncing them together may cause you to lose stability within the shoulder and injure yourself.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_30">Decline Dumbbell Flyes</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_30">Instructions \n1. Pick up the dumbbells off the floor using a neutral grip (palms facing in). Position the ends of the dumbbells in your hip crease, and sit down on an decline bench. \n2. To get into position, lay back and keep the weights close to your chest. Once you are in position, take a deep breath, then press the dumbbells to lockout at the top. \n3. Slightly retract your shoulder blades, unlock your elbows, and slowly lower the dumbbells laterally while maintaining the angle at your elbow. \n4. Once the dumbbells reach chest level, reverse the movement by squeezing your pecs together and bringing the dumbbells back to their starting position. \n5. Without allowing the dumbbells to touch, start the next repetition, and continue until the set is completed. \n\nTips \n1. Use a slight decline such as 30 degrees. Extremes are never the best option. \n2. Imagine you’re trying to hug a tree while you complete the exercise. \n3. Don’t squeeze the dumbbell handles excessively tight as this can over recruit the forearms and biceps thereby reducing activation of the pecs. \n4. Avoid touching or banging the dumbbells together at the top of each repetition to keep constant tension on the intended muscle groups.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_31">Decline Bench Press</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_31">Instructions \n1. Lie flat on an decline bench, set your hands just outside of shoulder width, and hook your feet underneath the pad. \n2. Set your shoulder blades by pinching them together and driving them into the bench. \n3. Take a deep breath and allow your spotter to help you with the lift off in order to maintain tightness through your upper back. \n4. Let the weight settle and ensure your upper back remains tight after lift off. \n5. Inhale and allow the bar to descend slowly by unlocking the elbows. \n6. Lower the bar in a straight line to just below your sternum (breastbone) and touch the chest. \n7. Push the bar back up in a straight line by pressing yourself into the bench and extending the elbows. \n8. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Technique first, weight second - no one cares how much you bench if you get injured. \n2. Keep the bar in line with your wrist and elbows and ensure it travels in a straight line. In order to keep the wrist straight, try to position the bar as low in the palm as possible while still being able to wrap the thumb. \n3. If you want to keep more tension through the triceps and chest, stop each repetition just short of lockout at the top.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_32">Dumbbell Bench Press</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_32">Instructions \n1. Pick up the dumbbells off the floor using a neutral grip (palms facing in). Position the ends of the dumbbells in your hip crease, and sit down on the bench. \n2. To get into position, lay back and keep the weights close to your chest. Once you are in position, take a deep breath, and press the dumbbells to lockout at the top. \n3. Slowly lower the dumbbells under control as far as comfortably possible (the handles should be about level with your chest). \n4. Contract the chest and push the dumbbells back up to the starting position. \n5. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n**Dropping the dumbbells to the side is discouraged unless you are experienced with the technique or using excessively heavy weights. \n**Ideally you should twist the dumbbells back to neutral (palms facing each other), bring your knees up so the ends of the dumbbells are touching your thighs, then use the weight of the dumbbells to rock back to an upright, seated position. \n\nTips \n1. Maintain more tension through the pecs by not locking out the elbows entirely. \n2. Keep the weights slightly tilted at a 45 degree angle in order to keep the elbows in a neutral position. \n3. Don’t allow the dumbbells to collide at the top of each rep - bouncing them together may cause you to lose stability within the shoulder and injure yourself. \n4. Squeeze the dumbbells as tight as possible to improve a phenomenon known as “irradiation” which promotes greater shoulder stability.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_33">Dumbbell Flyes</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_33">Instructions \n1. Pick up the dumbbells off the floor using a neutral grip (palms facing in). Position the ends of the dumbbells in your hip crease, and sit down on the bench. \n2. To get into position, lay back and keep the weights close to your chest. Once you are in position, take a deep breath, then press the dumbbells to lockout at the top. \n3. Slightly retract your shoulder blades, unlock your elbows, and slowly lower the dumbbells laterally while maintaining the angle at your elbow. \n4. Once the dumbbells reach chest level, reverse the movement by squeezing your pecs together and bringing the dumbbells back to their starting position. \n5. Without allowing the dumbbells to touch, start the next repetition, and continue until the set is completed. \n\nTips \n1. Imagine you’re trying to hug a tree while completing the exercise. \n2. Don’t squeeze the dumbbell handles excessively tight as this can over recruit the forearms and biceps thereby reducing activation of the pecs. \n3. Avoid touching or banging the dumbbells together at the top of each repetition in order to keep constant tension on the intended muscle groups. \n4. Always keep a slight bend in the elbows and never lower the weight to the point where you get any sort of pain and pressure at the front of the shoulder joint.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_34">Incline Dumbbell Flyes</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_34">Instructions \n1. Pick up the dumbbells off the floor using a neutral grip (palms facing in). Position the ends of the dumbbells in your hip crease, and sit down on an incline bench. \n2. To get into position, lay back and keep the weights close to your chest. Once you are in position, take a deep breath, then press the dumbbells to lockout at the top. \n3. Slightly retract your shoulder blades, unlock your elbows, and slowly lower the dumbbells laterally while maintaining the angle at your elbow. \n4. Once the dumbbells reach chest level, reverse the movement by squeezing your pecs together and bringing the dumbbells back to their starting position. \n5. Without allowing the dumbbells to touch, start the next repetition, and continue until the set is completed. \n\nTips \n1. Use a slight incline such as 30 degrees. Extremes are never the best option. \n2. Imagine you’re trying to hug a tree while you complete the exercise. \n3. Don’t squeeze the dumbbell handles excessively tight as this can over recruit the forearms and biceps thereby reducing activation of the pecs. \n4. Avoid touching or banging the dumbbells together at the top of each repetition in order to keep constant tension on the intended muscle groups.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_35">Incline Dumbbell Bench Press</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_35">Instructions \n1. Pick up the dumbbells off the floor using a neutral grip (palms facing in). Position the ends of the dumbbells in your hip crease, and sit down on the edge of an incline bench. \n2. To get into position, lay back and keep the weights close to your chest. Once you are in position, take a deep breath, and press the dumbbells to lockout at the top. \n3. Slowly lower the dumbbells under control as far as comfortably possible (the handles should be about level with your chest). \n4. Contract the chest and push the dumbbells back up to the starting position. \n5. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n**Dropping the dumbbells to the side is discouraged unless you are experienced with the technique or using excessively heavy weights. \n**Ideally you should twist the dumbbells back to neutral (palms facing each other), bring your knees up so the ends of the dumbbells are touching your thighs, then use the weight of the dumbbells to rock back to an upright, seated position. \n\nTips \n1. Maintain more tension through the pecs by not locking out the elbows entirely. \n2. Keep the weights slightly tilted at a 45 degree angle in order to keep the elbows in a neutral position. \n3. Don’t allow the dumbbells to collide at the top of each rep - bouncing them together may cause you to lose stability within the shoulder and injure yourself. \n4. Squeeze the dumbbells as tight as possible to improve a phenomenon known as “irradiation” which promotes greater shoulder stability.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_36">Incline Bench Press</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_36">Instructions \n1. Lie flat on an incline bench and set your hands just outside of shoulder width. \n2. Set your shoulder blades by pinching them together and driving them into the bench. \n3. Take a deep breath and allow your spotter to help you with the lift off in order to maintain tightness through your upper back. \n4. Let the weight settle and ensure your upper back remains tight after lift off. \n5. Inhale and allow the bar to descend slowly by unlocking the elbows. \n6. Lower the bar in a straight line to the base of the sternum (breastbone) and touch the chest. \n7. Push the bar back up in a straight line by pressing yourself into the bench, driving your feet into the floor for leg drive, and extending the elbows. \n8. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Technique first, weight second - no one cares how much you bench if you get injured. \n2. Keep the bar in line with your wrist and elbows and ensure it travels in a straight line. In order to keep the wrist straight, try to position the bar as low in the palm as possible while still being able to wrap the thumb. \n3. If you want to keep more tension through the triceps and chest, stop each repetition just short of lockout at the top.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_37">Push-Ups</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_37">Instructions \n1. Assume a quadruped position on the floor with your hands under your shoulders, toes tucked, and knees under hips. \n2. Extend one leg at a time and assume a pushup position with the legs straight, elbows extended, and head in a neutral position looking at the floor. \n3. Slowly descend to the floor by retracting the shoulder blades and unlocking the elbows. \n4. Descend until the upper arms are parallel or your chest touches the floor. \n5. Push back to the starting point by extending the elbows and driving your palms into the floor. \n6. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Your arms should resemble an arrow in the bottom position, not a “T”. \n2. Your spine should remain rigid throughout the entire exercise, think of the pushup as a moving plank. \n3. Squeeze your glutes and brace your abs before descending in order to keep the ribcage neutral. \n4. Keep the chin down and don’t look forward. \n5. Imagine you’re trying to push your thumbs together while completing the movement, this will improve activation of the pecs.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_38">Reverse Barbell Wrist Curl Over Bench</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_38">Instructions \n1. Set up for the reverse wrist curl by selecting a light barbell and kneeling in front of a flat bench. \n2. Grasp the barbell with a reverse grip (palms facing down) at around shoulder width apart. \n3. Place your forearms and elbows on the bench so that both wrists are hanging over the edge of the bench. This is the starting position. \n4. Begin curling your wrist upwards. Focus on moving only the wrists, while keeping your forearms as still as possible. \n5. Lower your wrists back down to the starting position and repeat for the desired reps.  \n\nTips \n1. A light weight should be used with proper technique. It doesn\'t take heavy weight to make this exercise effective. \n2. Use full range of motion - lowing the bar and raising the bar as far as comfortably possible.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_39">Barbell Wrist Curl Over Bench</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_39">Instructions \n1. Grasp a barbell at shoulder width apart using an underhand grip (palms facing up) and sit down in front of a flat bench. \n2. Kneel down and rest the back of your forearms on top of the bench so that your wrists are just off the end of it. \n3. Bending only at the wrists, let the barbell drop as far as possible. This is the starting position for the exercise. \n4. Slowly raise the bar up as far as possible squeezing the forearm muscles at the top of the movement. \n5. Pause, and then slowly lower the barbell back to the starting position. \n6. Repeat for desired reps. \n\nTips \n1. A light weight should be used with proper technique. It doesn\'t take heavy weight to make this exercise effective. \n2. Keep the rep timing slow, and pause/squeeze the forearms for a count of two at the top of the movement for added intensity. \n3. Use a full range of motion by allowing the weight to drop as far as possible at the bottom of the movement.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_40">Standing Wrist Curl Behind Back</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_40">Instructions \n1. Begin the exercise by selecting a barbell weight and holding it behind your back using an underhand grip (palms facing out). Your hands should be placed around shoulder width apart. \n2. Stand straight up with your feet shoulder width apart and look straight forward. Bending only at the wrists, let the barbell drop as far as possible. This is the starting position for the exercise. \n3. Slowly raise the barbell up as far as possible squeezing the forearm muscles at the top of the movement. Only your wrists should be moving. \n4. Pause, and then slowly lower the barbell back to the starting position. \n5. Repeat for desired reps. \n\nTips \n1. A light weight should be used with proper technique. It doesn\'t take heavy weight to make this exercise effective. \n2. Keep the rep timing slow, and pause/squeeze the forearms for a count of two at the top of the movement for added intensity. \n3. Use a full range of motion by allowing the weight to drop as far as possible at the bottom of the movement. \n4. It would be wise to have a training partner either hand you the bar or use a rack to pick it up.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_41">Barbell Lunge</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_41">Instructions \n1. It is safest to perform the lunge inside a squat rack. Set up for the exercise by setting the barbell to just below shoulder height and loading the weight you want to use. \n2. Stand under the bar with your feet at about shoulder width apart. Position the bar so that it is resting on the muscles on the top of your back, not on the back of your neck. The bar should feel comfortable. If it doesn\'t, try adding some padding to the bar. \n3. Now take your hands over the back and grip the bar with a wide grip for stability. \n4. You should now bend at the knees and straighten your back in preparation to take the weight off the rack. Keeping your back straight and eyes up, push up through the legs and take the weight off the rack. \n5. Take a few steps back and stabilize yourself. You are now in the starting position. \n6. Step forward with your left leg while maintaining your balance and squat down through your hips. Keep your torso straight and head up. Don\'t allow your knee to track out over your toes. \n7. Push yourself back to the starting position by using your heal to drive you. \n8. Repeat this movement with your right leg and then repeat for desired reps. \n\nTips \n1. Never allow your knees to track out over your toes during this movement. Doing so will place undue stress on the knee joints.  \n2. This exercise requires a good deal of balance and is not recommended for those with balance issues. Begin by using a very light weight to first perfect the movement. \n3. Keep your head up and back straight throughout the exercise. Never allow your back to round. </string>

    <string name="ex_name_42">Barbell Back Squat</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_42">Instructions \n1. Set up for the exercise by setting the barbell to just below shoulder height and loading the weight you want to use. \n2. Stand under the bar with your feet at about shoulder width apart. \n3. Position the bar so that it is resting on the muscles on the top of your back, not on the back of your neck. The bar should feel comfortable. If it doesn\'t, try adding some padding to the bar. \n4. Now take your hands over the back and grip the bar with a wide grip for stability. \n5. You should now bend at the knees and straighten your back in preparation to take the weight off the rack. \n6. Keeping your back straight and eyes up, push up through the legs and take the weight off the rack. \n7. Take a small step back and stabilize yourself. \n8. Keeping your eyes facing forward slowly lower your body down. Don\'t lean forward as you come down. Your buttocks should come out and drop straight down. \n9. Squat down until your thighs are parallel with the floor, and then slowly raise your body back up by pushing through your heels. \n10. Do not lock the knees out when you stand up, and then repeat the movement. \n\nTips  \nCommon mistakes when squatting: \n1. Rounding the lower back: It\'s crucially important that you keep a straight back when you squat! You can ensure your back is straight by keeping your eyes facing forward, chest out, shoulder blades back, and back arched. Keep your core muscles tensed throughout the movement to help hold your back in place. \n2. Pushing from the balls of your feet: This puts unnecessary strain on joints and tendons. Always push up through your heels. Curling up your toes can help you get the technique right. \n3. Leaning forward: This happens when your hips move up faster than your shoulders. To prevent this keep the rep timing slow and controlled and stick your buttocks out as you go down. \n4. Knees come too far forward: When you squat down, your hips should be dropping straight down, not coming forward. Using a light weight, perfect your form standing side on to a mirror. Your knees should never track out and over your toes. \n5. Not squatting deep enough: Using squats to their full potential requires squatting down at least until your thighs are around parallel to the floor. \n6. Knees in or out: Don\'t point your knees in or out when you\'re lowering or pushing the weight. This puts unnecessary strain on the knee joints. \n7. Looking down: As soon as you look down your back rounds, simple as that.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_43">Dumbbell Lunge</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_43">Instructions \n1. Choose a pair of dumbbells and stand up straight with a slight bend in your knees. \n2. Hold the dumbbells down at your sides. You are now in the starting position. \n3. Step forward with your left leg while maintaining your balance and squat down through your hips. \n4. Keep your torso straight and head up. Don\'t allow your knee to track out over your toes. \n5. Push yourself back to the starting position by using your heal to drive you. \n6. Repeat this movement with your right leg and then repeat for desired reps. \n\nTips \n1. Never allow your knees to track out over your toes during this movement. Doing so will place undue stress on the knee joints. \n2. This exercise requires a good deal of balance and is not recommended for those with balance issues. \n3. Keep your head up and back straight throughout the exercise. Never allow your back to round.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_44">Barbell Front Squat</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_44">Instructions \n1. Position the safety stops at roughly waist height and then place the bar just underneath shoulder height. \n2. Position the hands just outside of shoulder width, step underneath the bar, and allow it to sit on the shoulders while driving the elbows high in front of the body. \n3. Take a breath and unrack the bar by pushing your hips forward and extending your knees. \n4. Take 2-3 steps back and position your feet just inside of shoulder width. \n5. Sit directly between your legs by simultaneously bending your knees and pushing your hips back. \n6. Once your thighs reach parallel with the floor, begin to reverse the movement. \n7. Keep your abs braced and drive your feet through the floor. \n8. Finish the lift by exhaling as you fully extend the hips and knees. \n\nTips \n1. Toe angle is highly individual - experiment to see what feels best for you. \n2. You can use either 2 or 3 fingers when front squatting in the front rack position as it will take some stress off the wrist. \n3. In order to keep the torso upright, focus on driving the elbows up out of the hole. \n4. If you can’t get into a front rack position to front squat, then use the cross arm grip. \n5. Drive through the whole foot - you want 3 points of contact: big toe, little toe, and heel. \n6. Some forward translation of the knees over the toes is alright provided that the knees don’t deviate excessively inward or outward. Those with longer femurs will have to allow their knees to come farther forward if they want to remain upright.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_45">Good Morning</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_45">Instructions \n1. Set a bar just below shoulder height in a rack and adjust the safeties to just above hip height. \n2. Set your hands equidistant apart, step underneath, and position the bar on your traps (or slightly below if you prefer a low bar version). \n3. Begin the movement by unlocking your knees and hinging back into the hips while keeping your spine neutral. \n4. Drive through the whole foot as you extend the hip back to the starting position. \n5. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Range of motion in the lift will largely be determined by an individual’s mobility as well as their ability to maintain a neutral spine. \n2. Experiment with a “false” (i.e. thumbless) grip as this helps to eliminate elbow and wrist issues in some folks. \n3. Neck position is highly individual - Some prefer a neutral neck position (i.e. keeping the chin tucked throughout the lift) while others do well with looking slightly up. Here’s some factors to consider: \n   a. If you’re someone who is more globally extended (i.e. athletic background), then you will likely be able to keep a neutral position more effectively by packing the chin. \n   b. On the opposite end of the spectrum, if you tend to be more flexion dominant (especially in your thoracic spine - upper back) then it would behoove you to look up slightly as this will drive more extension.\n   c. Experiment with each and see which one works best for your individual anatomy and biomechanics.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_46">Leg Extensions</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_46">Instructions \n1. Select the desired resistance on the weight stack and insert the pin. \n2. Adjust the seat so that the knees are directly in line with the axis of the machine. \n3. Sit down and position your shins behind the pad at the base of the machine. \n4. Take a deep breath and extend your legs as you flex your quadriceps. \n5. As you lock out the knees, exhale to complete the repetition. \n6. Slowly lower your feet back to the starting position and repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Ensure the axis of rotation for the knee directly matches that of the machine. In other words, the point of rotation for the machine should be in line with your knee joint itself. If the knee is positioned too \nfar in front or behind the axis of rotation, there will be excessive stress added to the joint which could cause significant injury. \n2. Typically extensions should not be done excessively heavy due to the lack of hamstring co-contraction with the quads. When one occurs in isolation it could present an injury risk to the knee if done with excessive weight. \n3. Pointing the toes can help to enhance mind muscle connection.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_47">Leg Press</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_47">Instructions \n1. Load the machine with the desired weight and take a seat. \n2. Sit down and position your feet on the sled with a shoulder width stance. \n3. Take a deep breath, extend your legs, and unlock the safeties. \n4. Lower the weight under control until the legs are roughly 45 degrees or slightly below. \n5. Drive the weight back to the starting position by extending the knees but don’t forcefully lockout. \n6. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. To keep tension on the quads, keep the knees just shy of lockout. \n2. To emphasize the glutes more, push through the heels. \n3. To emphasize the quads more, push through the balls of the feet. \n4. Don’t allow the hips to posteriorly tilt and roll off the pad. \n5. Keep your low back flat against the pad throughout the movement. \n6. Maintain a neutral head position by not looking up or down excessively. \n7. Self spotting is possible by simply applying pressure to the knees with the hands. Use only when necessary. \n8. Toe angle is individual and will depend upon each individual’s hip anatomy and ankle mobility - experiment and adjust based upon feel.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_48">Lying Leg Curls</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_48">Instructions \n1. The lying leg curl is a great exercise to isolate the hamstrings. Set up for the leg curl by selecting the weight you want to use on the stack and adjusting the padding to suit your leg length. \n2. Lay face down on the machine. The padding should be positioned just above the back of your ankles. If it\'s higher than that, adjust the length. \n3. Tense up the hamstrings by taking the weight slightly off the stack. This is the starting position for the exercise. \n4. Squeeze the hamstrings and curl the weight up as far as possible. \n5. Squeeze the hamstring hard, and then slowly lower the weight back to the starting position. \n6. Repeat for desired reps. \n\nTips \n1. Common mistakes with the leg curl are; moving the weight up and down too fast and not using a full range of motion. \n2. Always control the weight throughout the set. Don\'t use momentum to move the weight up, and don\'t allow it to drop back down quickly. \n3. Always use a full range of motion by curling the weight up as far as possible and lowering it as far as possible without the weight dropping on the stack.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_49">Romanian Deadlift (AKA RDL)</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_49">Instructions \n1. Position the bar over the top of your shoelaces and assume a hip width stance. \n2. Assume a double overhand grip just outside of hip width and deadlift the weight into position at the top with the hips and knees locked out. \n3. Begin the RDL by pushing your hips back and hinging forward until the bar is just below knee height. \n4. Drive through the whole foot and focus on pushing the floor away. \n5. Return to the starting position and repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Range of motion in the lift will largely be determined by an individual’s mobility as well as their ability to maintain a neutral spine. Standing on a box or bench is likely counterproductive as most won’t have the mobility to control that much range of motion effectively. \n2. It is typically recommended that you utilize straps or hook grip when going excessively heavy if grip is the limiting factor as you could run into issues with the bar drifting if using mixed grip. \n3. Neck position is highly individual - Some prefer a neutral neck position (i.e. keeping the chin tucked throughout the lift) while others do well with looking slightly up. Here’s some factors to consider: \n   a. If you’re someone who is more globally extended (i.e. athletic background), then you will likely be able to keep a neutral position more effectively by packing the chin. \n   b. On the opposite end of the spectrum, if you tend to be more flexion dominant (especially in your thoracic spine - upper back) then it would behoove you to look up slightly as this will drive more extension. \n   c. Experiment with each and see which one works best for your individual anatomy and biomechanics.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_50">Dumbbell Stiff Leg Deadlift</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_50">Instructions \n1. Set up for the dumbbell stiff leg deadlift by choosing a pair of dumbbells and holding them down at your sides. \n2. Stand up straight with a slight bend in your knees and your feet around shoulder width apart. This is your starting position. \n3. Keep your back as straight as possible and bend over at the waist lowering the dumbbells over the tops of you feet. Your knees should be kept stationary during the movement. \n4. Focus on the stretch in your hamstrings, and continue to lower the dumbbells down as far as your hamstrings will let you comfortably. \n5. Now engage the hamstrings and begin to raise the dumbbells straight back up. Your eyes should be facing up and your shoulders back. This will prevent your lower back from rounding. \n6. Squeeze up through the glutes and hamstrings until you\'re standing straight up. \n7. Repeat for desired reps. \n\nTips \n1. You must keep your eyes looking up at all times. As soon as you look down at the floor your back will round! \n2. The dumbbells need to stay close to your body throughout the set. The further the dumbbells are from your body the more strain is on your lower back. \n3. Focus on stretching the hamstrings out as you lower the dumbbells and contracting them as you raise back up. The greater the mind-muscle connection the more you\'ll get out of this exercise. \n4. It\'s best to have your knees slightly bent during the set but fixed (ie: bend them slightly but keep them locked in the same place throughout the set). \n5. During the descent, to protect your lower back, keep your weight back on the heels. Do not let your weight shift forward onto the toes. If you find the your weight on the toes when at the bottom position of the exercise, you are performing it incorrectly.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_51">Seated Arnold Press</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_51">Instructions \n1. Set up an adjustable angle bench to 90 degrees and select the desired weight from the rack. \n2. Pick up the dumbbells from the floor using a neutral grip (palms facing in). Position the end of the dumbbells on your knees and sit down on the bench. \n3. Using a safe and controlled motion, kick your knees up one at a time in order to get each dumbbell into place. \n4. Once the dumbbells are in place, rotate your palms so they are facing you. \n5. Take a deep breath then press the dumbbells overhead by extending the elbows and contracting the deltoids. \n6. As you press, rotate the dumbbells until your palms are facing forward. \n7. Slowly lower the dumbbells back to the starting position (the arms should be roughly 90 degrees or slightly lower depending upon limb lengths). \n8. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Keep your back flat against the pad throughout the duration of the exercise. \n2. Don’t allow the head to jut forward excessively. \n3. Drive the bicep to the ear and exhale as you press. \n4. If you sense any pressure in your neck or traps during the movement, look to address a lack of thoracic spine extension or shoulder flexion. \n5. Keeping the elbows slightly bent at the top and not locking out entirely will help to keep tension on the shoulders. \n6. If you can’t lock out the elbows overhead than it may indicate a lack of shoulder mobility due to poor scapular upward rotation.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_52">Bent Over Dumbbell Reverse Fly</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_52">Instructions \n1. Select the desired weight from the rack then take a few steps back into an open area. \n2. Hinge from the hips until your body is almost parallel to the floor and allow the arms to hang straight down from the shoulders with a neutral grip. \n3. Take a deep breath and pull the dumbbells towards the ceiling using the rear deltoids. \n4. Slowly lower the dumbbells back to the starting position under control. \n5. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Ideally we want to focus on the rear deltoids, not the scapular retractors so movement at the shoulder blade should be limited. Move the shoulder within the joint, not the shoulder blade on the ribcage. \n2. Keep the abs braced and don’t arch the back at the top of the movement. \n3. If you can’t hinge to 90 degrees, then hinge as far as comfortably possible while completing the exercise. Or, you could also take a seated position to complete the exercise as well. \n4. If you experience shoulder pain during the movement then it may be beneficial to rotate the dumbbells until the thumbs are pointing away from one another and the palms are facing forward. This is also known as a supinated grip and will externally rotate the shoulder. \n5. Don’t jut your head forward during the movement - this about stimulation for a small muscle group. Focus during the movement and don’t just rely on momentum. \n6. Allow the arms to move freely but don’t lock out the elbows.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_53">Seated Dumbbell Press</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_53">Instructions \n1. Set up an adjustable angle bench to 90 degrees and select the desired weight from the rack. \n2. Pick up the dumbbells from the floor using a neutral grip (palms facing in). Position the end of the dumbbells on your knees and sit down on the bench. \n3. Using a safe and controlled motion, kick your knees up one at a time in order to get each dumbbell into place. \n4. Once the dumbbells are in place, rotate your palms so they are facing forward. \n5. Take a deep breath then press the dumbbells overhead by extending the elbows and contracting the deltoids. \n6. Slowly lower the dumbbells back to the starting position (the arms should be roughly 90 degrees or slightly lower depending upon limb lengths). \n7. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Keep your back flat against the pad throughout the duration of the exercise. \n2. Don’t allow the head to jut forward excessively. \n3. Drive the bicep to the ear and exhale as you press. \n4. If you sense any pressure in your neck or traps during the movement, look to address a lack of thoracic spine extension or shoulder flexion. \n5. Keeping the elbows slightly bent at the top and not locking out entirely will help to keep tension on the shoulders. \n6. If you can’t lock out the elbows overhead than it may indicate a lack of shoulder mobility due to poor scapular upward rotation.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_54">Standing Dumbbell Front Raise</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_54">Instructions \n1. Choose a pair of dumbbells and stand up straight with your feet at around shoulder width apart. \n2. Hold the dumbbells with your arms fully extended down by your thighs in front of you body. \n3. Use an overhand grip (palms facing your body). Hold the dumbbells roughly 4 inches off of your body. This is the starting position. \n4. Begin by raising your arms straight out in front of you body with your palms facing the floor. Keep a slight bend in your elbow. \n5. Moving only at the shoulders and keeping your body as still as possible, continue raising the dumbbells out in front of you until your arms are just above parallel to the floor. \n6. Pause for a brief moment at the top of the movement, and slowly lower the dumbbells back to the starting position. \n7. Repeat for desired reps. \n\nTips \n1. Practice good form with a light weight. \n2. Focus on moving only at the shoulders. The rest of your body should be kept as still as possible and your arms should hold the same form throughout the movement. \n3. Use slow and controlled movement - avoid \"swinging\" the weights up and dropping them quickly.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_55">Dumbbell Lateral Raise</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_55">Instructions \n1. The dumbbell lateral raise is a good exercise for building width in your upper body which gives you the \"V\" shape. Grab a set of dumbbells and stand straight up with the dumbbells at your sides. \n2. Your palms should be facing your body. You should be holding the dumbbells slightly off your body, as this keeps the tension on the side delts. This is your starting position for the exercise. \n3. To execute, slowly raise the dumbbells up to around shoulder height. It\'s important that you do not let your wrists go above your elbows while raising the weight, as this will take the work off the side delts and put it on the front delts. \n4. Pause at the top of the movement, and then slowly lower the weight back to the starting position. \n5. Do not let the dumbbells touch your body, and then raise them for the next rep. \n\nTips \n1. The dumbbell lateral raise is one of those exercises that so many people do incorrectly. First, this is an isolation exercise, so you should be focusing on stretch and muscle contraction, not using heavy weights. \n2. Second, you MUST keep your rep timing slow and controlled. So many people use momentum to swing heavy weights up, and this is not going to get you the best results from the dumbbell lateral raise. \n3. Third, it very important that your elbows stay above your wrists. If your wrists come up too far, the focus comes off your side delts and onto your front delts. A good trick to ensure this does not happen is to tilt the dumbbells down as if you were pouring a jug of water as you raise them up. This makes it very hard to raise the wrists higher than the elbows. \n4. And finally, keep the side delts under stress for the whole set by not allowing the dumbbells to touch your body or \"hang\" at the bottom of the movement.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_56">Military Press Behind Neck</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_56">Instructions \n1. Adjust the barbell to just below shoulder height then load the desired weight onto the bar. \n2. Assume a shoulder width stance and place your hands outside of shoulder width with a pronated grip on the bar. \n3. Step underneath the bar and rack it on your traps. \n4. Take two steps back, inhale, brace, tuck the chin, and press the bar to lockout. \n5. Exhale once the bar gets to lockout and reverse the movement slowly while controlling the bar behind your neck. \n6. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. This is one of the most advanced shoulder pressing progressions and many won’t have the requisite shoulder mobility or core stability to complete the movement. \n*If you experience pain during the movement, considering implementing one of the other shoulder pressing variations such as landmine or dumbbell version. \n3. Reach tall at the top and don’t worry about keeping the shoulders packed down and back. \n4. Fight to control the bar from rolling your wrists into extension and think about “rolling your knuckles toward the ceiling.” \n5. Keep momentum out of the movement and don’t add any additional leg drive by flexing and extending the knees. \n6. Squeeze your glutes and brace your abs as you press. You shouldn’t be leaning back excessively as you press. \n7. Imagine you’re trying to look out a window at the top, your ears should be in line with your biceps. \n8. You can use a staggered stance to prevent the lower back from arching excessively but if you still can’t control the anterior core then consider using a half kneeling regression shown on the site.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_57">Machine Reverse Fly</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_57">Instructions \n1. Face the fly machine while seated with your chest against the pad and the handles positioned in front of your torso. \n2. Reach forward and grasp each handle with a pronated or neutral grip. \n3. Contract the rear delts while keeping the elbows bent and open the arms in a reverse fly motion. \n4. Slowly lower the handles back to the starting position and repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Ensure the movement comes entirely from the upper arm moving in the shoulder socket rather than scapular retraction. \n2. The shoulder blades shouldn’t move drastically - there may be some end range retraction but nothing drastic. \n3. Don’t allow the head to jut forward as the arms open.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_58">Standing Military Press (AKA Overhead Press)</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_58">Instructions \n1. Adjust the barbell to just below shoulder height then load the desired weight onto the bar. \n2. Assume a shoulder width stance and place your hands at (or just outside of) shoulder width with a pronated grip on the bar. \n3. Step underneath the bar and unrack it while keeping the spine in a neutral position. \n4. Take two steps back, inhale, brace, tuck the chin, then press the bar to lockout overhead. \n5. Exhale once the bar gets to lockout and reverse the movement slowly while controlling the bar back to your chest. \n6. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Reach tall at the top and don’t worry about keeping the shoulders packed down and back. \n2. Allow the elbows to rotate and point outward at the top of the movement but tuck them tight to the ribcage at the bottom. \n3. Fight to control the bar from rolling your wrists into extension and think about “rolling your knuckles toward the ceiling.” \n4. Keep momentum out of the movement and don’t add any additional leg drive by flexing and extending the knees. \n5. Squeeze your glutes and brace your abs as you press. You shouldn’t be leaning back excessively as you press. \n6. Imagine you’re trying to look out a window at the top, your ears should be in line with your biceps. \n7. If your shoulders are bothering you during the movement, consider experimenting with a wider grip or utilizing some of the vertical pressing progressions listed on the site. \n8. You can use a staggered stance to prevent the lower back from arching excessively but if you still can’t control the anterior core then consider using a half kneeling regression shown on the site.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_59">EZ Bar Upright Barbell Row</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_59">Instructions \n1. Grasp a barbell with an overhand grip that is slightly less than shoulder width. The bar should be resting on the top of your thighs with your arms extended and a slight bend in your elbows. Your back should also be straight. This will be your starting position. \n2. Now exhale and use the sides of your shoulders to lift the bar, raising your elbows up and to the side. Keep the bar close to your body as you raise it. Continue to lift the bar until it nearly touches your chin. Tip: Your elbows should drive the motion, and should always be higher than your forearms. Remember to keep your torso stationary and pause for a second at the top of the movement. \n3. Lower the bar back down slowly to the starting position. Inhale as you perform this portion of the movement. \n4. Repeat for the recommended amount of repetitions. \n\nVariations: This exercise can also be performed using a straight bar attached to a low pulley and it can also be performed using dumbbells, though this later exercise should be reserved by people that are well familiarized with correct execution. \n\nTips \n1. Keep the elbows high but don’t allow the upper arm to go past parallel as this may increase the risk of impingement. \n2. If you experience pain in the shoulders during the movement than it may require a slight squeeze of the traps to elevate the shoulders and open up some of the subacromial space. \n3. Don’t allow your back to arch as you pull the barbell up. \n4. Extra momentum used during the movement can potentially shift the load to other compensatory muscles so try to limit excessive movement if possible. \n5. As you drive the elbows high, ensure the head doesn\’t jut forward.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_60">Close Grip Barbell Bench Press</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_60">Instructions \n1. Set up for the close grip chest press by adjusting the rack height (if adjustable) and loading the weight you want to use on the barbell. \n2. Lay back on the bench with your feet firmly on the floor. \n3. Grip the bar with an overhand grip (palms facing your feet) with your hands around 12 inches apart.  \n4. Take the barbell off the rack and hold it straight above your chest. Bend the elbows slightly to take the weight onto your chest/triceps. \n5. Slowly lower the bar to your middle chest. \n6. Pause, then slowly push the bar back to the starting position. Don\'t lock your elbows out! \n7. Repeat for desired reps. \n\nTips \n1. Focus on using your chest to move the weight. \n2. Keep the rep timing slow and control the weight - especially when lowering it. \n3. Start by using a light weight if you are new to this exercise.  \n4. The bar should be lowered to your middle chest ONLY.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_61">Close Grip Push Up</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_61">Instructions \n1. The close grip push up is a variation of the push up that focuses on hitting the triceps. Set up by placing your palms on the floor with your thumbs touching on another. \n2. Extend your legs back so that only your toes are touching the floor and your body is straight. \n3. Bend slightly at the elbows to keep tension in your triceps. \n4. Keeping your body straight, slowly lower yourself as far as possible without hitting the floor. \n5. Pause, and then push back up to the starting position without locking your elbows out. \n6. Repeat for desired reps. \n\nTips \n1. Keep your elbows tucked in at your side throughout the set. \n2. Don\'t lock your elbows out. This takes the tension off the triceps and makes the exercise less effective. \n3. The close grip push up is a good finishing exercise or a second exercise in a superset.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_62">Tricep Dips</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_62">Instructions \n1. Many people don\'t know that there are two ways to do dips. Focusing on your triceps, or focusing on your chest. This version of the dip hits the triceps hardest. Grasp the parallel dip bars with an inward grip. \n2. If the bars are adjustable, adjust them in to around shoulder width apart. \n3. Jump up of the floor and take your weight on the bars. \n4. The key to hitting your triceps on this version of the dip is to keep your body as straight as possible and don\'t lean forward. This may mean not crossing your legs and keeping them hanging down. \n5. Slowly lower yourself down, keeping your eyes facing forward. \n6. Lower until your elbow is at around the same height as your shoulder, and then raise your body back up without locking your arms at the top of the movement. \n7. Repeat for desired reps. \n\nTips \n1. Do not lower yourself down too far, as this can result in heavy strain on your shoulder joints and possible injury. \n2. Use the mind-muscle connection to focus on working your triceps throughout the movement. Squeeze your triceps hard at the top of the movement and feel the stretch on the way down. \n3. Do not lock your elbows out at the top of the movement. \n4. And finally, keep the rep timing slow for maximum results from this exercise.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_63">Standing Dumbbell Triceps Extension</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_63">Instructions \n1. To begin, stand up with a dumbbell held by both hands. Your feet should be about shoulder width apart from each other. Slowly use both hands to grab the dumbbell and lift it over your head until both arms are fully extended. \n2. The resistance should be resting in the palms of your hands with your thumbs around it. The palm of the hands should be facing up towards the ceiling. This will be your starting position. \n3. Keeping your upper arms close to your head with elbows in and perpendicular to the floor, lower the resistance in a semicircular motion behind your head until your forearms touch your biceps. Tip: The upper arms should remain stationary and only the forearms should move. Breathe in as you perform this step. \n4. Go back to the starting position by using the triceps to raise the dumbbell. Breathe out as you perform this step. \n5. Repeat for the recommended amount of repetitions. \n\nVariations \n1. Another way to perform this exercise is to use an e-z or straight bar instead in which case you will be holding the bar from the inside (around 5 inches between both hands) with the palms facing forward (pronated grip). \n2. There is also a bar that has parallel bars inside (often referred to as a triceps blaster) and this can also be used for this exercise. \n3. Finally, a low pulley cable with a rope attachment or bar (straight or e-z) attachment at the end can be used as well for variety purposes as well. \n\nTips \n1. Don’t overextend through the lumbar spine, keep your ribcage down by maintaining tension through the abs and glutes. \n2. Using a slow eccentric (lowering portion) of the exercise can help to improve tension and mind muscle connection. \n3. Keep the head in a fairly neutral position, don’t allow the neck to jut forward as this may place excessive pressure on the cervical spine.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_64">EZ-Bar Skullcrusher</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_64">Instructions \n1. Select your desired weight and sit on the edge of a flat bench. \n2. To get into position, lay back and keep the bar close to your chest. Once you are supine, press the weight to lockout. \n3. Lower the weights towards your head by unlocking the elbows and allowing the ez bar to drop toward your forehead or just above. \n4. Once your forearms reach parallel or just below, reverse the movement by extending the elbows while flexing the triceps to lockout the weight. \n5. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Don’t overextend through the lumbar spine as you lower the weight, keep some tension through the abdominals. \n2. Exhale as you extend the elbows and lockout the weight overhead. \n3. If you experience elbow pain during the movement, consider implementing a slight angle (incline or decline) or adjust elbow position (in versus out). \n4. You may slightly reduce tension through the ligamentous portions of the triceps during the movement by keeping the bar just above your head and not locking out directly over your line of sight.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_65">Standing Overhead EZ Bar Tricep Extension</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_65">Instructions \n1. Select the desired weight from the rack and stand in an open area. \n2. To get into position, reverse curl the bar to your chest and then press it straight overhead by locking out the triceps. \n3. Lower the weights towards your shoulders by unlocking the elbows and allowing the ez bar to drop behind your head. \n4. Once your forearms reach parallel or just below, reverse the movement by extending the elbows while flexing the triceps to lockout the weight. \n5. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Don’t overextend through the lumbar spine, keep your ribcage down by maintaining tension through the abs and glutes. \n2. Using a slow eccentric (lowering portion) of the exercise can help to improve tension and mind muscle connection. \n3. Keep the head in a fairly neutral position, don’t allow the neck to jut forward as this may place excessive pressure on the cervical spine.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_66">Standing Overhead EZ Bar Tricep Extension</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_66">Instructions \n1. Select the desired weight from the rack and stand in an open area. \n2. To get into position, reverse curl the bar to your chest and then press it straight overhead by locking out the triceps. \n3. Lower the weights towards your shoulders by unlocking the elbows and allowing the ez bar to drop behind your head. \n4. Once your forearms reach parallel or just below, reverse the movement by extending the elbows while flexing the triceps to lockout the weight. \n5. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. Don’t overextend through the lumbar spine, keep your ribcage down by maintaining tension through the abs and glutes. \n2. Using a slow eccentric (lowering portion) of the exercise can help to improve tension and mind muscle connection. \n3. Keep the head in a fairly neutral position, don’t allow the neck to jut forward as this may place excessive pressure on the cervical spine.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_67">Reverse Grip Cable Tricep Pushdown</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_67">Instructions \n1. Attach a straight bar to a cable stack as high as possible and assume a standing position. \n2. Grasp the straight bar with a supinated grip (palms facing up) and lean forward slightly by hinging at the hips. \n3. Initiate the movement by extending the elbows and flexing the triceps. \n4. Pull the handle downward until the elbows are almost locked out and then slowly lower under control back to the starting position. \n5. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. If you want to keep more tension in the triceps, don’t lock the elbows out entirely. \n2. Imagine there’s a screw running through your elbow and don’t allow them to move in front of the body as you extend at the bottom of the movement. \n3. Experiment with static elbow positioning throughout the lift - some may find that they get a better stretch in the bottom portion of the movement by allowing their elbows to drift behind the body during the eccentric portion of the movement (similar to a drag curl). \n4. Ensure the shoulder blades don’t tilt forward as you extend the elbows.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_68">Standing Overhead Tricep Extension with rope</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_68">Instructions \n1. Set up for the exercise by attaching a rope to the low pulley of a pulley cable machine and selecting the weight you want to use on the stack. \n2. Facing away from the pulley, grab the rope behind your neck with a neutral grip (palms facing in) keeping your hands close together as stand straight up with a slight bend in your knees. This will lift the weight slightly from the stack. \n3. Keep your feet around shoulder width apart. Your forearms arms should be parallel to the floor at this point and your elbows should be pointed at the ceiling. \n4. You should be grasping the rope behind your head. You are now in the starting position. \n5. Moving only at your elbow joints slowly push the rope straight up until your arms are fully extended. As you push, spread the rope out until your hands are around shoulder width apart at the peak of the movement.   \n6. Pause, and then slowly bring the rope back to the starting position allowing your hands to reunite. \n7. Repeat this movement for desired reps.  \n\nTips \n1. Focus on moving the weight with your triceps, keeping control of the weight as you slowly lower the weight stack back to the starting position. \n2. Keep your body as still as possible, moving only your forearms. \n3. Keep your head up and look straight ahead throughout the movement.</string>

    <string name="ex_name_69">Triceps Pushdown</string>
    <string name="ex_desc_69">Instructions \n1. Attach a straight or angled bar to a cable stack as high as possible and assume a standing position. \n2. Grasp the straight or angled bar with a pronated grip (palms facing down) and lean forward slightly by hinging at the hips. \n3. Initiate the movement by extending the elbows and flexing the triceps. \n4. Pull the handle downward until the elbows are almost locked out and then slowly lower under control back to the starting position. \n5. Repeat for the desired number of repetitions. \n\nTips \n1. If you want to keep more tension in the triceps, don’t lock the elbows out entirely. \n2. Imagine there’s a screw running through your elbow and don’t allow them to move in front of the body as you extend at the bottom of the movement. \n3. Experiment with static elbow positioning throughout the lift - some may find that they get a better stretch in the bottom portion of the movement by allowing their elbows to drift behind the body during the eccentric portion of the movement (similar to a drag curl). \n4. Ensure the shoulder blades don’t tilt forward as you extend the elbows.</string>

    <string name="Abs">Abs</string>
    <string name="Back">Back</string>
    <string name="Biceps">Biceps</string>
    <string name="Calf">Calf</string>
    <string name="Chest">Chest</string>
    <string name="Forearms">Forearms</string>
    <string name="Legs">Legs</string>
    <string name="Shoulders">Shoulders</string>
    <string name="Triceps">Triceps</string>

    <string name="day">Day</string>
    <string name="round">Round</string>
    <string name="day1">2 days per week</string>
    <string name="day2">3 days per week</string>
    <string name="day3">4 days per week</string>
    <string name="restorePurchases">Restore Purchases</string>
    <string name="textUpgrade">Upgrade to Premium version to unlock New 50 Exercises and remove Ads.</string>
    <string name="upgrade">UPGRADE NOW</string>
    <string name="one_day_ADS1">1-Day NO ADS</string>
    <string name="one_day_ADS2">SPONSORED VIDEO</string>

    <string name="free">FREE</string>
    <string name="tell_friend">Tell a Friend</string>
    <string name="send_feedback">Send Feedback</string>
    <string name="facebook">Share app on Facebook</string>
    <string name="rate_app">Rate us</string>
    <string name="twitter">Share app on Twitter</string>
    <string name="ic_googleplay">Our other apps</string>
    <string name="ic_settings_">Settings</string>
    <string name="social_follow">Stay connected with VGFIT</string>
    <string name="daily_reminder">Daily reminder</string>
    <string name="frequency">Frequency</string>
    <string name="after_days">After %1$s days of inactivity</string>
    <string name="units">Units</string>
    <string name="menu_bt">Menu Button</string>
    <string name="success">Success!</string>
    <string name="reminder">Reminder</string>
    <string name="purch_restored">In-App purchases were restored</string>

    <string name="work_1">Beginner Fitness</string>
    <string name="work_2">Body Transformer Fitness</string>
    <string name="work_3">General Fitness</string>
    <string name="work_4">Antagonist Muscles</string>
    <string name="work_5">Same Muscle</string>
    <string name="work_6">Trisets</string>
    <string name="work_2header">Supersets</string>
    <string name="work_1header">Workout</string>


    <string name="resetKey">Reset</string>
    <string name="startKey">Start</string>
    <string name="pauseKey">Pause</string>
    <string name="resumeKey">Resume</string>
    <string name="intervalsKey">Intervals</string>
    <string name="myWorkoutsKey">My workouts</string>
    <string name="editKey">Edit</string>
    <string name="roundsKey">Rounds</string>
    <string name="doneKey">Done</string>
    <string name="worktimekey">Work time</string>
    <string name="resttimekey">Rest time</string>
    <string name="currentsetkey">Current settings</string>
    <string name="minkey">Min</string>
    <string name="seckey">Sec</string>

    <string name="enter_text">Enter text message</string>
    <string name="exercise">Exercise</string>
    <string name="muscle">Muscle</string>
    <string name="timer">Timer</string>
    <string name="ex_cat_88">Аll</string>


    <string name="reps1_1_1">3 sets of 12,12,12 reps</string>
    <string name="reps1_1_4">50 reps</string>
    <string name="reps1_1_7">3 sets of 12,12,12 reps</string>
    <string name="reps1_1_10">2 sets of 12-10 reps</string>
    <string name="reps1_1_28">3 sets of 15,12,10 reps</string>
    <string name="reps1_1_34">3 sets of 25,25,25 reps</string>

    <string name="reps1_2_2">3 sets of 15,12,10 reps</string>
    <string name="reps1_2_27">3 sets of 15,12,10 reps</string>
    <string name="reps1_2_39">3 sets of 15,12,10 reps</string>
    <string name="reps1_2_42">3 sets of 25,25,25 reps</string>
    <string name="reps1_2_43">2 sets of 15,15 reps</string>
    <string name="reps1_2_48">3 sets of 15,12,10 reps</string>

    <string name="reps1_3_3">2 sets of 15,15 reps</string>
    <string name="reps1_3_15">3 sets of 25,25,25 reps</string>
    <string name="reps1_3_52">3 sets of 15,12,10 reps</string>
    <string name="reps1_3_58">3 sets of 15,12,10 reps</string>
    <string name="reps1_3_62">3 sets of 15,12,10 reps</string>
    <string name="reps1_3_64">3 sets of 15,12,10 reps</string>

    <string name="reps2_4_1">3 sets of 25-30 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_4_2">3 sets of 12-15 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_4_3">3 sets of 12-15 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_4_4">3 sets of 12-15 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_4_10">3 sets of 12-15 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_4_13">3 sets of 25-30 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_4_60">3 sets of 12-15 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_4_64">3 sets of 12-15 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_4_69">3 sets of 12-15 reps</string>

    <string name="reps2_5_1">3 sets of 25-30 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_5_2">3 sets of 25-30 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_5_3">3 sets of 12-15 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_5_15">3 sets of 12-15 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_5_20">3 sets of 12-15 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_5_22">3 sets of 12-15 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_5_28">3 sets of 25-30 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_5_33">3 sets of 12-15 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_5_35">3 sets of 25-30 reps</string>

    <string name="reps2_6_1">3 sets of 25-30 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_6_2">3 sets of 25-30 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_6_3">3 sets of 12-15 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_6_41">3 sets of 25-30 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_6_42">4 sets of 12-15 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_6_48">3 sets of 25-30 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_6_52">3 sets of 25-30 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_6_55">3 sets of 25-30 reps</string>
    <string name="reps2_6_56">3 sets of 25-30 reps</string>

    <string name="reps3_7_3">4 sets of 15,12,10,8 reps</string>
    <string name="reps3_7_8">4 sets of 15,12,10,8 reps</string>
    <string name="reps3_7_15">4 sets of 15,12,10,8 reps</string>
    <string name="reps3_7_27">4 sets of 25,25,25   reps</string>
    <string name="reps3_7_28">4 sets of 15,12,10,8 reps</string>
    <string name="reps3_7_42">4 sets of 15,12,10,8 reps</string>
    <string name="reps3_7_55">4 sets of 15,12,10,8 reps</string>
    <string name="reps3_7_60">4 sets of 15,12,10,8 reps</string>

    <string name="reps3_8_1">3 sets of 12,10,8 reps</string>
    <string name="reps3_8_4">4 sets of 15,12,10,8 reps</string>
    <string name="reps3_8_21">4 sets of 15,12,10,8 reps</string>
    <string name="reps3_8_27">4 sets of 15,12,10,8 reps</string>
    <string name="reps3_8_35">3 sets of 25,25,25   reps</string>
    <string name="reps3_8_47">3 sets of 15,12,10,8 reps</string>
    <string name="reps3_8_53">4 sets of 15,12,10,8 reps</string>
    <string name="reps3_8_62">4 sets of 15,12,10,8 reps</string>

    <string name="reps3_9_3">4 sets of 15,12,10,8 reps</string>
    <string name="reps3_9_5">4 sets of 15,12,10,8 reps</string>
    <string name="reps3_9_17">4 sets of 25,25,25   reps</string>
    <string name="reps3_9_27">4 sets of 15,12,10,8 reps</string>
    <string name="reps3_9_28">4 sets of 15,12,10,8 reps</string>
    <string name="reps3_9_35">3 sets of 15,12,10   reps</string>
    <string name="reps3_9_41">4 sets of 15,12,10,8 reps</string>
    <string name="reps3_9_52">4 sets of 15,12,10,8 reps</string>

    <string name="buy">Buy</string>
    <string name="subscription_info">Your subscription renew within 24-hours before yhe subscription period ends, you will be charged through your Google Play account. Manage your subscription in Menu. By continuing you accept our <a href="https://vgfit.com/privacy">Privacy Policy</a> and <a href="https://vgfit.com/terms"> Terms of Service. </a> <a href="http://play.google.com/store/account/subscriptions">Manage subscriptions.</a> </string>

    <string name="nutrition">Nutrition</string>
    <string name="nutritionPlanName1">Build muscle</string>
    <string name="nutritionPlanName2">Lean body</string>
    <string name="_3_days_for_free">7-day Free Trial</string>
    <string name="new_workoutsN">NEW\nworkouts</string>
    <string name="title_11">Exercises</string>
    <string name="one_week">1 week for Free</string>
    <!--<string name="new_workoutsN">Yoga\nClasses</string>-->
    <string name="week_after">/week after</string>
    <string name="month_after">/month after</string>
    <string name="year_after">/year after</string>
    <string name="free_trial">3-day\nFree Trial</string>
    <string name="month">/mo</string>
    <string name="year">/year</string>
    <string name="one_time_payment"> one time payment</string>
    <string name="get_lifetime_access">GET LIFETIME ACCESS</string>
    <string name="get_workouts_courses_with_powerful_support">Get 100% ready workouts courses with powerful support!</string>
    <string name="only_now">Only now</string>
    <string name="start_your_positive_transformation_today">Start your positive transformation today!</string>
    <string name="monthly_slim">MONTHLY</string>
    <string name="try_it_now">TRY IT NOW</string>
    <string name="_3_day_nfree_trial">3-day \nFree Trial</string>
    <string name="_7_day_nfree_trial">7-day\nFree Trial</string>
    <string name="after">after</string>
    <string name="nutrition_plans">Nutrition Plans</string>
    <string name="executing">Executing</string>

    <string name="subscription_terms">We currently offer auto-renewing subscription option: <b> %s </b>. By subscribing, you get unlimited access to 111 poses and 19 yoga classes.\n\nThese prices are for United States customers. Pricing in other countries may vary and actual charges may be converted to your actual currency depending on the country of residence.\n\nYour subscription will automatically renew at the end of each term and your creditcard will be charged through your iTunes account. You can turn off auto-renew at any time from your account settings but refunds will not be provided for any unused portion of the term. Note that, if you wish to avoid auto-renewal, you must turn it off at least 24 hours prior to the end of the current period. That\'s how it works!\n\nWe take the satisfaction and security of our customers very seriously. Read our terms of service at  <a href="https://vgfit.com/terms"> https://vgfit.com/terms </a> and our privacy policy at <a href="https://vgfit.com/privacy">https://vgfit.com/privacy</a>\n\nTo manage your subscriptions see this link for a step by step guide: <a href="https://support.google.com/googleplay/answer/7018481">Subscription on Google Play</a></string>
    <string name="subscribe_year">%s days of free trial followed by %s per Year</string>
    <string name="subscribe_month">%s days of free trial followed by %s per Month</string>
    <string name="subscribe_week">%s days of free trial followed by %s per Week</string>


<!--   VGFIT Localization-->

    <string name="strenght">Strength</string>
    <string name="endurance">Endurance</string>
    <string name="mobility">Mobility</string>
    <string name="focused">Focused</string>

    <string name="strenght_description">GET STRONG AND \n BUILD LEAN MUSCLE"</string>
    <string name="endurance_description">TOTAL BURNER AND \n CARDIO IMPROVING</string>
    <string name="mobility_description">GET FIT AND \n GAIN FLEXIBILITY"</string>
    <string name="focused_description">OVERALL FITNESS AND \n GAIN POWER</string>

    <string name="workouts">Workouts</string>
    <string name="exercises">Exercises</string>
    <string name="plans">Challenges</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="more">More</string>
    <string name="start_7_minutes">Start 7 Minutes</string>
    <string name="custom">custom</string>

    <string name="download_all_videos">Download all videos</string>
    <string name="downloading_videos">Downloading Videos</string>

    <string name="exercise_name">Exercise name</string>


    <string name="category_1">Abdominals</string>
    <string name="category_2">Back</string>
    <string name="category_3">Biceps</string>
    <string name="category_4">Chest</string>
    <string name="category_5">Legs</string>
    <string name="category_6">Shoulders</string>
    <string name="category_7">Triceps</string>
    <string name="category_8">Stretching</string>

    <string name="extra_workout_1">WEIGHT LOSS PLAN</string>
    <string name="extra_workout_2">BUILD MUSCLE PLAN</string>
    <string name="extra_workout_3">ABS &amp; CORE</string>
    <string name="extra_workout_4">FUNCTIONAL WORKOUTS</string>

    <string name="exercise_1">DUMBBELL-CRUNCH</string>
    <string name="exercise_2">MEDICINE BALL TOE TOUCH</string>
    <string name="exercise_3">BODYWEIGHT LEG RAISE WITH BALL</string>
    <string name="exercise_4">ALTERNATE HEEL TOUCH</string>
    <string name="exercise_5">BODYWEIGHT TOE TOUCH</string>
    <string name="exercise_6">BODYWEIGHT SIT-UP</string>
    <string name="exercise_7">BODYWEIGHT CRUNCH</string>
    <string name="exercise_8">WEIGHTED TWIST RUSSIAN</string>
    <string name="exercise_9">WEIGHTED CRUNCH</string>
    <string name="exercise_10">MODIFIED ELBOW TO KNEE CRUNCH </string>
    <string name="exercise_11">MODIFIED ELBOW TO KNEE CRUNCH SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_12">BODYWEIGHT SIDE BRIDGE</string>
    <string name="exercise_13">BODYWEIGHT SIDE BRIDGE SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_14">OBLIQUE V-UP SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_15">OBLIQUE V-UP</string>
    <string name="exercise_16">ONE LEG DROP</string>
    <string name="exercise_17">ONE LEG DROP SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_18">MEDICINE BALL PASS</string>
    <string name="exercise_19">CLAM</string>
    <string name="exercise_20">ROLLOUT</string>
    <string name="exercise_21">BODYWEIGHT PULL IN</string>
    <string name="exercise_22">BALL CRUNCH</string>
    <string name="exercise_23">SWISS BALL CRUNCH</string>
    <string name="exercise_24">MEDICINE BALL TWIST</string>
    <string name="exercise_25">STABILITY BALL TWIST (MEDICINE BALL)</string>
    <string name="exercise_26">DUMBBELL TWIST</string>
    <string name="exercise_27">BOSU DUMBBELL CRUNCH</string>
    <string name="exercise_28">BODYWEIGHT SIDE BRIDGE 1</string>
    <string name="exercise_29">BODYWEIGHT SIDE BRIDGE-1 SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_30">MEDICINE BALL TWIST 1</string>
    <string name="exercise_31">BODYWEIGHT LEG RAISE</string>
    <string name="exercise_32">BODYWEIGHT LEG RAISE 2</string>
    <string name="exercise_33">BARBELL ROLLOUT</string>
    <string name="exercise_34">ABDOMINAL LEG RAISE 2</string>
    <string name="exercise_35">BODYWEIGHT TRUNK ROTATION</string>
    <string name="exercise_36">BODYWEIGHT TWIST 2</string>
    <string name="exercise_37">BODYWEIGHT TOE TOUCH 2</string>
    <string name="exercise_38">BODYWEIGHT SCISSOR KICK</string>
    <string name="exercise_39">BICYCLE</string>
    <string name="exercise_40">BODYWEIGHT TOE TOUCH 3</string>
    <string name="exercise_41">BODYWEIGHT LEG RAISE 3</string>
    <string name="exercise_42">MEDICINE BALL TRUNK ROTATION</string>
    <string name="exercise_43">MEDICINE BALL CRUNCH</string>
    <string name="exercise_44">BODYWEIGHT SCISSOR HORIZONTAL</string>
    <string name="exercise_45">BODYWEIGHT SUPERMAN</string>
    <string name="exercise_46">BODYWEIGHT SUPERMAN ALTERNATING</string>
    <string name="exercise_47">BARBELL ROW</string>
    <string name="exercise_48">BODYWEIGHT SUPERMAN 3</string>
    <string name="exercise_49">BODYWEIGHT ARM AND LEG LIFT</string>
    <string name="exercise_50">BODYWEIGHT ARM AND LEG LIFT STRAIGHT</string>
    <string name="exercise_51">BODYWEIGHT ARM AND LEG LIFT STRAIGHT SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_52">BALANCE BALL PLANK</string>
    <string name="exercise_53">BALANCE BALL LOWER BACK</string>
    <string name="exercise_54">DUMBBELL PUSH-UP ROW</string>
    <string name="exercise_55">STABILITY BALL BRIDGE</string>
    <string name="exercise_56">DUMBBELL ROW</string>
    <string name="exercise_57">DUMBBELL DEADLIFT</string>
    <string name="exercise_58">BENCH PLANK</string>
    <string name="exercise_59">CHEER PLANK</string>
    <string name="exercise_60">DUMBBELL ROW 2</string>
    <string name="exercise_61">DUMBBELL ROW 2 SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_62">BARBELL GOOD MORNING</string>
    <string name="exercise_63">CURL BAR ROW</string>
    <string name="exercise_64">CURL BAR ROW 2</string>
    <string name="exercise_65">STABILITY BALL BICEPS CURL</string>
    <string name="exercise_66">DUMBBELL BICEPS CURL</string>
    <string name="exercise_67">CURL</string>
    <string name="exercise_68">DUMBBELL BICEPS CURL DOWN</string>
    <string name="exercise_69">DUMBBELL BICEPS CURL BENCH</string>
    <string name="exercise_70">DUMBBELL BICEPS CURL BENCH SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_71">DUMBBELL BICEPS NECURAL INCLINE</string>
    <string name="exercise_72">WRIST CURLS OUTSIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_73">DUMBBELL BICEPS BENCH CURL UP</string>
    <string name="exercise_74">DUMBBELL BICEPS SEATED CURL</string>
    <string name="exercise_75">EZ CURL BAR BICEPS CURL</string>
    <string name="exercise_76">BARBELL WRIST CURL</string>
    <string name="exercise_77">MEDICINE BALL PUSHUP</string>
    <string name="exercise_78">STEPPER PUSH-UP</string>
    <string name="exercise_79">BODYWEIGHT PUSH-UP STEPPER</string>
    <string name="exercise_80">BODYWEIGHT KNEE PUSH-UP KNEES</string>
    <string name="exercise_81">DUMBBELL FLOOR PRESS</string>
    <string name="exercise_82">BODYWEIGHT PUSH-UP INSIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_83">BODYWEIGHT PUSH-UP REGULAR</string>
    <string name="exercise_84">BODYWEIGHT PUSH-UP EXTENSION</string>
    <string name="exercise_85">BODYWEIGHT PUSH-UP TOUCH</string>
    <string name="exercise_86">BODYWEIGHT PUSH-UP </string>
    <string name="exercise_87">MEDICINE PUSH-UP SIDES</string>
    <string name="exercise_88">SUPPORT PUSH-UP</string>
    <string name="exercise_89">PUSH-UP WALKING</string>
    <string name="exercise_90">DUMBBELL PUSH-UP ROW 1</string>
    <string name="exercise_91">BOSU PUSH-UP SIDES</string>
    <string name="exercise_92">ROLLING PUSH-UP</string>
    <string name="exercise_93">STABILITY BALL CHEST PRESS</string>
    <string name="exercise_94">BENCH INCLINE PUSH-UP</string>
    <string name="exercise_95">STABILITY BALL FLY</string>
    <string name="exercise_96">DUMBBELL T-PUSH-UP</string>
    <string name="exercise_97">CHAIR BENT KNEES</string>
    <string name="exercise_98">PUSH-UP DUMBBELL EXTENSION</string>
    <string name="exercise_99">BAR BENCH PRESS INCLINE</string>
    <string name="exercise_100">BENCH PRES OERHAND</string>
    <string name="exercise_101">BENCH PRESS DECLINE</string>
    <string name="exercise_102">WIGHTED PUSH-UP</string>
    <string name="exercise_103">BENCH PRESS DECLINE UNDERHAND</string>
    <string name="exercise_104">DUMBBELL DECLINE BENCH PRESS</string>
    <string name="exercise_105">DUMBBELL DECLINE FLY</string>
    <string name="exercise_106">DUMBBELL OVERHAND BENCH PRESS</string>
    <string name="exercise_107">BENCH DECLINE PUSH-UP</string>
    <string name="exercise_108">DUMBBELL PULL-OVER</string>
    <string name="exercise_109">DUMBBELL FLY INCLINE BENCH</string>
    <string name="exercise_110">BODYWEIGHT PLANK LEG TOUCH 1</string>
    <string name="exercise_111">LYING HIP EXTENSION</string>
    <string name="exercise_112">STABILITY BALL LEG CARL</string>
    <string name="exercise_113">LYING HIP EXTENSION 1</string>
    <string name="exercise_114">LYING HIP EXTENSION-1 SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_115">BODYWEIGHT HOP</string>
    <string name="exercise_116">MEDICINE BALL LUNGE</string>
    <string name="exercise_117">DUMBBELL LUNGE FORWARD</string>
    <string name="exercise_118">MEDICINE BALL LUNGE 2</string>
    <string name="exercise_119">MEDICINE BALL SQUAT</string>
    <string name="exercise_120">MEDICINE BALL LUNGE 1</string>
    <string name="exercise_121">BODYWEIGHT LUNGE SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_122">BODYWEIGHT LUNGE SIDE SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_123">BOSU JUMP</string>
    <string name="exercise_124">BODYWEIGHT OPEN JUMP</string>
    <string name="exercise_125">BODYWEIGHT JUMPING JACKS</string>
    <string name="exercise_126">DUMBBELL LUNGE PRESS</string>
    <string name="exercise_127">BOSU KNEE UNDER RUNNING</string>
    <string name="exercise_128">BOSU LUNGE 2</string>
    <string name="exercise_129">BOSU JUMP SQUAD</string>
    <string name="exercise_130">BODYWEIGHT HIGHT KNEE JUMP</string>
    <string name="exercise_131">BARBELL SQUAD</string>
    <string name="exercise_132">BODYWEIGHT HIGHT KNEE BOXING</string>
    <string name="exercise_133">DUMBBELL CLEAN AND JERK</string>
    <string name="exercise_134">DUMBBELL SHRUG JUMP</string>
    <string name="exercise_135">DUMBBELL FRONT SQUAD</string>
    <string name="exercise_136">DUMBBELL LUNGE SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_137">DUMBBELL LUNGE SIDE SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_138">BODYWEIGHT SQUAD SINGLE LEG SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_139">BODYWEIGHT SQUAD SINGLE LEG</string>
    <string name="exercise_140">DUMBBELL LUNGE 2</string>
    <string name="exercise_141">DUMBBELL SNATCH</string>
    <string name="exercise_142">DUMBBELL BURPEE</string>
    <string name="exercise_143">DUMBBELL CLEAN AND JERK 1</string>
    <string name="exercise_144">BOSU SIT-UP</string>
    <string name="exercise_145">DUMBBELL SINGLE LEG DEADLIFT</string>
    <string name="exercise_146">DUMBBELL SINGLE LEG DEADLIFT SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_147">DUMBBELL SQUAD SPLIT</string>
    <string name="exercise_148">DUMBBELL SQUAD SPLIT SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_149">BARBELL SQUAD ASSISTED</string>
    <string name="exercise_150">BARBELL SPLIT SINGLE LEG</string>
    <string name="exercise_151">BARBELL SPLIT SINGLE LEG SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_152">LYING HIP EXTENSION CHAIR</string>
    <string name="exercise_153">BODYWEIGHT CALF RAISE</string>
    <string name="exercise_154">BENCH HIGH KNEE JUMP</string>
    <string name="exercise_155">BENCH HIGH KNEE JUMP 2</string>
    <string name="exercise_156">BENCH SIDE JUMP</string>
    <string name="exercise_157">BENCH LUNGE</string>
    <string name="exercise_158">DUMBBELL SQUAD JUMP</string>
    <string name="exercise_159">BENCH KNEE UP</string>
    <string name="exercise_160">BARBELL LUNGE BACKWARD</string>
    <string name="exercise_161">BARBELL SQUAD HACK</string>
    <string name="exercise_162">BARBELL LUNGE BACKWARD 2</string>
    <string name="exercise_163">BARBELL SQUAD OVERHEAD 2</string>
    <string name="exercise_164">BARBELL DEADLIFT SUMO</string>
    <string name="exercise_165">DUMBBELL SQUAT 2</string>
    <string name="exercise_166">BARBELL SQUAT 2</string>
    <string name="exercise_167">DUMBBELL ROTATING T EXTENSION</string>
    <string name="exercise_168">DUMBBELL ROTATING T EXTENSION SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_169">DUMBBELL PUSH UP PRESS</string>
    <string name="exercise_170">BODYWEIGHT PUSH-UP DRIVE BUMPER</string>
    <string name="exercise_171">BALANCE BALL FRONT RAISE 3</string>
    <string name="exercise_172">BALANCE BALL FRONT RAISE</string>
    <string name="exercise_173">FRONT PLATE RAISE</string>
    <string name="exercise_174">DUMBBELL CORKSCREW</string>
    <string name="exercise_175">DUMBBELL CORKSCREW SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_176">STANDING SCARECROW 2</string>
    <string name="exercise_177">DUMBBELL SHRUG</string>
    <string name="exercise_178">DUMBBELL REAR DELT ROW</string>
    <string name="exercise_179">REAR LATERAL RAISE</string>
    <string name="exercise_181">DUMBBELL SINGLE ARM</string>
    <string name="exercise_182">DUMBBELL SINGLE ARM SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_183">DUMBBELL SHOULDER PRESS</string>
    <string name="exercise_184">DUMBBELL LATERAL RAISE</string>
    <string name="exercise_185">DUMBBELL FRONT RAISE 2</string>
    <string name="exercise_186">DUMBBELL LATERAL RAISE 1</string>
    <string name="exercise_187">BENCH DUMBBELL ROW</string>
    <string name="exercise_188">BARBELL SPLIT JERK</string>
    <string name="exercise_189">BAR UPRIGHT ROW</string>
    <string name="exercise_190">BARBELL FRONT RAISE</string>
    <string name="exercise_191">PUSH PRESS</string>
    <string name="exercise_192">BARBELL BENT-OVER ROW</string>
    <string name="exercise_193">BODYWEIGHT PUSH-UP GRIP PLANCHE</string>
    <string name="exercise_194">ARMY PUSH UP</string>
    <string name="exercise_195">MEDICINE BALL PUSH UP</string>
    <string name="exercise_196">BOSU KNEELING PUSH UP</string>
    <string name="exercise_197">STABILITY BALL PUSH-UP</string>
    <string name="exercise_198">STABILITY BALL FRENCH PRESS</string>
    <string name="exercise_199">DUMBBELL ROW KICKBACK</string>
    <string name="exercise_200">STANDING SINGLE ARM TRICEPS EXTENSION</string>
    <string name="exercise_201">STANDING SINGLE ARM TRICEPS EXTENSION SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_202">BENCH DIP</string>
    <string name="exercise_203">OVERHEAD TRICEPS EXTENSION</string>
    <string name="exercise_204">LYING ONE-ARM EXTENSION</string>
    <string name="exercise_205">LYING ONE-ARM EXTENSION SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_206">LYING TRICEPS EXTENSION</string>
    <string name="exercise_207">OVERHEAD TRICEPS EXTENSION 1</string>
    <string name="exercise_208">STRETCH STANDING OVERHEAD ARMS</string>
    <string name="exercise_209">STRETCH NECK STANDING SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_210">STANDING BODY ARMS</string>
    <string name="exercise_211">STANDING BEHIND HEAD</string>
    <string name="exercise_212">STANDING BEHIND HEAD SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_213">STRETCH SQUAT TORSO TWIST</string>
    <string name="exercise_214">STRETCH STANDING LEGS ARMS</string>
    <string name="exercise_215">STRETCH STANDING HAND TO FOOT</string>
    <string name="exercise_216">STRETCH SITTING KNEE BENT</string>
    <string name="exercise_217">STRETCH ADDUCTORS STANDING</string>
    <string name="exercise_218">STRETCH ADDUCTORS STANDING SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_219">STRETCH LYING KNEE BENT</string>
    <string name="exercise_220">STRETCH LYING KNEE BENT SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_221">STRETCH KNEELING CHILD POSE</string>
    <string name="exercise_222">STRETCH LOWER BACK ARMS ASSIST</string>
    <string name="exercise_223">BODYWEIGHT SKI JUMP</string>
    <string name="exercise_224">BODYWEIGHT HIGH KNEES</string>
    <string name="exercise_225">JUMP SUMO 2</string>
    <string name="exercise_226">DOUBLE SQUAT</string>
    <string name="exercise_227">BODYWEIGHT PUSH-UP TOUCH 2</string>
    <string name="exercise_228">BODYWEIGHT BURPEE</string>
    <string name="exercise_229">BODYWEIGHT PUSH-UP 3</string>
    <string name="exercise_230">STEAM ENGINE</string>
    <string name="exercise_231">BODYWEIGHT LEG RAISE 1</string>
    <string name="exercise_232">CROW</string>
    <string name="exercise_233">PLANK</string>
    <string name="exercise_236">SINGLE DUMBBELL LUNGE SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_237">SINGLE DUMBBELL LUNGE SIDE SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_238">DUMBBELL SNATCH 1</string>
    <string name="exercise_239">DUMBBELL SNATCH-1 SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_240">STANDING SIDE SINGLE ARM</string>
    <string name="exercise_241">STANDING SIDE SINGLE ARM SECOND SIDE</string>
    <string name="exercise_242">SITTING BODY CURL</string>
    <string name="exercise_244">STRETCH ADDUCTORS SITTING</string>
    <string name="exercise_261">TOE TOUCH 3</string>
    <string name="exercise_262">DUMBBELL RISE</string>
    <string name="exercise_263">BENT-LEG V-UP</string>
    <string name="exercise_264">BODYWEIGHT TOE TOUCH 1</string>
    <string name="exercise_265">ABDOMINAL V-MOVE</string>
    <string name="exercise_266">BODYWEIGHT PLANK LEG TOUCH</string>
    <string name="exercise_267">EZ CURL BAR DEADLIFT</string>
    <string name="exercise_268">DUMBBELL BICEPS CURLS ON BENCH</string>
    <string name="exercise_269">BODYWEIGHT MOUNTAIN CLIMBERS</string>
    <string name="exercise_270">BOSU LEG CURL</string>
    <string name="exercise_271">MEDICINE BALL CRUNCH BENCH</string>
    <string name="exercise_272">BARBELL SQUAD 2</string>
    <string name="exercise_273">DUMBBELL CALF RAISE</string>
    <string name="exercise_274">BARBELL CALF RAISE</string>
    <string name="exercise_275">PUSH UP ROTATING T EXTENSION</string>
    <string name="exercise_276">STANDING SCARECROW 1</string>
    <string name="exercise_277">INVLINE SHOULDERS ROTATION</string>
    <string name="exercise_278">STANDING TRICEPS EXTENSION</string>
    <string name="exercise_279">BARBELL TRICEPS EXTENSION</string>

    <string name="description_1">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR. LIFT LEGS UNTIL LEGS ARE PERPENDICULAR WITH THE FLOOR. FULLY EXTEND YOUR ARMS ABOVE YOU AND HOLD THE DUMBBELL.\n\nSTEP 2: REACH YOUR TOES WITH YOUR HANDS. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN FOR STATING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_2">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR.FULLY EXTEND YOUR ARMS ABOVE YOU AND HOLD MEDICINE BALL PERPENDICULAR. \n\nSTEP :2 LIFT YOUR FEET AND ARMS TOWARD THE AIR. TOUCHING WITH THE MEDICINE BALL YOUR LEGS AND GOING BACK TO THE FIRST POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_3">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR. HOLD THE BALL WITH YOUR HANDS. EXTEND LEGS FULLY. RAISE YOUR LEGS TOWARD YOUR UPPER BOD AND PASS THE BALL UNDER YOUR BENT LEG. \n\nSTEP 2: AS YOU RETURN TO STARTING POSITION RACE AND BENT YOUR OTHER LEG TOWARDS YOUR UPPER BODY AND AGAIN PASS THE BALL UNDER THE BENT LEG. \n\nTHIS IS ONE REPETITION.</string>
    <string name="description_4">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMIN \n\nSTEP 1: LAY DOWN ON THE FLOOR, BEND YOUR KNEES AND KEEP YOUR FEET 18-24 INCHES APART. KEEP YOUR ARMS STRAIGHT NEAR YOUR BODY. \n\nSTEP 2: NOW CRUNCH OVER 3-4 INCHES AND TOUCH YOUR RIGHT HEEL ONCE. THAT CRUNCH BACK AND REPEAT IT. CRUNCH OVER AND TOUCH YOUR LEFT HEEL. WHILE CRUNCHING KEEP YOUR LOWER BACK ON THE FLOOR. REPEAT THIS REPEFIFION.</string>
    <string name="description_5">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR. LIFT LEGS UNTIL ONE LEG IS PERPENDICULAR WITH THE FLOOR. FULLY EXTEND YOUR ARMS ABOVE YOU. \n\nSTEP 2: REACH FOR TOES WITH YOUR HANDS. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_6">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE BACK ON THE FLOOR. PUT HANDS BEHIND YOUR HEAD. KNEES ARE BEND AND FEET ARE ON THE FLOOR. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE YOUR UPPER BODY UPWARD. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO YOUR STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_7">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE BACK ON THE FLOOR. PUT HANDS BEHIND YOUR HEAD. KNEES ARE BEND AND FEET ARE ON THE FLOOR. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE YOUR UPPER BODY UPWARD. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO YOUR STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_8">MUSCLE GROUP: OBLIQUES \n\nSTEP 1: SIT DOWN WITH YOUR FEET FLAT AND KNEES BENT. GRASP A WEIGHTED WITH BOTH HANDS. LEAN BACK SLIGHTLY AS YOU FULLY EXTEND YOUR ARMS STRAIGHT IN FRONT OF YOU. \n\nSTEP 2: TWIST YOUR TORSO IN ONE DIRECTION. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. \n\nSTEP 3: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. TWIST YOUR TORSO IN THE OTHER DIRECTION. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_9">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR. FEET ARE FLAT ON THE FLOOR AND KNEES ARE BENT. FULLY EXTEND YOUR ARMS KEEPING THE WEIGHTED. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE YOUR UPPER BODY UPWARD WHILE KEEPING YOUR LOWER BACK ON THE FLOOR. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_262">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: SIT ON THE FLOR. HOLD THE DUMBBELL, LIE BACK AND RISE YOUR LEGS UNTIL YOU REACH A POSITION OF BALANCE. \n\nSTEP 2: BEND YOUR KNEES TOWARDS YOUR UPPER BODY. AT THE SAME TIME OPEN YOUR ARMS. MOVE UPPER BODY FORWARD TO MAINTAIN POSITION OF BALANCE. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_11">MUSCLE GROUP: OBLIQUES \n\nSTEP 1: LAI DOWN ON THE FLOOR, BEND YOUR LEGS AND PUT YOUR FEET ON THE GROUND. MOVE YOUR HANDS BEHIND YOUR EARS AND PUT YOUR ELBOWS OUT. CURVE YOUR RIGHT LEG UP AND REST YOUR FOOT ON YOUR LEFT KNEE. \n\nSTEP 2: CRUNCH FORWARDS AND LIFT IT SIDEWAYS AND TRY TO TOUCH YOUR LEFT ELBOW TO YOUR RIGHT KNEE. THAN CRUNCH BACKWARDS, NOW SWAP AND CRUNCH FORWARD AND LIFT IT SIDEWAYS AND TRY TO TOUCH YOUR RIGHT ELBOW TO YOUR LEFT KNEE. REPEAT THIS.</string>
    <string name="description_12">MUSCLE GROUP: OBLIQUES \n\nSTEP 1: LIE ON YOUR SIDE. MAKE SURE ONE LEG IS ON TOP OF THE OTHER. POSITION THE FOREARM ON THE FLOOR PERPENDICULAR WITH YOUR BODY. \n\nSTEP 2: USE YOUR FOREARM TO LIFT YOUR UPPER BODY OF THE GROUND. THE OTHER ARM IS PLACED ON THE SIDE OF YOUR BODY. YOUR BODY SHOULD BE STRAIGHT. ONLY YOUR FOREARM AND THE SIDE OF YOUR FOOT SHOULD BE TOUCHING THE FLOOR. HOLD THIS POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_263">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR, PUT YOUR ARMS AT THE SIDES. BENT YOUR KNEES OP AND HOLD THEM STILL. \n\nSTEP 2: QUICKLY LIFT YOUR TORSO AS YOU PULL YOUR CHEST TO YOUR KNEES. KEEP YOUR ARMS PARALLEL TO THE FLOOR.</string>
    <string name="description_264">MUSCLE GRUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR. EXTEND YOUR LEGS PUT YOUR HANDS BEHIND YOUR HEAD. STEP 2: REACH YOUR TOES WITH YOUR HANDS. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_15">MUSCLE NAME: OBLIQUES \n\nSTEP 1: LIE ON YOUR SIDE WITH YOUR BODY IN A STRAIGHT LINE AND YOUR ARMS CROSSED AGAINST YOUR CHEST. \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT YOUR LEGS OFF THE FLOOR, MAKING SURE TO KEEP THEM TIGHTLY BOUND CONTRACTING, EVEN THOUGHT THERE ISN\'T TOO MUCH MOTION INVOLVED. \n\nSTEP 3: PAUSE, THEN SLOWLY RETURN TO THE STARTING POSITION. REPEAT AS MANY TIMES AS NEEDED THEN SWITCH SIDES.</string>
    <string name="description_16">MUSCLE GROUSZECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR WITH YOUR HANDS ASIDE, AND YOUR FEET STRAIGHT. \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT ONE LEG, BEND IT TO 90 DEGREES AND LAY IT OVER THE OTHER ONE, THAT STAYS STRAIGHT. \n\nSTEP 3: MAINTAINING THIS POSITION START THE EXERCISE BY LIFTING THE STRAIGHT LEG UP. \n\nSTEP 4: REPEAT THIS POSITION AS NECESSARY. SWITCH LEGS AND REPEAT.</string>
    <string name="description_265">MUSCLE: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1. WHILE LYING ON YOUR BACK, EXTEND YOUR LEGS AND ARMS FULLY. \n\nSTEP 2. SLOWLY LIFT YOUR HEAD AND SHOULDERS. AS YOU CURL UPWARD, ATTEMPT TO REACH AS HIGH AS POSSIBLE WITH YOUR FINGERS. \n\nSTEP 3. HOLD. THEN RETURN TO THE STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_18">MUSCLE: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1. LIE ON YOUR BACK BEND YOUR KNEES WITH YOUR ARMS AND LEGS STRAIGHT UP IN THE AIR HOLDING A BALL IN YOUR HANDS. \n\nSTEP 2. SLOWLY LIFT YOUR HEAD AND SHOULDERS. PLACE THE BALL ON YOUR LEGS. \n\nSTEP 3. HOLD. THEN RETURN TO THE STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_19">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE ON THE FLOOR WITH YOUR HANDS CROSSED OVER YOUR CHEST. BRING YOUR KNEES TO A 90 DEGREES ANGLE TO YOUR TORSO. LEGS ARE PRESSED TOGETHER. \n\nSTEP 2: WITH YOUR ABS CONTRACTED RAISE BOTH YOURS SHOULDERS AND PELVIS UP AS IF TRYING TO REACH THE CEILING WITH YOUR KNEES.</string>
    <string name="description_20">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: PLACE THE ROLLOUT ON THE FLOOR WITH CIRCULAR WEIGHT. HOLD THE ROLL WITH SHOULDER WIDTH OVERHAND GRIP. POSITION YOUR KNEES NEAR THE ROLL. KEEP YOUR BACK ARCHED AND YOUR THIGHS STRAIGHT. \n\nSTEP 2: ROLL OUT ON FRONT OF YOU, ALLOWING YOUR UPPER BODY TO EXTEND. STOP WHEN YOUR BACK IS STRAIGHTENED OUT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_21">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE ON THE FLOOR. PLACE HANDS UNDER YOUR HIP. EXTEND LEGS FULLY. SLIGHTLY RAISE LEGS. \n\nSTEP 2: BEND LEGS TOWARDS YOUR UPPER BODY. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_22">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE BACK ON THE STABILITY BALL. POSITION HANDS ON YOUR HEAD AND FEET ON THE FLOOR. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE YOUR UPPER BODY UPWARD WHILE KEEPING YOUR LOWER BACK ON THE STABILITY BALL. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_23">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE BACK ON THE STABILITY BALL. POSITION HANDS ON YOUR HEAD AND FEET ON THE FLOOR. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE YOUR UPPER BODY UPWARD WHILE KEEPING YOUR LOWER BACK ON THE STABILITY BALL. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_24">MUSCLE GROUP: OBLIQUES \n\nSTEP 1: SIT DOWN WITH YOUR LEGS FULLY EXTEND IN FRONT OF YOU. HOLD A MEDICINE BALL WITH BOTH HANDS. LEAN BACK UNTIL YOU ARE BALANCING ON YOUR TAILBONE. \n\nSTEP 2: TWIST YOUR TORSO IN ONE DIRECTION. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. \n\nSTEP 3: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. \n\nSTEP 4: TWIST YOUR TORSO IN THE OTHER DIRECTION. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_25">MUSCLE GROUP: OBLIQUES \n\nSTEP 1ILIE BACK ON THE STABILITY BALL. HOLD A MEDICINE BALL ABOVE YOU. \n\nSTEP 2: TWIST YOUR TORSO IN ONE DIRECTION. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. \n\nSTEP 3: TWIST YOUR TORSO IN OTHER DIRECTION. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_26">MUSCLE GROUP: OBLIQUES \n\nSTEP: 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD DUMBBELL WITH BOTH HANDS IN FRONT OF YOU. \n\nSTEP 2: TWIST YOUR TORSO IN ONE DIRECTION. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND \n\nSTEP 3: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. \n\nSTEP 4: TWIST YOUR TORSO IN THE OTHER DIRECTION. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_27">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1. PLACE A BOSU BALL ON THE FLOOR AND LIE WITH YOUR BACK ON IT. KEEP YOUR KNEES BENT, FEET FLAT, AND PLACE YOUR HANDS TO THE SIDES OF YOUR HEAD. \n\nSTEP 2. LIFT YOUR HEAD AND SHOULDERS OFF THE BOSU, KEEPING YOUR FEET FLAT ON THE FLOOR THROUGHOUT THE MOVEMENT. RESIST THE URGE TO PULL YOUR HEAD UP WITH YOUR HANDS FOCUS ON USING YOUR ABDOMINAL AND CORE MUSCLES TO DO THE WORK. \n\nSTEP 3. LOWER TO THE STARTING POSITION AND REPEAT.</string>
    <string name="description_28">MUSCLE GROUP: OBLIQUES \n\nSTEP: 1: POSITION ONE FOREARM ON THE BENCH WITH YOUR FEET ON THE FLOOR. THE ENTIRE FOREARM SHOULD BE ON THE BENCH. MAKE SURE ONE LEG IS ON TOP OF THE OTHER. THE OTHER ARM IS PLACED ON THE SIDE OF YOUR BODY. \n\nSTEP 2: KEEP YOUR BODY STRAIGHT. ONLY YOUR FOREARM SHOULD BE TOUCHING THE BENCH AND ONLY THE SIDE OF YOUR FOOT SHOULD BE TOUCHING THE FLOOR. HOLD THIS POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_271">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP: 1: LIE BACK ON THE DECLINE BENCH. HOLD MEDICINE BALL IN FRONT OF YOUR CHEST. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE YOUR UPPER BODY UPWARD. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_30">MUSCLE: OBLIQUES \n\nSTEP: 1: LIE BACK ON THE DECLINE BENCH. HOLD MEDICINE BALL WITH BOTH HANDS. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE YOUR UPPER BODY UPWARD AND TOWARDS THE RIGHT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND \n\nSTEP 3: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. \n\nSTEP 4: RAISE YOUR UPPER BODY UPWARD AND TOWARDS THE LEFT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND RETURN STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_31">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: SIT ON THE SIDE OF THE BENCH. HOLD ONTO THE SIDE OF THE BENCH WITH BOTH HANDS AT SHOULDER WIDTH. LIE BACK AND RAISE YOUR LEGS UNTIL YOU REACH A POSITION OF BALANCE. \n\n STEP 2: BEND YOUR KNEES TOWARDS YOUR UPPER BODY. AT THE SAME TIME, MOVE UPPER BODY FORWARD TO MAINTAIN POSITION OF BALANCE. HOLD FOR NONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_32">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: SIT ON THE SIDE OF THE BENCH. HOLD ONTO THE SIDE OF THE BENCH WITH BOTH HANDS AT SHOULDER WIDTH. LIE BACK AND RAISE YOUR LEGS UNTIL YOU REACH A POSITION OF BALANCE. \n\nSTEP 2: BEND YOUR KNEES TOWARDS YOUR UPPER BODY. AT THE SAME TIME, MOVE UPPER BODY FORWARD TO MAINTAIN POSITION OF BALANCE. HOLD FOR NONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_33">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: PLACE BARBELL ON THE FLOOR WITH CIRCULAR WEIGHTS. HOLD BARBELL WITH SHOULDER WITH OVERHAND GRIP. POSITION YOUR KNEES NEAR THE BARBELL. KEEP YOUR BACK ARCHED AND YOUR THINGS STRAIGHT. \n\nSTEP 2: ROLL THE BARBELL OUT IN FRONT OF YOU, ALLOWING YOUR UPPER BODY TO EXTEND. STOP WHEN YOUR BACK IS STRAIGHTENED OUT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_34">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE ON THE FLOOR WITH LEGS EXTENDED STRAIGHT, AND HOLD ON TO THE TOP OF THE FLOOR. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE YOUR LEGS STRAIGHT UP, SLIGHTLY LIFTING YOUR LOWER BACK OFF THE FLOOR. \n\nSTEP 3: HOLD FOR A FEE SECONDS, THEN LOWER YOUR LEGS BACK DOWN TO THE START POSITION. KEEP YOUR LEGS STRAIGHT THROUGHOUT THE MOTION.</string>
    <string name="description_35">MUSCLE GROUP: OBLIQUES \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR. LIFT LEGS UNTIL THIGHS ARE PERPENDICULAR WITH THE GROUND. BEND YOUR KNEES. FULLY EXTEND YOUR ARMS TO YOUR SIDES. \n\nSTEP: 2: WHILE TWISTING THE UPPER BODY, LOWER YOUR LEGS TO ONE SIDE. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. \n\nSTEP: 3: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION \n\nSTEP 4: WHILE TWISTING THE UPPER BODY, LOWER YOUR TO THE OTHER SIDE. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_36">MUSCLE GROUP: OBLIQUES \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR. LIFT LEGS UNTIL THIGHS ARE PERPENDICULAR WITH THE GROUND. KEEP LEGS STRAIGHT. FULLY EXTEND YOUR ARMS TO YOUR SIDES. \n\nSTEP: 2: WHILE TWISTING THE UPPER BODY, LOWER YOUR LEGS TO ONE SIDE. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. \n\nSTEP: 3: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION \n\nSTEP 4: WHILE TWISTING THE UPPER BODY, LOWER YOUR TO THE OTHER SIDE. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_37">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR. LIFT LEGS UNTIL UNTIL LEGS ARE PERPENDICULAR WITH THE FLOOR. FULLY EXTEND YOUR ARMS ABOVE YOU. \n\nSTEP 2: REACH FOR YOUR TOES WITH YOUR HAND. MOVE TO THE SIDE AFTER EVERY TOUCHING AND COME RETURN TO STARTING POSITION AT THE MIDDLE.</string>
    <string name="description_38">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR. PLACE HANDS NEXT TO YOUR SIDES. EXTEND LEGS FULLY AND SLIGHTLY ELEVATED. WHILE KEEPING LEGS STRAIGHT, RAISE ONE LEG UP \n\nSTEP 2: AS YOU LOWER LEG, RAISE THE OTHER LEG UP THIS IS ONE REPETITION.</string>
    <string name="description_39">MUSCLE GROUP: OBLIQUES \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR. LIFT LEGS SO THAT YOUR THIGHS ARE PERPENDICULAR WITH THE GROUND. PUT HANDS BEHIND YOUR HEAD. \n\nSTEP 2: MOVE LEFT ELBOW AND RIGHT LEG TOWARD THE BODY UNTIL THEY TOUCH \n\nSTEP 3: MOVE LEFT ELBOW AND RIGHT LEG BACK TO STARTING POSITION. AT THE SAME TIME, MOVE RIGHT ELBOW AND LEFT LEG TOWARD THE BODY UNTIL THEY TOUCH. THIS IS ONE REPETITION.</string>
    <string name="description_40">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR. LIFT LEGS UNTIL LEGS ARE PERPENDICULAR WITH THE FLOOR. FULLY EXTEND YOUR ARMS ABOVE YOU. \n\nSTEP 2: REACH FOR YOUR TOES WITH YOUR HANDS. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_41">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP: 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLAT BENCH. PLACE HANDS ON THE BENCH. EXTEND LEGS FULLY. \n\nSTEP 2: RALSE AND BEND LEGS TOWARDS YOUR UPPER BODY. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_42">MUSCLE GROUP: OBLIQUES \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR. LIFT LEGS UNTIL THIGHS ARE PERPENDICULAR WITH THE GROUND. KEEP LEGS BENT AND KEEP THE MEDICINE BALL BETWEEN YOUR KNEES. MOVE LEGS TO SIDE. \n\nSTEP 2: WHILE KEEPING THE UPPER BODY STILL, LOWER YOUR LEGS TO THE OTHER SIDE SIDE. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND AND RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_43">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP: 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR. HOLD MEDICINE BALL OVERHEAD WITH ARMS FULLY EXTENDED. KEEP KNEES BENT AND FEET FLAT ON FLOOR. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE YOUR UPPER BODY UPWARD WHILE KEEPING YOUR LOWER BACK ON THE FLOOR. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_44">MUSCLE GROUP: OBLIQUES \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR. PLACE HANDS NEXT TO YOUR SIDES. EXTEND LEGS FULLY AND SLIGHTLY ELEVATED. WHILE, KEEPING LEGS STRAIGHT, RAISE ONE LEG HIGHER THEN THE OTHER. \n\nSTEP 2: EXTEND BOTH LEGS WIDE AND OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 3: AS YOUR LOWER LEG, RAISE THE OTHER LEG UP. \n\nSTEP 4: EXTEND BOTH LEGS WIDE AND OUTWARD.</string>
    <string name="description_45">MUSCLE GROUP: LOWER BACK \n\nSTEP 1: LIE PRONE ON THE FLOOR. FULLY EXTEND YOUR ARMS IN FRONT OF YOU. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE YOUR LEGS AND UPPER BODY TOWARDS THE CEILING. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_46">MUSCLE GROUP: LOWER BACK \n\nSTEP 1: LIE PRONE ON THE FLOOR. FULLY EXTEND YOUR ARMS IN FRONT OF YOU. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE LEFT LEG AND RIGHT ARM TOWARDS THE CEILING. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. \n\nSTEP 3: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. \n\nSTEP 4: RAISE RIGHT LEG AND LEFT ARM TOWARDS THE CEILING. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION,</string>
    <string name="description_47">MUSCLE GROUP: LATISSIMUS DORSI \n\nSTEP 1: BEND YOUR KNEES SLIGHTLY. KEEP BACK BENT AND STRAIGHT. HOLD BARBELL UNDER YOU WITH SHOULDER WIDTH UNDERHAND GRIP. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE THE BARBELL VERTICALLY TOWARDS YOUR CHEST. REFRAIN FROM FLARING YOUR ELBOWS OUT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_48">MUSCLE GROUP: LOWER BACK \n\nSTEP 1: LIE PRONE ON THE FLOOR. KEEP YOUR ARMS BEHIND OF YOU HEAD. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE YOUR LEGS AND UPPER BODY TOWARDS THE CEILING. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION</string>
    <string name="description_49">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: KNEEL DOWN AND PLACE YOUR HANDS ON THE FLOOR. RAISE YOUR RIGHT ARM AND LEFT LEG UP INTO THE AIR. \n\nSTEP 2: BRING YOUR ARM AND LEG OUTWARD. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_50">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: KEEP YOUR LEGS DOWN AND PLACE YOUR HANDS ON THE FLOOR. RAISE YOUR RIGHT ARM AND LEFT LEG UP INTO THE AIR. \n\nSTEP 2: BRING YOUR ARM AND LEG OUTWARD. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_266">MUSCLE GROUP: LOWER BACK \n\nSTEP 1: LIE PRONE ON THE FLOOR. RAISE YOURSELF UP SO THAT ONLY YOUR TOES AND FOREARMS ARE ON THE FLOOR. KEEP YOUR BACK STRAIGHT. LIFT YOUR RIGHT LEG UP. TOUCH YOUR HEEL. RETURN TO THE PLANK POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_52">MUSCLE GROUP: LOWER BACK \n\nSTEP 1: LIE PRONE ON THE FLOOR. RAISE YOURSELF UP SO THAT ONLY YOUR TOES AND FOREARMS ARE ON BALANCE BALL. KEEP YOUR BACK STRAIGHT. HOLD FOR AS LONG AS POSSIBLE.</string>
    <string name="description_53">MUSCLE GROUP: LOWER BACK \n\nSTEP 1: LIE WITH YOUR CHEST ON THE BALANCE BALL. KEEP YOUR ARMS BEHIND YOUR HEAD. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE YOUR UPPER BODY TOWARDS THE CEILING. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_54">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORALIS \n\nSTEP 1 HOLD ONTO TWO DUMBBELLS WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY THE DUMBBELLS AND TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. \n\nSTEP 3: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. \n\nSTEP 4: LIFT ONE DUMBBELL UP BY MOVING YOUR ELBOW UPWARD. YOUR HAND SHOULD MOVE IN A VERTICAL LINE. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. \n\nSTEP 5: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. \n\nSTEP 6: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. \n\nSTEP 7: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION \n\nSTEP 8: LIFT THE OTHER DUMBBELL UP BY MOVING YOUR ELBOW UPWARD. YOUR HAND SHOULD MOVE IN A VERTICAL LINE. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_55">MUSCLE GROUP: GLUTES \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR WITH FEET POSITIONED ON THE STABILITY BALL. POSITION HANDS ON YOUR SIDES TO STABILIZE YOUR POSITION. \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT YOUR HIP UPWARD. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_56">MUSCLE GROUP: LATISSIMUS DORSI \n\nSTEP 1: BEND YOUR KNEES SLIGHTLY. KEEP BACK BENT AND STRAIGHT. HOLD DUMBBELLS TO YOUR SIDE WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE THE DUMBBELLS VERTICALLY TOWARDS YOUR CHEST. REFRAIN FROM FLARING YOUR ELBOW OUT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_57">MUSCLE GROUP: LOWER BACK \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD DUMBBELLS OF YOUR THIGHS WITH OVERHAND GRIP. LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL DUMBBELLS ARE AROUND SHIN LEVEL. KNEES BEND SLIGHTLY. KEEP CHEST STICKING OUTWARD AND YOUR BACK STRAIGHT. \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT YOURSELF UP UNTIL YOUR ARE STANDING STRAIGHT. KEEP YOUR CHEST OUT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_58">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE PRONE ON THE FLOOR. RAISE YOURSELF UP SO THAT ONLY YOUR TOES AND FOREARMS ARE ON THE FLOOR. KEEP YOUR BACK STRAIGHT. HOLD FOR AS LONG AS POSSIBLE.</string>
    <string name="description_59">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: POSITION LEGS ON CHEER. WHILE KEEPING BACK STRAIGHT, PLACE FOREARMS ON THE FLOOR. YOUR FOREARMS ARE PERPENDICULAR WITH YOUR UPPER ARMS. HOLD FOR AS LONG AS YOU CAN.</string>
    <string name="description_60">MUSCLE GROUP: LATISSIMUS DORSI \n\nSTEP 1: KNEEL WITH ONE LEG ON A FLAT BENCH AND PLACE ONE HAND ON THE BENCH FOR SUPPORT. PLACE OTHER LEG ON THE FLOOR AND HOLD DUMBBELL WITH A NEUTRAL GRIP. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE THE DUMBBELL VERTICALLY TOWARDS YOUR CHEST. REFRAIN FROM FLARING YOUR ELBOW OUT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_267">MUSCLE GROUP: LOWER BACK \n\nSTEP 1: PLACE EZ CURL BAR ON THE FLOOR. POSITION YOURSELF SO THAT YOUR SHINS ARE AN INCH AWAY FROM THE BAR. STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. WITHOUT MUCH HIP MOVEMENT, LOWER YOURSELF TO GRASP THE EZ CURL BAR WITH OVERHAND GRIP. BEND KNEES SLIGHTLY. STICK CHEST OUTWARD AND LOOK AHEAD. \n\nSTEP 2: PULL EZ CURL BAR UP UNTIL YOU ARE STANDING STRAIGHT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_62">MUSCLE GROUP: HAMSTRINGS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. PLACE BARBELL ON THE BACK OF YOUR SHOULDERS. HOLD BARBELL WITH OVERHAND GRIP. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. ADJUST FEET TO POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: KEEP BACK STRAIGHT AND BEND UPPER BODY UNTIL IT IS PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_63">MUSCLE GROUP: LATISSIMUS DORSI \n\nSTEP 1: BEND YOUR KNEES SLIGHTLY. KEEP BACK BENT AND STRAIGHT. HOLD EZ CURL BAR UNDER YOU WITH SHOULDER WIDTH OVERHAND GRIP. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE THE EZ CURL BAR VERTICALLY TOWARDS YOUR CHEST. REFRAIN FROM FLARING YOUR ELBOWS OUT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_64">MUSCLE GROUP: LATISSIMUS DORSI \n\nSTEP 1: BEND YOUR KNEES SLIGHTLY. KEEP BACK BENT AND STRAIGHT. HOLD EZ CURL BAR UNDER YOU WITH SHOULDER WIDTH OVERHAND GRIP. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE THE EZ CURL BAR VERTICALLY TOWARDS YOUR CHEST. REFRAIN FROM FLARING YOUR ELBOWS OUT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_65">MUSCLE GROUP: BICEBS BRACHII \n\nSTEP 1: SIT ON THE STABILITY BALL. LET KETTLEBELLS HANG NEXT TO YOU WITH FIRM NEUTRAL GRIP. KEEP ARMS STRAIGHT. \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT KETTLEBELLS UP WHILE KEEPING YOUR UPPER ARMS IN PLACE REFRAIN FROM USING YOUR SHOULDERS DURING THE MOVEMENT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_66">MUSCLE GROUP: BRACHIORADIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: WHILE STANDING WITH BACK STRAIGHT, HOLD DUMBBELLS AT YOUR SIDES WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. KEEP ARMS STRAIGHT. \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT DUMBBELLS UP WHILE KEEPING YOUR UPPER ARMS IN PLACE REFRAIN FROM USING YOUR SHOULDERS DURING THE MOVEMENT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_67">MUSCLE GROUP: BICEBS BRACHII \n\nSTEP 1: STAND WITH FEET ABOUT HIP-WIDTH APART, ABS ENGAGED AS YOU HOLD MEDIUM HEAVY DUMBBELLS IN FRONT OF THE THIGHS. SQUEEZE THE BICEPS AND BEND THE ARMS, CURLING THE WEIGHTS UP TOWARDS THE SHOULDERS. \n\nSTEP 2: KEEP THE ELBOWS STATIONARY AND ONLY BRING THE WEIGHT AS HIGH AS YOU CAN WITHOUT MOVING THE ELBOWS. SLOWLY LOWER THE WEIGHTS, KEEPING A SLIGHT BEND IN THE ELBOWS AT THE BOTTOM (E.G., DON\'T LOCK THE JOINTS AND TRY TO KEEP TENSION ON)</string>
    <string name="description_68">MUSCLE GROUP: BICEBS BRACHII \n\nSTEP 1: BEND YOUR KNEES SLIGHTLY. KEEP BACK BENT AND STRAIGHT. HOLD ONE DUMBBELL WITH UNDERHAND GRIP. POSITION ELBOW AT THE INNER THIGH. \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT DUMBBELL UP WHILE KEEPING YOUR UPPER ARM IN PLACE. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_69">MUSCLE GROUP: BICEBS BRACHII \n\nSTEP 1: SID DOWN ON THE BENCH. KEEP BACK BENT AND STRAIGHT. HOLD ONE DUMBBELL WITH UNDERHAND GRIP. POSITION ELBOW AT THE INNER THIGH. \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT DUMBBELL UP WHILE KEEPING YOUR UPPER ARM IN PLACE. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_268">MUSCLE GROUP: BICEPS BRACHII\u0020\u0020\n\nSTEP 1: WHILE STANDING WITH BACK STRAIGHT, HOLD ONE DUMBBELL WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. REST UPPER ARM ON THE TOP OF THE INCLINE BENCH. \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT DUMBBELL UP WHILE KEEPING YOUR UPPER ARMS IN PLACE. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. LOWER DUMBBELL BACK TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <!-- biceps 10 -->
    <string name="description_71">MUSCLE GROUP: BRACHIORADIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE PRONE ON THE INCLINE BENCH. LET DUMBBELLS HANG NEXT TO YOU WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. KEEP ARMS STRAIGHT. \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT DUMBBELLS UP WHILE KEEPING YOUR UPPER ARMS IN PLACE REFRAIN FROM USING YOUR SHOULDERS DURING THE MOVEMENT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_72">MUSCLE NAME: WRIST FLEXORS \n\nSTEP 1: SIT WITH YOUR FOREARMS RESTING ON YOUR THIGHS OR ON A BENCH. TAKE AN UNDERHAND GRIP ON THE BAR WITH YOUR WRISTS PASSIVELY EXTENDED INHALE AND CURL YOUR WRIST UP. EXHALE AS YOU COMPLETE THE MOVEMENT.</string>
    <string name="description_73">MUSCLE GROUP: BRACHIORADIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: SID ON THE BENCH WITH BACK STRAIGHT, HOLD DUMBBELLS NEXT TO YOUR SIDES WITH UNDERHAND GRIP. KEEP ARMS STRAIGHT. \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT DUMBBELLS UP WHILE KEEPING YOUR UPPER ARMS IN PLACE REFRAIN FROM USING YOUR SHOULDERS DURING THE MOVEMENT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_74">MUSCLE GROUP: BICEPS BRACHII \n\nSTEP 1: WHILE SEATED WITH BACK STRAIGHT, LET DUMBBELLS HANG NEXT TO YOU WITH UNDERHAND GRIP. KEEP ARMS STRAIGHT. \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT DUMBBELLS UP WHILE KEEPING YOUR UPPER ARMS IN PLACE REFRAIN FROM USING YOUR SHOULDERS DURING THE MOVEMENT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_75">MUSCLE GROUP: BICEPS BRACHII \n\nSTEP 1: WHILE STANDING WITH BACK STRAIGHT, HOLD EZ CURL BAR WITH SHOULDER WIDTH UNDERHAND GRIP. EZ CURL BAR IS POSITIONED IN FRONT OF YOUR THIGHS. \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT EZ CURL BAR UP WHILE KEEPING YOUR UPPER ARMS IN PLACE REFRAIN FROM USING YOUR SHOULDERS DURING THE MOVEMENT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. LOWER YOUR ARMS BACK TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_76">MUSCLE GROUP: WRIST FLEXORS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. POSITION BARBELL BEHIND YOUR HAMSTRINGS. HOLD BARBELL WITH UNDERHAND GRIP. \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT BARBELL WITH YOUR WRISTS. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_77">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN CHEST FIRST WITH YOUR HANDS ON THE FLOOR. POSITION HANDS NEXT TO YOUR LOWER CHEST. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR HANDS AND TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. POSITION MEDICINE BALL UNDER ONE HAND. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARD YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_78">MUSCLE GROUP: PRCTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: PLACE YOUR FEET ON THE STEPPER AND YOUR HANDS ON THE FLOOR. POSITION HANDS NEXT TO YOUR LOWER CHEST. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR HANDS ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_79">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORALIS \n\nSTEP 1: PLACE YOUR HANDS ON THE STEPPER AND YOUR TOES ON THE FLOOR. POSITION HANDS NEXT TO YOUR CHEST. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR HANDS ARE ON THE BENCH MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE STEPPER BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_80">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN CHEST FIRST WITH YOUR HANDS ON THE FLOOR. POSITION HANDS NEXT TO YOUR LOWER CHEST. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR HANDS AND KNEES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_81">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR. GRASP THE DUMBBELLS WITH OVERHAND GRIP. REST YOUR UPPER ARMS ON THE FLOOR WHILE POINTING DUMBBELLS TOWARD THE CEILING. \n\nSTEP 2: FULLY EXTEND ARMS TOWARDS THE CEILING. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. KEEP YOUR ENTIRE BACK ON THE BENCH AT ALL TIMES. REFRAIN FROM ANY LEG MOVEMENTS. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_82">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN CHEST FIRST WITH YOUR HANDS ON THE FLOOR. FORM A DIAMOND SHAPE WITH YOUR HANDS. POSITION HANDS UNDER YOUR LOWER CHEST. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR HANDS AND TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_83">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN CHEST FIRST WITH YOUR HANDS ON THE FLOOR. POSITION HANDS UNDER YOUR SHOULDERS. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE NARROWER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR HANDS AND TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_84">MUSCLE GROUP: PRCTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN CHEST FIRST WITH YOUR HANDS ON THE FLOOR. POSITION HANDS UNDER YOUR SHOULDERS. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE NARROWER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR HANDS AND TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. \n\nSTEP 3: EXTEND ONE ARM AFTER EVERY TIME YOU COME UP. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_85">MUSCLE GROUP: PRCTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN CHEST FIRST WITH YOUR HANDS ON THE FLOOR. POSITION HANDS UNDER YOUR SHOULDERS. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE NARROWER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR HANDS AND TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. \n\nSTEP 3: TOUCH YOUR OPPOSITE SHOULDER AFTER EVERY TIME YOU COME UP. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_86">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN CHEST RST WITH YOUR HANDS ON THE FLOOR. POSITION HANDS NEXT TO YOUR LOWER CHEST. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR HANDS AND TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. AT THE SAME TIME, BRING ONE KNEE TOWARDS YOUR ELBOW. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND \n\nSTEP 3: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. \n\nSTEP 4: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. AT THE SAME TIME, BRING YOUR OTHER KNEE TOWARDS YOUR ELBOW. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND.</string>
    <string name="description_87">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN CHEST FIRST WITH YOUR HANDS ON THE FLOOR. POSITION HANDS NEXT TO YOUR LOWER CHEST. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR HANDS AND TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. POSITION THE MEDICINE BALL UNDER ONE HAND. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARD YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. \n\nSTEP 3: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. \n\nSTEP 4: ROLL THE BALL OVER TO THE OTHER HAND \n\nSTEP 5: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARD YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. \n\nSTEP 6: LIFT YOURSELF UP FROM THE FLOOR. ROLL THE BALL BACK TO THE FIRST HAND.</string>
    <string name="description_88">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORALIS \n\nSTEP 1. WITH TWO DUMBBELLS PLACED SHOULDER-WIDTH APART ON THE FLOOR IN FRONT OF YOU, KNEEL DOWN AND HOLD ONTO THEM. KEEP YOUR ARMS STRAIGHT, EXTENDED, FEET FAIRLY TOGETHER AND LOCK YOUR ELBOWS. \n\nSTEP 2. LOWER YOUR BODY TO THE FLOOR BY PLAEINGA BEND IN YOUR ELBOWS AND KEEPING YOUR BACK STRAIGHT. \n\nSTEP 3. PUSH YOURSELF BACK UP UNTIL YOUR ARMS ARE STRAIGHT AND ELBOWS.</string>
    <string name="description_89">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN CHEST FIRST WITH YOUR HANDS ON THE FLOOR. POSITION HANDS NEXT TO YOUR LOWER CHEST. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR HANDS AND TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. KEEP YOUR BACK AND LEGS STRAIGHT. \n\nSTEP 2: WITHOUT MOVING YOUR ARMS, HOP TOWARD YOUR ARMS. HOP BACK TO STARTING POSITION AFTERWARD.</string>
    <string name="description_90">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORALIS \n\nSTEP 1: HOLD ONTO TWO DUMBBELLS WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY THE DUMBBELLS AND TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND \n\nSTEP 3: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION \n\nSTEP 4: LITU ONE AUMEELL UP DY MOVING YOUR ELBOW UPWARD. YOUR HAND SHOULD MOVE IN A VERTICAL LINE. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND \n\nSTEP 5: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. \n\nSTEP 6: LOWER IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND \n\nSTEP 7: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_91">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN CHEST FIRST WITH YOUR HANDS ON THE BOSU. POSITION HANDS NEXT TO YOUR LOWER CHEST AND TO ONE SIDE. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR HANDS AND TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND \n\nSTEP 3: PUSH UP. \n\nSTEP 4: LAND WITH YOUR HANDS ON THE OTHER SIDE. \n\nSTEP 5: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. \n\nSTEP 6: PUSH UP AND RETURN TO STARTING.</string>
    <string name="description_92">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN CHEST FIRST WITH YOUR HANDS ON THE FLOOR. POSITION HANDS NEXT TO YOUR LOWER CHEST. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR HANDS AND TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. LIFT YOUR BEHIND UP IN THE AIR. ARMS SHOULD STRAIGHTEN OUT. \n\nSTEP 2: PRETENDING THAT THERE IS AN IMAGINARY BAR TWO FEET FROM THE GROUND, GO UNDER THE BAR UNTIL YOUR ENTIRE UPPER BODY PASSED THE BAR. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND. ARMS STRAIGHTEN OUT AT THE END OF THE MOVEMENT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_93">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE BACK ON THE STABILITY BALL. FEET ARE ON THE FLOOR. GRASP THE DUMBBELLS WITH OVERHAND GRIP. HOLD THE DUMBBELLS NEXT TO YOUR CHEST. \n\nSTEP 2: FULLY EXTEND YOUR ARMS IN FRONT OF YOU. HOLD FOR A BRIEF MOMENT. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_94">MUSCLE: PECTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: PLACE YOUR HANDS ON THE BENCH AND YOUR TOES ON THE FLOOR. POSITION HANDS NEXT TO YOUR CHEST. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR HANDS ARE ON THE BENCH. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE BENCH BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_95">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE BACK ON THE STABILITY BALL. FEET ARE ON THE FLOOR. HOLD ONTO TWO DUMBBELLS WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. FULLY EXTEND YOUR ARMS ABOVE YOUR CHEST. \n\nSTEP 2: WHILE MAINTAINING A SLIGHT BEND IN YOUR ELBOWS, LOWER DUMBBELLS TO EACH SIDE UNTIL THE DUMBBELLS ARE NEXT TO YOUR UPPER BODY. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_96">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORIALIS: \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN CHEST FIRST WITH YOUR PALMS ON THE FLOOR. HOLD DUMBBELLS WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. POSITION HANDS NEXT TO YOUR LOWER CHEST. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR PALMS AND TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST LIS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. \n\nSTEP 3: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. \n\nSTEP 4: RAISE ONE ARM UNTIL DUMBBELL POINTS TO THE CEILING. HOLD FOR ONE SECONDS \n\nSTEP 5: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. \n\nSTEP 6: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. \n\nSTEP 7: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_97">MUSCLE GROUP: TRICEPS BRACHII \n\nSTEP 1: PLACE YOUR PALMS AT THE EDGE OF THE BENCH WITH FINGERS CURLED AROUND THE EDGE OF THE CHAIR. KEEP YOUR ARMS WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. POSITION THE REST OF YOUR BODY IN A SITTING POSITION IN FRONT OF THE CHAIR. KEEP KNEES BENT. \n\nSTEP 2: BEND YOUR ARMS UNTIL YOUR UPPER ARMS ARE NEARLY PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. HOLD FOR A SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_98">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: HOLD ONTO TWO DUMBBELLS WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY THE DUMBBELLS AND TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. EXTEND FULLY THE HAND WITH DUMBBELL. \n\nSTEP 2: YOUR ARM HAS TO BE AT THE LEVEL OF YOURAYES. \n\nSTEP 3: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. \n\nSTEP 4: LIFT ONE DUMBBELL UP BY MOVING YOUR ELBOW UPWARD. YOUR HAND SHOULD MOVE IN A VERTICAL LINE. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. \n\nSTEP 5: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. \n\nSTEP 6: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. \n\nSTEP 7: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION \n\nSTEP 8: LIFT THE OTHER DUMBBELL UP BY MOVING YOUR ELBOW UPWARD. YOUR HAND SHOULD MOVE IN A VERTICAL LINE. HOLD ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_99">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE BACK ON THE INCLINE BENCH. HOLD THE EZ CURL BAR WITH OVERHAND GRIP. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS IS SLIGHTER WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH. HOLD THE EZ CURL BAR WITH ARMS FULLY EXTENDED. THE EZ CURL BAR IS DIRECTLY ABOVE THE CENTER OF YOUR CHEST. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER THE EZ CURL BAR TOWARDS YOUR LOWER CHEST AS YOU KEEP YOUR ELBOWS CLOSE TO YOUR BODY. THE EZ CURL BAR SHOULD SLIGHTLY TOUCH YOUR CHEST AT THE END OF THE MOVEMENT. REFRAIN FROM BOUNCING THE EZ CURL BAR OFF YOUR CHEST. HOLD FOR A BRIEF MOMENT. RETURN STARTING POSITION. KEEP YOUR ENTIRE BACK ON THE BENCH AT ALL TIMES. REFRAIN FROM ANY LEG MOVEMENTS.</string>
    <string name="description_100">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE BACK ON THE FLAT BENCH. HOLD THE EZ CURL BAR WITH OVERHAND GRIP. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS IS SLIGHTER WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH HOLD THE EZ CURL BAR WITH ARMS FULLY EXTENDED. THE EZ CURL BAR IS DIRECTLY ABOVE THE CENTER OF YOUR CHEST. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER THE EZ CURL BAR TOWARDS YOUR LOWER CHEST AS YOU KEEP YOUR ELBOWS CLOSE TO YOUR BODY. THE EZ CURL BAR SHOULD SLIGHTLY TOUCH YOUR CHEST AT THE END OF THE MOVEMENT. REFRAIN FROM BOUNCING THE EZ CURL BAR OFF YOUR CHEST. HOLD FOR A BRIEF MOMENT. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. KEEP YOUR ENTIRE BACK ON THE BENCH AT ALL TIMES. REFRAIN FROM ANY LEG MOVEMENTS.</string>
    <string name="description_101">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE BACK ON THE DECLINE BENCH. HOLD THE EZ CURL BAR WITH OVERHAND GRIP. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS IS WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH. HOLD THE EZ CURL BAR WITH ARMS FULLY EXTENDED. THE EZ CURL BAR IS DIRECTLY ABOVE THE CENTER OF YOUR CHEST. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER THE EZ CURL BAR TOWARDS YOUR LOWER CHEST AS YOU KEEP YOUR ELBOWS CLOSE TO YOUR BODY. THE EZ CURL BAR SHOULD SLIGHTLY TOUCH YOUR CHEST AT THE END OF THE MOVEMENT. REFRAIN FROM BOUNCING THE EZ CURL BAR OFF YOUR CHEST. HOLD FOR A BRIEF MOMENT. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. KEEP YOUR ENTIRE BACK ON THE BENCH AT ALL TIMES. REFRAIN FROM ANY LEG.</string>
    <string name="description_102">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1. GO INTO THE STANDARD PUSHUP SITION, WITH HANDS BENEATH YOUR SHOULDERS. THIS TIME THOUGH, ASK A PARTNER TO PLACE A WEIGHT PLATE ON YOUR BACK, BETWEEN YOUR SHOULDER BLADES. \n\nSTEP 2. KEEP YOUR BODY STRAIGHT AS YOU LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS UNTIL YOUR CHEST TOUCHES THE FLOOR. \n\nSTEP 3. PAUSE, THEN PUSH YOURSELF UP.</string>
    <string name="description_103">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE BACK ON THE DECLINE BENCH. HOLD THE EZ CURL BAR WITH UNDERHAND GRIP. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS IS SLIGHTER WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH HOLD THE EZ CURL BAR WITH ARMS FULLY EXTENDED. THE EZ CURL BAR IS DIRECTLY ABOVE THE CENTER OF YOUR CHEST. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER THE EZ CURL BAR TOWARDS YOUR LOWER CHEST AS YOU KEEP YOUR ELBOWS CLOSE TO YOUR BODY. THE EZ CURL BAR SHOULD SLIGHTLY TOUCH YOUR CHEST AT THE END OF THE MOVEMENT. REFRAIN FROM BOUNCING THE EZ CURL BAR OFF YOUR CHEST. HOLD FOR A BRIEF MOMENT. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. KEEP YOUR ENTIRE BACK ON THE BENCH AT ALL TIMES. REFRAIN FROM ANY LEG MOVEMENTS.</string>
    <string name="description_104">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE BACK ON THE DECLINE BENCH. HOLD THE DUMBBELLS WITH OVERHAND GRIP. KEEP YOUR ARMS FULLY EXTENDED. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER THE DUMBBELLS TOWARDS YOUR LOWER CHEST AS YOU KEEP YOUR ELBOWS CLOSE TO YOUR BODY. HOLD FOR A BRIEF MOMENT. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. KEEP YOUR ENTIRE BACK ON THE BENCH AT ALL TIMES. REFRAIN FROM ANY LEG MOVEMENTS.</string>
    <string name="description_105">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE DECLINE BENCH. HOLD ONTO TWO DUMBBELLS WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. FULLY EXTEND YOUR ARMS ABOVE YOUR CHEST. \n\nSTEP 2: WHILE MAINTAINING A SLIGHT BEND IN YOUR ELBOWS, LOWER DUMBBELLS TO EACH SIDE UNTIL THE DUMBBELLS ARE NEXT TO YOUR UPPER BODY. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_106">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE BACK ON THE FLAT BENCH. HOLD THE DUMBBELLS WITH OVERHAND GRIP. KEEP YOUR ARMS FULLY EXTENDED. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER THE DUMBBELLS TOWARDS YOUR LOWER CHEST AS YOU KEEP YOUR ELBOWS CLOSE TO YOUR BODY. HOLD FOR A BRIEF MOMENT. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. KEEP YOUR ENTIRE BACK ON THE BENCH AT ALL TIMES. REFRAIN FROM ANY LEG MOVEMENTS.</string>
    <string name="description_107">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1. PLACE YOUR FEET ON A BENCH OR ANY ELEVATED STEP AND GET INTO A STANDARD PUSHUP POSITION. \n\nSTEP 2. LOWER YOUR BODY UNTIL YOUR CHEST NEARLY TOUCHES THE FLOOR, PAUSE, THEN PUSH YOURSELF BACK TO THE STARTING POSITION. MAINTAIN PROPER FORM THROUGHOUT BY PREVENTING YOUR HIPS FROM SAGGING AT ANY POINT, KEEP YOUR CORE STIFF BY BRACING YOUR ABDOMINAL MUSCLES AND STRAIGHTEN YOUR LEGS WHILE PLACING YOUR WEIGHT ON YOUR TOES.</string>
    <string name="description_108">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1. LIE ON A FLAT BENCH WITH YOUR HEAD SUPPORTED AND YOUR FEET EITHER IN CONTRACT WITH THE FLOOR OR A RAISED PLATFORM. HOLD A DUMBBELL WITH BOTH HANDS, ENCIRCLING IT WITH YOUR PALMS AGAINST THE UNDERSIDE OF THE TOP SET OF PLATES. RAISE THE DUMBBELL UP IN FRONT OF YOUR CHEST, WITH YOUR ELBOWS SLIGHTLY BENT. \n\nSTEP 2. INHALE AND LOWER THE DUMBBELL BACK PAST YOUR HEAD AND BACK TO THE LIMIT 6NYDE2RANGE OF MOTION, KEEPING YOUR ELBOWS SLIGHTLY BENT AT ALL TIMES. HOLD THE STRETCH FOR A SECOND BEFORE EXHALING AND RETURNING THE DUMBBELL BACK UP TO THE STARTING POSITION. \n\nSTEP 3. REPEAT FOR THE NUMBER OF REPETITIONS DESIRED, MAINTAINING CORRECT POSTURE.</string>
    <string name="description_109">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE INCLINE BENCH. HOLD ONTO TWO DUMBBELLS WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. FULLY EXTEND YOUR ARMS ABOVE YOUR CHEST. \n\nSTEP 2: WHILE MAINTAINING A SLIGHT BEND IN YOUR ELBOWS, LOWER DUMBBELLS TO EACH SIDE UNTIL THE DUMBBELLS ARE NEXT TO YOUR UPPER BODY. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_110">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE PRONE ON THE FLOOR. RAISE YOURSELF UP SO THAT ONLY YOUR TOES AND FOREARMS ARE ON THE FLOOR. KEEP YOUR BACK STRAIGHT. LIFT YOUR RIGHT LEG UP. HOLD FOR AS LONG AS POSSIBLE.</string>
    <string name="description_111">MUSCLE GROUP: GLUTES \n\nSTEP 1. LIE FLAT ON THE FLOOR OR MAT WITH ARLÉ LEG EXTENDED STRAIGHT AND THE OTHER LEG BENT WITH THE FOOT FLAT ON THE FLOOR. PLACE YOUR ARMS DOWN ON THE MAT, ON THE SIDE OF YOUR HIPS. \n\nSTEP 2. RAISE YOUR LOWER BACK OFF THE FLOOR WHILE KEEPING YOUR EXTENDED LEG STRAIGHT. AORD THEN RETURN TO YOUR ORIGINAL POSITION AFTER A FEW REPETITIONS, SWITCH LEGS AND REPEAT WITH THE OTHER SIDE.</string>
    <string name="description_112">MUSCLE GROUP: HAMSTRINGS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR. PLACE YOUR FEET ON THE STABILITY BALL. YOUR LOWER BACK SHOULD BE LIFTED OFF THE GROUND. USE YOUR ARMS TO STABILIZE YOUR POSITION. \n\nSTEP 2: ROLL BALL TOWARDS YOUR BODY. AT THE END OF THE MOVEMENT, THE BOTTOMS OF YOUR FEET ARE ON THE BALL. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_113">MUSCLE GROUP: GLUTES \n\nSTEP 1. LIE FLAT ON THE FLOOR OR MAT WITH ARLÉ LEG EXTENDED STRAIGHT AND THE OTHER LEG BENT WITH THE FOOT FLAT ON THE FLOOR. PLACE YOUR ARMS DOWN ON THE MAT, ON THE SIDE OF YOUR HIPS. \n\nSTEP 2. RAISE YOUR LOWER BACK OFF THE FLOOR WHILE KEEPING YOUR EXTENDED LEG STRAIGHT. HOLD THEN RETURN TO YOUR ORIGINAL POSITION AFTER A FEW REPETITIONS, SWITCH LEGS AND REPEAT WITH THE OTHER SIDE.</string>
    <string name="description_269">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN CHEST FIRST WITH YOUR PALMS ON THE FLOOR. POSITION HANDS NEXT TO YOUR HEAD. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR HANDS AND TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD \n\nSTEP 2: BEND ONE LEG TOWARDS THE UPPER BODY. \n\nSTEP 3: AS YOU BRING YOUR LEG BACK TO STARTING POSITION, BEND OTHER LEG TOWARDS THE UPPER BODY. THIS IS ONE REPETITION.</string>
    <string name="description_115">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE PRONE ON THE FLOOR. RAISE YOURSELF UP SO THAT ONLY YOUR TOES AND HANDS ARE ON THE FLOOR. KEEP YOUR BACK STRAIGHT. \n\nSTEP 2: WHILE KEEPING ARMS IN PLACE, HOP INWARD SO YOUR KNEES ARE CLOSE TO YOUR CHEST. HOP BACK TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_116">MUSCLE NAME: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD MEDICINE BALL IN FRONT OF YOU WITH ARMS FULLY EXTENDED. \n\nSTEP 2: WHILE KEEPING YOUR BACK STRAIGHT, STEP TO YOUR SIDE WITH ONE FOOT AND LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. THE BACK FOOT PIVOTS BUT STAYS IN POSITION. STOP WHEN YOUR FRONT THIGH IS PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_117">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD DUMBBELLS OVERHEAD WITH ARMS STRAIGHT. \n\nSTEP 2: WHILE KEEPING YOUR BACK STRAIGHT, STEP FORWARD WITH ONE FOOT AND LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. STOP WHEN YOUR FRONT THIGH IS PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. \n\nSTEP 3: STEP BACK AND RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. \n\nSTEP 4: WHILE KEEPING YOUR BACK STRAIGHT, STEP FORWARD WITH THE OTHER FOOT AND LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. STOP WHEN YOUR FRONT THIGH IS PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. STEP BACK AND RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_118">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD MEDICINE BALL OVERHEAD WITH ARMS FULLY EXTENDED. \n\nSTEP 2: WHILE KEEPING YOUR BACK STRAIGHT, STEP TO YOUR SIDE WITH ONE FOOT AND LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. THE BACK FOOT PIVOTS BUT STAYS IN POSITION. STOP WHEN YOUR THIGH IS PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. REPEAT WITH OTHER SIDE.</string>
    <string name="description_119">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD THE MEDICINE BALL IN FRONT OF YOU. ADJUST FEET TO FACE SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. YOUR BACK SHOULD BE STRAIGHT THROUGHOUT THE WHOLE MOVEMENT. STOP WHEN YOUR THIGHS ARE PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. WHEN YOU RETURN THE STARTING POSITION, GENERATE ENERGY FROM YOUR LOWER BACK.</string>
    <string name="description_120">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD MEDICINE BALL OVERHEAD WITH ARMS FULLY EXTENDED. \n\nSTEP 2: WHILE KEEPING YOUR BACK STRAIGHT, STEP FORWARD WITH ONE FOOT AND LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. STOP WHEN YOUR FRONT THIGH IS PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. STEP BACK AND RETURN TO STARTING POSITION. REPEAT WITH OTHER SIDE.</string>
    <string name="description_121">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD YOUR ARMS IN THE FRONT OF YOUR CHEST. \n\nSTEP 2: WHILE KEEPING YOUR BACK STRAIGHT, STEP TO YOUR SIDE WITH ONE FOOT AND LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. THE BACK FOOT PIVOTS BUT STAYS IN POSITION. STOP WHEN YOUR FRONT THIGH IS PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_270">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1. WHILE LYING ON YOUR BACK, PLACE LOWER LEGS ON A SWISS BALL. THEN, PUT YOUR HANDS FLAT ON HIPS. \n\nSTEP 2. PUSH YOUR HIPS UP SO THAT YOUR BODY FORMS A STRAIGHT LINE FROM YOUR SHOULDERS TO YOUR KNEES. WITHOUT PAUSING, PULL YOUR HEELS TOWARD YOU AND ROLL THE BALL AS CLOSE AS POSSIBLE TO YOUR BUTT. \n\nSTEP 3. PAUSE, THEN ROLL THE BALL BACK UNTIL YOUR BODY IS IN A STRAIGHT LINE AGAIN.</string>
    <string name="description_123">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1. STAND UPRIGHT IN FRONT OF A BOSU WITH YOUR ARMS EXTENDED STRAIGHT DOWNWARD BY YOUR SIDE. THE BOSU SHOULD BE PLACED A COUPLE STEPS IN FRONT OF YOUR STANDING POSITION AND TO ONE SIDE. \n\nSTEP 2. STEP FORWARD AND SIDEWAYS ONTO THE BOSU, LOWERING YOUR BODY DOWNWARD SO THAT YOU HAVE A BEND YOUR ONE KNEE, WHILE KEEPING THE TRAILING LEG STRAIGHT. \n\nSTEP 3. PUSH OFF OF YOUR BENT FOOT TO RETURN TO STARTING POSITION AND REPEAT. TO MAKE THE EXERCISE MORE CHALLENGING, HOLD A PAIR OF DUMBBELLS IN EACH HAND AS YOU PERFORM THE ROUTINE.</string>
    <string name="description_124">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND TALL WITH YOUR BACK STRAIGHT. KEEP YOUR HANDS AT YOUR SIDES. \n\nSTEP 2: BEND KNEES SLIGHTLY. \n\nSTEP 3: JUMP UP AS HIGH AS YOU CAN.</string>
    <string name="description_125">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND TALL WITH YOUR BACK STRAIGHT. KEEP YOUR HANDS AT YOUR SIDES. \n\nSTEP 2: JUMP OUTWARD WITH YOUR FEET WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. AT THE SAME TIME, RAISE YOUR ARMS OVERHEAD. PAUSE BRIEFLY AND RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_126">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD DUMBBELLS AT YOUR SIDES WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. \n\nSTEP 2: WHILE KEEPING YOUR BACK STRAIGHT, STEP FORWARD WITH ONE FOOT AND LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. STOP WHEN YOUR FRONT THIGH IS PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. HOLD DUMBBELL OVERHEAD WITH ARMS STRAIGHT. STEP BACK AND RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_127">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1. FLIP A BOSU BALL OVER SO THAT THE FOUNDED PORTION IS FACING THE FLOOR. POSITION YOUR HANDS ON THE SIDES \n\nSTEP 2. BRACE YOUR ABDOMINAL AND CORE MUSCLES AS YOU LOWER YOURSELF SO THAT YOUR ENÉST REARLY TOUCHES THE BAL. TUCK YOUR ELBOWS AS YOU LOWER YOUR BODY SO THAT YOUR UPPER ARMS FORM A 45-DEGREE ANGLE WITH YOUR BODY AT THE BOTTOM OF THE MOVEMENT. \n\nSTEP 3. PAUSE AT THE BOTTOM, THEN PUSH YOURSELF BACK TO THE STARTING POSITION. DO NOT ALLOW YOUR HIPS TO SAG AT ANY POINT DURING THE MOVEMENT AND REPEAT.</string>
    <string name="description_128">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1. STAND UPRIGHT IN FRONT OF A BOSU WITH YOUR ARMS EXTENDED STRAIGHT DOWNWARD BY YOUR SIDE. THE BOSU SHOULD BE PLACED A COUPLE STEPS IN FRONT OF YOUR STANDING POSITION. \n\nSTEP 2. STEP FORWARD ONTO THE BOSU, LOWERING YOUR BODY DOWNWARD SO THAT YOU HAVE A BEND IN YOUR ONE KNEE, AS ILLUSTRATED \n\nSTEP 3. PUSH OFF OF THAT FOOT TO RETURN TO STARTING POSITION AND REPEAT. TO MAKE THE EXERCISE MORE CHALLENGING, HOLD A PAIR OF DUMBBELLS IN EACH HAND AS YOU PERFORM THE ROUTINE.</string>
    <string name="description_129">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1. STAND UPRIGHT ON A BOSU WITH YOUR FARMS BY YOUR SIDE. \n\nSTEP 2. BEND DOWN AT YOUR HIPS AND KNEES INTO A HALF-WAY SQUAT POSITION LEAN YDURITORSO FORWARD SLIGHTLY FOR BALANCE \n\nSTEP 3. JUMP STRAIGHT UPWARD BY PUSHING OFF YOUR FEET IN A CONTROLLED MANNER, TRYING TO LAND BACK INTO A SQUAT POSITION ON THE BOSU. FOR ADDED DIFFICULTY, HOLD A DUMBBELL IN EACH HAND.</string>
    <string name="description_130">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND TALL WITH YOUR BACK STRAIGHT. KEEP YOUR HANDS AT YOUR SIDES. \n\nSTEP 2: BEND KNEES SLIGHTLY. \n\nSTEP 3: JUMP UP AS HIGH AS YOU CAN. BRING YOUR KNEES TOWARD YOUR CHEST.</string>
    <string name="description_131">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD BARBELL WITH OVERHAND GRIP. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. ADJUST FEET TO FACE SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. LIFT BARBELL OVERHEAD WITH ARMS FULLY EXTENDED. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. YOUR BACK IS STRAIGHT THROUGHOUT THE WHOLE MOVEMENT. STOP WHEN YOUR THIGHS ARE PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. WHEN YOU RETURN THE STARTING POSITION, GENERATE ENERGY FROM YOUR LOWER BACK.</string>
    <string name="description_132">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET CLOSE TO EACH OTHER. RUN IN PLACE WHILE LIFTING KNEE TO STOMACH LEVEL. KEEP THE DUMBBELL IN YOUR HANDS AND BOXING IN THE SAME TIME WITH MOVING YOUR LEGS. \n\nSTEP 2: AS ONE FOOT LOWERS, THE OTHER RISES. THIS IS ONE REPETITION.</string>
    <string name="description_133">MUSCLE GROUP: HAMSTRINGS \n\nSTEP 1: SQUAT DOWN. HOLD DUMBBELLS UNDER YOU WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. KEEP BACK STRAIGHT. STICK CHEST OUTWARD AND LOOK AHEAD. \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT DUMBBELLS OFF THE GROUND. AS THE DUMBBELLS PASS YOUR SHIN, JUMP UPWARD. USE THE MOMENTUM TO RAISE DUMBBELLS TO YOUR SHOULDER. \n\nSTEP 3: AS YOU CATCH THE DUMBBELLS ON THE SHOULDER, SQUAT DOWN WITH THE MOMENTUM. STAND UP STRAIGHT AFTERWARDS. \n\nSTEP 4: BEND KNEES SLIGHTLY AND JUMP \n\nSTEP 5: DURING THE JUMP, RAISE DUMBBELLS OVERHEAD. STAND STRAIGHT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_134">MUSCLE GROUP: TRAPEZIUS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD DUMBBELLS AT YOUR SIDES WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. \n\nSTEP 2: BEND YOUR KNEES SLIGHTLY. \n\nSTEP 3: JUMP. SHRUG YOUR SHOULDERS WHEN YOU JUMP. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_135">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD ONTO THE DUMBBELLS WITH UNDERHAND GRIP. REST DUMBBELLS ON YOUR SHOULDERS. ADJUST FEET TO FACE SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. YOUR BACK SHOULD BE STRAIGHT THROUGHOUT THE WHOLE MOVEMENT. THE LOWERING MOTION IS SIMILAR TO SITTING ON A CHAIR. STOP WHEN YOUR THIGHS ARE PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. WHEN YOU RETURN THE STARTING POSITION, GENERATE ENERGY FROM YOUR LOWER BACK.</string>
    <string name="description_136">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD DUMBBELLS AT YOUR SIDES WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. \n\nSTEP 2: WHILE KEEPING YOUR BACK STRAIGHT, STEP FORWARD WITH ONE FOOT AND LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. STOP WHEN YOUR FRONT THIGH IS PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. STEP BACK AND RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_137">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD DUMBBELLS AT YOUR SIDES WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. \n\nSTEP 2: WHILE KEEPING YOUR BACK STRAIGHT, STEP TO YOUR SIDE WITH ONE FOOT AND LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. THE BACK FOOT STAYS IN POSITION. STOP WHEN YOUR FRONT THIGH IS PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_236">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD DUMBBELLS AT YOUR SIDES WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. \n\nSTEP 2: WHILE KEEPING YOUR BACK STRAIGHT, STEP TO YOUR SIDE WITH ONE FOOT AND LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. THE BACK FOOT STAYS IN POSITION. STOP WHEN YOUR FRONT THIGH IS PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_139">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT. LIFT LEFT LEG BEHIND YOU. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEE. YOUR BACK SHOULD BE STRAIGHT THROUGHOUT THE WHOLE MOVEMENT. STOP WHEN YOUR THIGH IS NEARLY PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. WHEN YOU RETURN THE STARTING POSITION, GENERATE ENERGY FROM YOUR LOWER BACK.</string>
    <string name="description_140">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD DUMBBELLS AT YOUR SIDES WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. \n\nSTEP 2: WHILE KEEPING YOUR BACK STRAIGHT, STEP FORWARD WITH ONE FOOT AND LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. STOP WHEN YOUR FRONT THIGH IS PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. STEP BACK AND RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_141">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. WHILE KEEPING YOUR BACK STRAIGHT, SQUAT DOWN. HOLD DUMBBELLS WITH OVERHAND GRIP IN FRONT OF YOUR SHINS. \n\nSTEP 2: JUMP AND PUSH YOURSELF UP. USE THE MOMENTUM TO RAISE DUMBBELLS OVERHEAD. SQUAT DOWN WHEN DUMBBELLS ARE OVERHEAD. \n\nSTEP 3: STAND UP STRAIGHT AND RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_142">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. \n\nSTEP 2: SQUAT DOWN AND TOUCH THE FLOOR WITH YOUR HANDS. \n\nSTEP 3: JUMP BACKWARD TO A PUSHUP POSITION. ONLY YOUR HANDS AND TOES ARE TOUCHING THE GROUND. \n\nSTEP 4: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARD YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND \n\nSTEP 5: FULL EXTEND YOUR ARMS TO GET BACK INTO PUSH UP POSITION. \n\nSTEP 6: JUMP FORWARD SO THAT YOUR FEET ARE NEAR YOUR HANDS. REMAIN IN A SQUAT POSITION. JUMP UPWARD WITH YOUR ARMS FULLY EXTENDED. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_143">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: SQUAT DOWN. HOLD DUMBBELL UNDER YOU WITH NEUTRAL KEEP BACK STRAIGHT. STICK CHEST OUTWARD AND LOOK AHEAD \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT DUMBBELL OFF THE GROUND. AS THE DUMBBELL PASSES YOUR SHIN, JUMP UPWARD. USE THE MOMENTUM TO RAISE DUMBBELL TO YOUR SHOULDER. \n\nSTEP 3: AS YOU CATCH THE DUMBBELL ON THE SHOULDER, SQUAT DOWN WITH THE MOMENTUM. STAND UP STRAIGHT AFTERWARDS. \n\nSTEP 4: BEND KNEES SLIGHTLY AND UP \n\nSTEP 5: DURING THE JUMP, RAISE DUMBBELL OVERHEAD. STAND STRAIGHT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_144">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1. BEGIN BY LYING ON THE BOSU BALL WITH YOUR HIPS JUST OFF THE EDGE OF THE BALL. PLACE YOUR HANDS BEHIND YOUR HEAD TO GENTLY SUPPORT YOUR NECK. \n\nSTEP 2. EXHALE AND CURL YOUR UPPER BODY OVER THE BOSU BALL. HOLD FOR A BRIEF SECOND AT THE TOP, BEFORE SLOWLY RETURNING TO THE STARTING POSITION. \n\nSTEP 3. MOVE IN A SLOW AND CONTROLLED FASHION. TRY TO KEEP YOUR HIPS STILL. FOCUS ON MOVING YOUR SPINE ONLY, NOT YOUR HIPS.</string>
    <string name="description_145">MUSCLE GROUP: GLUTES \n\nSTEP 1. STAND HOLDING DUMBBELLS IN FRONT OF YOUR THIGHS, PALMS TURNED TOWARD YOUR BODY. YOUR FEET SHOULD BE SHOULDER-WIDTH APART, TOES POINTED FORWARD. \n\nSTEP 2. LIFT YOUR RIGHT FOOT UP BEHIND YOU, A FEW INCHES OFF THE FLOOR, WITH YOUR RIGHT THIGH PERPENDICULAR TO THE FLOOR. PUSH YOUR HIPS BACK AND ALLOW YOUR TORSO TO BEND FORWARD, WHILE KEEPING YOUR ABS TIGHT AND BACK FLAT. YOUR LEFT KNEE SHOULD BENT SIGHTLY. \n\nSTEP 3. BEND FORWARD AS FAR AS YOU CAN WHILE KEEPING YOUR LOWER BACK FLAT. RETURN TO THE STARTING POSITION. REPEAT WITH THE OTHER LEG.</string>
    <string name="description_273">MUSCLE GROUP: SOLEUS \n\nSTEP 1: WHILE SEATED WITH BACK STRAIGHT, CENTER ONE DUMBBELL ON EACH OF YOUR LOWER THIGHS. USE YOUR HANDS TO STABILIZE ANY MOVEMENT. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE YOUR CALVES BY TIPTOEING. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_147">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: HOLD THE DUMBBELLS AT YOUR SIDES WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. STAND STRAIGHT WITH ONE FOOT FORWARD AND ONE FOOT BEHIND. REST THE BACK FOOT ON A BENCH. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR FRONT KNEE. STOP WHEN YOUR FRONT THIGH IS PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_274">MUSCLE GROUP: GASTROCNEMIUS \n\nSTEP 1: WHILE STANDING WITH BACK STRAIGHT, POSITION BARBELL ON TOP OF YOUR SHOULDERS. HOLD BARBELL WITH OVERHAND GRIP. DISTANCE BETWEEN HANDS SHOULD BE WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE YOUR CALVES BY TIPTOEING. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. LOWER YOUR CALVES BACK TO THE GROUND.</string>
    <string name="description_149">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH A FLAT BENCH BEHIND YOU. FEET ARE SHOULDER WIDTH APART. PLACE BARBELL ON THE BACK OF YOUR SHOULDERS. HOLD BARBELL WITH OVERHAND GRIP. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. ADJUST FEET TO FACE SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. YOUR BACK IS STRAIGHT THROUGHOUT THE WHOLE MOVEMENT. STOP WHEN YOUR THIGHS ARE PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND OR WHEN YOUR BEHIND TOUCHES THE BENCH. WHEN YOU RETURN THE STARTING POSITION, GENERATE ENERGY FROM YOUR LOWER BACK.</string>
    <string name="description_150">MUSCLE NAME: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: PLACE BARBELL ON THE BACK OF YOUR SHOULDERS. HOLD BARBELL WITH OVERHAND GRIP. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. STAND STRAIGHT WITH ONE FOOT FORWARD AND ONE FOOT BEHIND. REST THE BACK FOOT ON A BENCH. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR FRONT KNEE. STOP WHEN YOUR FRONT THIGH IS PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_272">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH A FLAT BENCH BEHIND YOU. FEET ARE SHOULDER WIDTH APART. PLACE BARBELL ON THE BACK OF YOUR SHOULDERS. HOLD BARBELL WITH OVERHAND GRIP. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. ADJUST FEET TO FACE SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. YOUR BACK IS STRAIGHT THROUGHOUT THE WHOLE MOVEMENT. STOP WHEN YOUR THIGHS ARE PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND OR WHEN YOUR BEHIND TOUCHES THE BENCH. WHEN YOU RETURN THE STARTING POSITION, GENERATE ENERGY FROM YOUR LOWER BACK.</string>
    <string name="description_152">MUSCLE GROUP: GLUTES \n\nSTEP 1. LIE ON THE FLOOR AND PLACE YOUR AEESP ON A CHAIR, KEEP YOUR KNEES SLIGHTLY BEND, AND YOUR ARMS AT YOUR SIDES. \n\nSTEP 2. PUSHING WITH YOUR GLUTES AND HAMSTRINGS, DIG THE HEELS OF YOUR FEET DOWN AND FITTAY OUR HIPS UNTIL YOUR BODY FORMS A RAMP. PAUSE, AND SLOWLY RETURN TO YOUR STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_153">MUSCLE: GASTROCNEMIUS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT. USE YOUR ARMS FOR BALANCE. RAISE ONE LEG OFF THE GROUND \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE YOUR OTHER CALF BY TIPTOEING. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_154">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND TALL WITH YOUR BACK STRAIGHT. KEEP YOUR HANDS AT YOUR SIDES. \n\nSTEP 2: BEND KNEES SLIGHTLY. \n\nSTEP 3: JUMP UP AS HIGH AS YOU CAN. BRING YOUR KNEES TOWARD YOUR CHEST.</string>
    <string name="description_155">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND TALL WITH YOUR BACK STRAIGHT. KEEP YOUR HANDS AT YOUR SIDES. \n\nSTEP 2: BEND KNEES SLIGHTLY. \n\nSTEP 3: JUMP UP AS HIGH AS YOU CAN. BRING YOUR KNEES TOWARD YOUR CHEST.</string>
    <string name="description_156">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND TALL WITH YOUR BACK STRAIGHT. KEEP YOUR HANDS AT YOUR SIDES. \n\nSTEP 2: BEND KNEES SLIGHTLY. MOVE FROM TO THE SIDES SUPPORTING YOUR LEG ON THE BENCH. \n\nSTEP 3: JUMP UP AS HIGH AS YOU CAN. BRING YOUR KNEES TOWARD YOUR CHEST.</string>
    <string name="description_157">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1. STAND UPRIGHT IN FRONT OF A BENCH WITH YOUR ARMS EXTENDED STRAIGHT DOWNWARD BY YOUR SIDE. THE BENCH SHOULD BE PLACED A COUPLE STEPS IN FRONT OF YOUR STANDING POSITION. \n\nSTEP 2. STEP FORWARD ONTO THE BENCH, LOWERING YOUR BODY DOWNWARD SO THAT YOU HAVE ABEND IN YOUR ONE KNEE, AS ILLUSTRATED \n\nSTEP 3. PUSH OFF OF THAT FOOT TO RETURN TO STARTING POSITION AND REPEAT. TO MAKE THE EXERCISE MORE CHALLENGING, HOLD A PAIR OF DUMBBELLS IN EACH HAND AS YOU PERFORM THE ROUTINE.</string>
    <string name="description_158">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH A FLAT BENCH BEHIND YOU. FEET ARE SHOULDER WIDTH APART. ADJUST FEET TO FACE SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. YOUR BACK IS STRAIGHT THROUGHOUT THE WHOLE MOVEMENT. STOP WHEN YOUR THIGHS ARE PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND OR WHEN YOUR BEHIND TOUCHES THE BENCH. WHEN YOU RETURN THE STARTING POSITION, GENERATE ENERGY FROM YOUR LOWER BACK.</string>
    <string name="description_159">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND TALL WITH YOUR BACK STRAIGHT. KEEP YOUR HANDS AT YOUR SIDES. \n\nSTEP 2: BEND KNEES SLIGHTLY. MOVE FROM TO THE SIDES SUPPORTING YOUR LEG ON THE BENCH. \n\nSTEP 3: JUMP UP AS HIGH AS YOU CAN. BRING YOUR KNEES TOWARD YOUR CHEST.</string>
    <string name="description_160">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. PLACE BARBELL ON THE BACK OF YOUR SHOULDERS. HOLD BARBELL WITH OVERHAND GRIP. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. \n\nSTEP 2: WHILE KEEPING YOUR BACK STRAIGHT, STEP BEHIND WITH ONE FOOT AND LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. STOP WHEN YOUR FRONT THIGH IS PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. STEP FORWARD TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_161">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD BARBELL WITH OVERHAND GRIP. PLACE BARBELL BEHIND YOUR HAMSTRINGS. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. YOUR BACK IS STRAIGHT THROUGHOUT THE WHOLE MOVEMENT. STOP WHEN YOUR THIGHS ARE PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND OR WHEN THE BARBELL TOUCHES THE FLOOR. WHEN YOU RETURN THE STARTING POSITION, GENERATE ENERGY FROM YOUR LOWER BACK.</string>
    <string name="description_162">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. PLACE BARBELL ON THE BACK OF YOUR SHOULDERS. HOLD BARBELL WITH OVERHAND GRIP. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. \n\nSTEP 2: WHILE KEEPING YOUR BACK STRAIGHT, STEP BEHIND WITH ONE FOOT AND LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. STOP WHEN YOUR FRONT THIGH IS PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. STEP FORWARD TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_163">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD BARBELL WITH OVERHAND GRIP. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. ADJUST FEET TO FACE SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. LIFT BARBELL OVERHEAD WITH ARMS FULLY EXTENDED \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. YOUR BACK IS STRAIGHT THROUGHOUT THE WHOLE MOVEMENT. STOP WHEN YOUR THIGHS ARE PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. WHEN YOU RETURN THE STARTING POSITION, GENERATE ENERGY FROM YOUR LOWER BACK.</string>
    <string name="description_164">MUSCLE GROUP: LOWER BACK \n\nSTEP 1: PLACE EZ CURL BAR ON THE FLOOR. POSITION YOURSELF SO THAT YOUR SHINS ARE AN INCH AWAY FROM THE BAR. STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. WITHOUT MUCH HIP MOVEMENT, LOWER YOURSELF TO GRASP THE EZ CURL BAR WITH OVERHAND GRIP. BEND KNEES SLIGHTLY. STICK CHEST OUTWARD AND LOOK AHEAD. \n\nSTEP 2: PULL EZ CURL BAR UP UNTIL YOU ARE STANDING STRAIGHT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_165">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD THE DUMBBELLS AT YOUR SIDES WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. ADJUST FEET TO FACE SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. YOUR BACK SHOULD BE STRAIGHT THROUGHOUT THE WHOLE MOVEMENT. STOP WHEN YOUR THIGHS ARE PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. WHEN YOU RETURN THE STARTING POSITION, GENERATE ENERGY FROM YOUR LOWER BACK.</string>
    <string name="description_166">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. PLACE BARBELL ON THE BACK OF YOUR SHOULDERS. HOLD BARBELL WITH OVERHAND GRIP. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. ADJUST FEET TO FACE SLIGHTLY OUTWARD \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. YOUR BACK IS STRAIGHT THROUGHOUT THE WHOLE MOVEMENT. STOP WHEN YOUR THIGHS ARE PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. WHEN YOU RETURN THE STARTING POSITION, GENERATE ENERGY FROM YOUR LOWER BACK.</string>
    <string name="description_167">MUSCLE NAME: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1. START IN A PUSHUP POSITION. KEEPING YOUR ARMS STRAIGHT AND YOUR CORE ENGAGED \n\nSTEP 2. SHIFT YOUR WEIGHT ONTO YOUR LEFT ARM, ROTATE YOUR TORSO TO THE RIGHT, AND RAISE YOUR RIGHT ARM TOWARD THE CEILING SO THAT YOUR BODY FORMS A T. \n\nSTEP 3. HOLD FOR THREE SECONDS, THEN RETURN TO START AND REPEAT ON THE OTHER SIDE. THAT\'S ONE REP.</string>
    <string name="description_275">MUSCLE NAME: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1. START IN A PUSHUP POSITION. KEEPING YOUR ARMS STRAIGHT AND YOUR CORE ENGAGED \n\nSTEP 2. SHIFT YOUR WEIGHT ONTO YOUR LEFT ARM, ROTATE YOUR TORSO TO THE RIGHT, AND RAISE YOUR RIGHT ARM TOWARD THE CEILING SO THAT YOUR BODY FORMS A T. \n\nSTEP 3. HOLD FOR THREE SECONDS, THEN RETURN TO START AND REPEAT ON THE OTHER SIDE. THAT\'S ONE REP.</string>
    <string name="description_169">MUSCLE GROUP: GLUTES, QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD DUMBBELLS WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. DUMBBELLS ARE POSITIONED ON YOUR SHOULDERS. \n\nSTEP 2: BEND KNEES SLIGHTLY. \n\nSTEP 3: PUSH UP UNTIL YOUR ARMS ARE FULLY EXTENDED OVERHEAD. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_170">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN CHEST FIRST WITH YOUR HANDS ON THE FLOOR. POSITION HANDS NEXT TO YOUR LOWER CHEST. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR HANDS AND TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. LIFT YOUR BEHIND UP IN THE AIR. ARMS SHOULD STRAIGHTEN OUT. \n\nSTEP 2: PRETENDING THAT THERE IS AN IMAGINARY BAR TWO FEET FROM THE GROUND, GO UNDER THE BAR UNTIL YOUR ENTIRE UPPER BODY PASSED THE BAR. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND. ARMS STRAIGHTEN OUT AT THE END OF THE MOVEMENT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_171">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1. SIT ON A SWISS-BALL WITH A LIGHT DUMBBELL IN EACH HAND. KEEP YOUR LEGS TOGETHER AND FEET FLAT ON THE FLOOR. YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE HANGING DOWN AT YOUR SIDES, WITH YOUR PALMS FACING BACK BEHIND YOU. \n\nSTEP 2. KEEPING YOUR ARMS PERFECTLY STRAIGHT, SLOWLY RAISE THE WEIGHTS OUT AND AP FRONT OF YOU UNTIL YOUR ARMS ARE PARALLEL TO THE FLOOR. \n\nSTEP 3. HOLD FOR A SECOND, THEN SLOWLY LOWER THE WEIGHTS BACK DOWN.</string>
    <string name="description_172">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1. SIT ON A SWISS-BALL WITH A LIGHT DUMBBELL IN EACH HAND. KEEP YOUR LEGS TOGETHER AND FEET FLAT ON THE FLOOR. YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE HANGING DOWN AT YOUR SIDES, WITH YOUR PALMS FACING BACK BEHIND YOU. \n\nSTEP 2. KEEPING YOUR ARMS PERFECTLY STRAIGHT, SLOWLY RAISE THE WEIGHTS OUT AND AP FRONT OF YOU UNTIL YOUR ARMS ARE PARALLEL TO THE FLOOR. \n\nSTEP 3. HOLD FOR A SECOND, THEN SLOWLY LOWER THE WEIGHTS BACK DOWN.</string>
    <string name="description_173">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1. STAND UPRIGHT, GRAB A SINGLE WEIGHT PLATE WITH ONE HAND ON EACH SIDE OF THE PLATE SIMILAR TO A CAR STEERING WHEEL. \n\nSTEP 2. RAISE THE IN FRONT OF YOU UNTIL YOU CAN SEE DOWN THE CENTER. \n\nSTEP 3. PAUSE FOR A FEW SECONDS, THEN LOWER IT IN A CONTROLLED AND SLOW MOTION.</string>
    <string name="description_174">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1. HOLD A WEIGHT PLATE USING BOTH AANDS AT THE LEVEL OF YOUR THIGHS. KEEP YOUR ARMS STRAIGHT, AND STAND FULLY UPRIGHT. \n\nSTEP 2. RAISE THE PLATE IN AN TO THE FRONT AND OVER YOUR SHOULDER TWISTING YOUR UPPER BODY TO THAT SIDE. \n\nSTEP 3. RETURN TO THE STARTING POSITION AND REPEAT THE MOTION BUT TARGET THE OTHER SIDE OF THE BODY.</string>
    <string name="description_276">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1. STAND UPRIGHT AND HOLD A LIGHT DUMBBELL ON EITHER SIDE OF YOUR LOWER CHEST, WITH FOREARMS POINTING STRAIGHT DOWN AND UPPER ARMS OUT TO THE SIDES YET SLIGHTLY LOWER THAN PARALLEL TO THE FLOOR. \n\nSTEP 2. KEEP YOUR SHOULDERS RELAXED SHRUG YOUR SHOULDERS AS IF YOU WERE TRYING FOLTOECH THEM TO YOUR EARS \n\nSTEP 3. HOLD THE TOP MOST POSITION, THEN GRADUALLY LOWER THEM TO THE STARTING POSITION. DO NOT BEND YOUR ELBOWS OR SHIFT YOUR HEAD FORWARD DURING THE MOTION REPEAT.</string>
    <string name="description_176">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1. STAND UPRIGHT AND HOLD A LIGHT DUMBBELL ON EITHER SIDE OF YOUR LOWER CHEST, WITH FOREARMS POINTING STRAIGHT DOWN AND UPPER ARMS OUT TO THE SIDES YET SLIGHTLY LOWER THAN PARALLEL TO THE FLOOR. \n\nSTEP 2. KEEP YOUR SHOULDERS RELAXED SHRUG YOUR SHOULDERS AS IF YOU WERE TRYING FOLTOECH THEM TO YOUR EARS \n\nSTEP 3. HOLD THE TOP MOST POSITION, THEN GRADUALLY LOWER THEM TO THE STARTING POSITION. DO NOT BEND YOUR ELBOWS OR SHIFT YOUR HEAD FORWARD DURING THE MOTION REPEAT.</string>
    <string name="description_177">MUSCLE GROUP: TRAPEZIUS \n\nSTEP 1. STAND UPRIGHT AND HOLD TWO FAIRLY AEAVY DUMBBELLS AT YOUR SIDES, WITH YOUR PALMS FACING EACH OTHER (NEUTRAL-GRIP). \n\nSTEP 2. KEEP YOUR SHOULDERS RELAXED SHRUG YOUR SHOULDERS AS IF YOU WERE TRYING FOLTOTCH THEM TO YOUR EARS. \n\nSTEP 3. HOLD THE TOP MOST POSITION, THEN GRADUALLY LOWER THEM TO THE STARTING POSITION. DO NOT BEND YOUR ELBOWS OR SHIFT HEAD FORWARD DURING THE MOTION. REPEAT.</string>
    <string name="description_178">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1. BEND OVER AT THE WAIST HOLDING THE DUMBBELL WITH YOUR ARMS STRAIGHT AND PALMS FACING IN, YOUR FEET HIP-WIDTH APART. \n\nSTEP 2. RAISE THE DUMBBELL UP AND OUTWARD TO SHOULDER HEIGHT, KEEPING YOUR BACK FLAT. BEND YOUR ELBOWS SLIGHTLY AS YOU LIFT IF NECESSARY, THEN LOWER THE DUMBBELL BACK TO THE START POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_179">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1. HOLD A PAIR OF DUMBBELLS SO THAT THUMBS ARE TURNED TOWARD EACH OTHER. FOCUS ON KEEPING YOUR BACK FLAT, ELBOWS SLIGHTLY BENT, AS YOU LEAN FORWARD AT THE WAIST AS FAR AS YOU CAN. LET THE DUMBBELLS HANG AT ARM\'S LENGTH \n\nSTEP 2. SLOWLY RAISE THE DUMBBELLS AS HIGH AS YOU CAN CHANGING THE BEND YOUR ELBOWS OR BENDING YOUR BACK. PAUSE, THEN LOWER THE DUMBBELLS TO THE STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_238">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1: BEGIN BY SQUATTING LOWER OVER A DUMBBELL. MAINTAIN A LOCKED AND RIGID LOWER BACK AND HAVE YOUR FEET PLACED A SHOULDER WIDTH APART. \n\nSTEP 2. GRASP THE DUMBBELL AND TIGHTEN THE ABDOMINAL MUSCLES. IN A RAPID AND US MOTION, LIFT THE DUMBBELL UPWARD UNTIL YOUR ARM IS STRAIGHT AND LOOKED, AS ILLUSTRATED. THE DUMBBELL SHOULD TRAVEL CLOSE TO THE BODY AND NOT SWING OUT OR AWAY. \n\nSTEP 3. BRIEFLY HOLD IT ABOVE YOUR HEAD, THEN BRING IT DOWN TO THE STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_181">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD DUMBBELL WITH OVERHAND GRIP. POSITION THE DUMBBELL NEXT TO YOUR HEAD. \n\nSTEP 2: BEND KNEES SLIGHTLY. \n\nSTEP 3: JUMP AND PUSH THE DUMBBELL UP. RAISE DUMBBELL OVERHEAD WITH ARMS FULLY EXTENDED. LAND WITH ONE FOOT FORWARD AND ONE FOOT BEHIND. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_277">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1. LIE BACKWARD ON A 45-DEGREE NCHIRIE BENCH WHILE HOLDING LIGHT DUMBBELLS IN EACH HAND. YOUR CHEST AND STOMACH SHOULD REST FLAT AGAINST THE BACKREST. \n\nSTEP 2. RAISE YOUR ELBOWS OUT TO YOUR SIDES UNTIL YOUR UPPER ARMS ARE PARALLEL TO THEHOOR WITH THE WEIGHTS POINTING DOWN YOUR ARMS SHOULD BE BENT AT 90-DEGREE ANGLES AT THIS POINT. \n\nSTEP 3. WITHOUT MOVING YOUR UPPER ARMS, ROTATE YOUR ARMS AND RAISE THE WEIGHTS FORWARD UNTIL YOUR FOREARMS ARE PARALLEL TO THE FLOOR YOUR ARMS SHOULD STILL BE BENT AT RIGHT ANGLES. THEN, REVERSE THE MOTION BY ROTATING THE WEIGHTS BACK DOWN.</string>
    <string name="description_183">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1: WHILE SEATED WITH BACK STRAIGHT, HOLD DUMBBELLS WITH OVERHAND GRIP. POSITION DUMBBELLS NEXT TO THE SIDES OF YOUR HEAD. \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT DUMBBELLS OVERHEAD UNTIL YOUR ARMS ARE FULLY EXTENDED. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_184">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1: WHILE SEATED WITH BACK STRAIGHT, HOLD DUMBBELLS AT YOUR SIDES WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. KEEP YOUR ARMS STRAIGHT. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE YOUR ARMS TO YOUR SIDES UNTIL THEY ARE PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_185">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1. GRAB A PAIR OF DUMBBELLS AND TAKE A SEATED POSITION ON AN INCLINE BENCH WITH ARMS STRAIGHT AND AT YOUR SIDES, THUMBS IN. \n\nSTEP 2. KEEPING YOUR ELBOWS STRAIGHT, RAISE THE DUMBBELLS UP AND FORWARD UNTIL HANDS ARE AT ABOUT EYE LEVEL. \n\nSTEP 3. KEEP THE BACKS OF YOUR WRISTS FLAT AND ELBOWS STRAIGHT THROUGHOUT. RETURN TO THE STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_186">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE ON YOUR SIDE ON THE INCLINE BENCH. HOLD DUMBBELL AT YOUR SIDE WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE YOUR ARM TO YOUR SIDE UNTIL IT IS PERPENDICULAR WITH YOUR UPPER BODY. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_187">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE PRONE ON THE INCLINE BENCH. HOLD DUMBBELLS UNDER YOU WITH OVERHAND GRIP. \n\nSTEP 2: AS YOU RAISE THE DUMBBELLS VERTICALLY TOWARDS YOUR CHEST, FLARE ELBOWS OUTWARD. STOP WHEN UPPER ARMS ARE PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_188">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1. GRAB A BARBELL WITH AN OVERHAND GRIP,SHOULDER—WIDTH APART, AND AT SHOULDER LEVEL IN FRONT OF YOUR BODY. YOUR KNEES SHOULD BE SLIGHTLY BENT AND SPACED SHOULDER-WIDTH APART. BRACE YOUR CORE MUSCLES. \n\nSTEP 2. BEND YOUR KNEES AND DIP YOUR BODY, WHILE KEEPING EVERYTHING ELSE IN TOA: \n\nSTEP 3. WITH A SUDDEN EXPLOSIVE PUSH, PRESS THE BARBELL OVER YOUR HEAD AS YOU PUSH UP WITH YOUR LEGS. YOUR ARMS SHOULD STRAIGHTEN COMPLETELY AS YOU PRESS THE BARBELL, AND YOUR LEGS SHOULD SPLIT APART SO THAT YOU ARE IN A STAGGERED STANCE ONE FOOT IN FRONT OF THE OTHER. KEEP YOUR FRONT KNEE SLIGHTLY BENT.</string>
    <string name="description_189">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1. STAND WITH YOUR FEET SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN FA SHOULDER-WIDTH APART AND TAKE AN OVERHAND GRIP ON A BARBELL WITH YOUR HANDS ALSO A SHOULDER-WIDTH APART. \n\nSTEP 2. PULL UP TO THE LEVEL OF YOUR CHIN, KEEPING THE BAR CLOSE TO YOUR BODY AND KEEPING YOUR ELBOWS HIGHER THAN THE BAR. \n\nSTEP 3. HOLD FOR A FEW SECONDS BEFORE LOWERING BACK TO THE START POSITION, ENSURING THAT YOUR ELBOWS REMAIN SLIGHTLY BENT AND AVDIDIRIG ANY BOUNCING OR JERKING MOVEMENTS.</string>
    <string name="description_190">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1. HOLD A BARBELL WITH A FULL OVERHAND, SHOULDER-WIDTH GRIP, AND STAND WITH THE BARBELL HANGING IN FRONT OF YOUR THIGHS. YOUR FEET SHOULD BE SHOULDER-WIDTH APART WITH YOUR KNEES SLIGHTLY BENT. PULL IN YOUR ABS AND TIGHTEN ALL YOUR UPPER-BODY MUSCLES, AND SLIGHTLY BEND YOUR ELBOWS. \n\nSTEP 2. RAISE THE BAR IN FRONT OF YOU UNTIL YOUR ARMS ARE PARALLEL TO THE FLOOR. \n\nSTEP 3. PAUSE, THEN RETURN TO THE STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_191">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1. PLACE A LOADED RACK AT ABOUT YOUR UPPER-CHEST LEVEL. GRASP THE BAR WITH BOTH HANDS, AND LIFT IT OFF THE RACK AND SUPPORT IT ON YOUR SHOULDERS. \n\nSTEP 2. DIP YOUR BODY BY SLIGHTLY BENDING THE KNEES, HIPS, AND ANKLES. \n\nSTEP 3. SUDDENLY DRIVE UPWARD WITH YOUR LEGS, PUSHING THE BARBELL UP OFF YOUR SHOULDERS AND VIGOROUSLY EXTENDING YOUR ARHIS OVERHEAD UNTIL YOUR ELBOWS ARE LOCKED \n\nSTEP 4. RETURN THE BARBELL BACK TO YOUR SHOULDERS AND REPEAT.</string>
    <string name="description_192">MUSCLE GROUP: LATISSIMUS 995G \n\nSTEP 1. WITH YOUR FEET SHOULDER-WIDTH APART AND YOUR KNEES BENT ROUGHLY 15 TO 30 DEGREES, KEEP YOUR TORSO STRAIGHT WITH A SLIGHT ARCH IN YOUR BACK AS YOU LEAN FORWARD AT THE HIPS. YOUR TORSO SHOULD BE, AT THIS POINT, ROUGHLY PARALLEL TO THE FLOOR. GRAB THE BARBELL OFF THE FLOOR USING A FALSE OVERHAND GRIP (THUMBS SHOULD BE IN LINE WITH THE REST OF YOUR FINGERS) THAT\'S SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH. LET THIS BAR HANG AT ARM\'S LENGTH IN FRONT OF YOU. \n\nSTEP 2. SLOWLY RETRACT YOUR SHOULDER BLADES AS TO HAVE THE BAR PULL UP TO THE POWER PART OF YOUR STERNUM. TRY NOT TO USE YOUR ARM MUSCLES, AND FOCUS ON GETTING THE MOST ACTIVITY OUT OF YOUR MIDDLE-BACK MUSCLES. \n\nSTEP 3. PAUSE AT THE TOP WHERE YOUR CHEST SHOULD BE STICKING OUT TOWARD THE BAR. THEN, SLOWLY RETURN TO THE STARTING POSITION WHILE KEEPING YOUR TORSO IN THE SAME POSITION</string>
    <string name="description_193">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN HANDS ON THE FLOOR. POSITION HANDS IN FRONT OF YOUR CHEST. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR HANDS AND TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR ELBOWS ARE NEARLY TOUCHING THE FLOOR. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_194">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN CHEST FIRST WITH YOUR HANDS ON THE FLOOR. POSITION HANDS NEXT TO YOUR LOWER CHEST. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR HANDS AND TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD \n\nSTEP 2: ALIGN YOUR SHOULDERS WITH YOUR HANDS, AND LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_195">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN CHEST FIRST WITH YOUR HANDS ON THE FLOOR. POSITION HANDS NEXT TO YOUR LOWER CHEST. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE SLIGHTLY THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR HANDS AND TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. POSITION MEDICINE BALL UNDER ONE HAND. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARD YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_196">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1. WHILE ON YOUR KNEES, PLACE YOUR AARDS A BOSU TURNED UPSIDE-DOWN. KEEP YOUR ARMS SHOULDER-WIDTH APART, ELBOWS BENT, AND CHEST AT NEAR TOUCHING POINT WITH THE BOSU. WHILE YOUR KNEES SHOULD BE BENT, MAKE SURE THAT YOUR FEET ARE UP AND NOT RESTING ON THE FLOOR, AS ILLUSTRATED. \n\nSTEP 2. PUSH UPWARD AND RAISE YOURSELF SO THAT YOUR ARMS ARE STRAIGHT. \n\nSTEP 3. LOWER YOUR CHEST ONCE MORE TOWARD THE BOSU. REPEAT. REMEMBER TO KEEP YOUR BACK FLAT THROUGHOUT THE MOVEMENT.</string>
    <string name="description_197">MUSCLE GROUP: PECTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: PLACE STABILITY BALL ON THE FLOOR. POSITION HANDS ON THE STABILITY BALL. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT YOUR HANDS ARE ON THE BALL AND YOUR TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE STABILITY BALL BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_198">MUSCLE GROUP: TRICEPS BRACHII \n\nSTEP 1. LAY BACKWARD ON A SWISS-BALL AND ENTER YOUR BACK ON IT. HOLD A PAIR OF DUMBBELLS IN YOUR ARMS AND STRAIGHTEN THEM OVER YOUR CHEST \n\nSTEP 2. BEND YOUR ELBOWS, BRINGING THE DUMBBELLS DOWN TO THE SIDES OF YOUR HEAD. \n\nSTEP 3. STRAIGHTEN YOUR ARMS, RAISING THE DUMBBELLS BACK TO THE START POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_199">MUSCLE GROUP: LOWER BACK \n\nSTEP 1. STAND WITH YOUR FEET SHOULDER- WIDTH APART AND WITH YOUR KNEES SLIGHTLY BENT. HOLD A LIGHT DUMBBELL IN EACH HAND AND BEND FORWARD AT THE WAIST UNTIL YOUR TORSO IS ALMOST PARALLEL TO THE FLOOR. HANG YOUR ARMS STRAIGHT DOWN WITH YOUR FACING IN, AS ILLUSTRATED. \n\nSTEP 2. ROW THE WEIGHTS STRAIGHT UP UNTIL THEY REACH THE SIDES OF YOUR CHEST AND YOUR ARHIS E BENT AT RIGHT ANGLES. IDEALLY, YOUR UPPER ARMS SHOULD BE PARALLEL TO THE FLOOR. \n\nSTEP 4. SQUEEZE YOUR TRICEPS, THEN BEND YOUR ELBOWS TO LOWER THE WEIGHTS BACK DOWN SO THAT THEY ARE ALONG YOUR SIDES ONCE AGAIN. \n\nSTEP 5. FINALLY, LOWER THE WEIGHTS BACK DOWN UNTIL YOUR ARMS ARE HANGING STRAIGHT DOWN.</string>
    <string name="description_200">MUSCLE GROUP: TRICEPS BRACHII \n\nSTEP 1. STAND STRAIGHT UPRIGHT WITH YOUR FEET SHOULDER-WIDTH APART, HOLDING A LIGHT DUMBBELL IN YOUR LEFT HAND. \n\nSTEP 2. PRESS THE DUMBBELL OVER YOUR HEAD SO THAT YOUR LEFT ARM IS STRAIGHT PALM POINTING OUT TO THE SIDE. REACH YOUR RIGHT ARM ACROSS YOUR FACE AND CUP YOUR LEFT ELBOW WITH YOUR RIGHT HAND THIS WILL HELP KEEP YOUR UPPER ARM STABLE AS YOU PERFORM THE EXERCISE. \n\nSTEP 3. WITHOUT MOVING YOUR UPPER ARM, SLOWLY BEND YOUR LEFT ELBOW AND LOWER THE DUMBBELL BEHIND YOUR HEAD AS FAR AS POSSIBLE \n\nSTEP 4. EXTEND THE DUMBBELL BACK OVERHEAD UNTIL YOUR LEFT ARM IS STRAIGHT AND REPEAT FOR ONE SET. THEN PLACE THE DUMBBELL IN YOUR RIGHT HAND AND REPEAT THE EXERCISE WITH YOUR RIGHT ARM.</string>
    <string name="description_278">MUSCLE GROUP: TRICEPS BRACHII \n\nSTEP 1. STAND STRAIGHT UPRIGHT WITH YOUR FEET SHOULDER-WIDTH APART, HOLDING A DUMBBELL OVERHEAD WITH BOTH HANDS UNDER THE INNER PLATE, AS SHOWN. HAVE IT HANG BEHIND YOUR UPPER BACK WITH ELBOWS BENT. \n\nSTEP 2. RAISE THE DUMBBELL OVERHEAD BY EXTENDING YOUR ELBOWS WHILE EXTENDING YOUR WRISTS. AT THE TOP, HOLD, THEN RETURN TO THE STARTING POSITION IN A CONTROLLED MANNER. REPEAT.</string>
    <string name="description_202">MUSCLE GROUP: TRICEPS BRACHII \n\nSTEP 1. PLACE YOUR PALMS ON A BENCH SO THEY FACE FORWARD, AND POSITION YOURSELF AS ILLUSTRATED. KEEP YOUR LEGS RELATIVELY STRAIGHT OUT IN FRONT, WITH BOTH HEELS FIRMLY ON THE FLOOR. STRAIGHTEN YOUR ARMS AND MOVE YOUR TORSO FORWARD SO THAT YOUR BEHIND AND BACK ARE JUST IN FRONT OF THE BENCH. \n\nSTEP 2. BEND YOUR ARMS TO RIGHT ANGLES, LOWERING YOUR BEHIND TOWARD THE FLOOR AS SHOWN. YOU CAN MAKE THE EXERCISE EASIER BY BY BENDING YOUR KNEES AND MOVING YOUR FEET CLOSER TO THE BENCH.</string>
    <string name="description_203">MUSCLE GROUP: TRICEPS BRACHII \n\nSTEP 1. GRAB A BARBELL WITH A SHOULDER- WIDTH, OVERHEAD GRIP. HOLD THE BAR AT ARM\'S LENGTH OVER YOUR HEAD. \n\nSTEP 2. WITHOUT MOVING YOUR UPPER ARMS, BEND YOUR ELBOWS TO LOWER BAR BEHIND YOUR AHEAD UNTIL YOUR FORE-ARMS ARE JUST PAST PARALLEL TO THE FLOOR. \n\nSTEP 3. PAUSE IN THIS POSITION, THEN RETURN THE BAR TO THE STARTING POSITION BY STRAIGHTENING YOUR ARMS.</string>
    <string name="description_204">MUSCLE GROUP: TRICEPS BRACHII \n\nSTEP 1. LIE ON A BENCH WITH YOUR KNEES BENT FARID FEET FLAT ON THE FLOOR. HOLD A FAIRLY LIGHT DUMBBELL IN YOUR LEFT HAND AND STRAIGHTEN THE ARM SO THAT THE WEIGHT IS ABOVE YOUR SHOULDER. USE YOUR RIGHT HAND TO REACH ACROSS YOUR CHEST AND UP THE UPPER PART OF YOUR LEFT ARM TO HELP STABILIZE IT. \n\nSTEP 2. TURN THE WEIGHT SO THAT YOUR PALM FACES IN. WITHOUT MOVING YOUR UPPER ARM BEND YOUR ELBOW AND SLOWLY LOWER THE DUMBBELL UNTIL IT REACHES THE SIDE OF YOUR HEAD. \n\nSTEP 3. SLOWLY PRESS THE WEIGHT BACK UP ABOVE YOU. FINISH THE SET, THEN SWITCH POSITIONS TO WORK YOUR RIGHT ARM.</string>
    <string name="description_279">MUSCLE GROUP: TRICEPS BRACHII \n\nSTEP 1: LIE BACK ON THE FLAT BENCH. HOLD BARBELL WITH SHOULDER WIDTH OVERHAND GRIP. FULLY EXTEND ARMS ABOVE YOUR HEAD. \n\nSTEP 2: WHILE KEEPING YOUR UPPER ARMS STATIONARY, LOWER THE BARBELL UNTIL IT IS BEHIND YOUR HEAD. REFRAIN FROM FLARING YOUR ELBOWS. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_206">Muscle Group: Triceps Brachii \n\nSTEP 1. Begin by grabbing a pair of lls and lying on a bench. With a neutral, shoulder- width grip, keep your arms straight as you hold the dumbbells up over your forehead. \n\nSTEP 2. Bend your elbows as you lower the weights down to the sides of your fohehead. Try ping your upper arms in the same position, and pause when your elbows are bent just past 90 degrees. Return to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="description_207">MUSCLE GROUP: TRICEPS BRACHII \n\nSTEP 1. GRAB A BARBELL WITH A SHOULDER- WIDTH, OVERHEAD GRIP. HOLD THE BAR AT ARM\'S LENGTH OVER YOUR HEAD. \n\nSTEP 2. WITHOUT MOVING YOUR UPPER ARMS, BEND YOUR ELBOWS TO LOWER THE BAR BEHIND YOUR FHEAD UNTIL YOUR FORE-ARMS ARE JUST PAST PARALLEL TO THE FLOOR. \n\nSTEP 3. PAUSE IN THIS POSITION, THEN RETURN THE BAR TO THE STARTING POSITION BY STRAIGHTENING YOUR ARMS.</string>
    <string name="description_208">MUSCLE GROUP: LATISSIMUS DORSI \n\nSTEP 1: STAND WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. KEEP YOUR LEGS SLIGHTLY BENT. POSITION YOUR HANDS IN FRONT OF YOU. INTERLACE YOUR FINGERS. \n\nSTEP 2: EXTEND YOUR ARMS OVERHEAD. PULL AS HIGH AS YOU CAN. HOLD THIS POSITION FOR 15-25 SECONDS.</string>
    <string name="description_209">MUSCLE GROUP: NECK \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. POSITION YOUR ARMS AT YOUR SIDE. \n\nSTEP 2: TURN YOUR NECK TO THE SIDE. YOUR UPPER BODY TWISTS SLIGHTLY. HOLD FOR 15-25 SECONDS. REPEAT WITH OTHER SIDE.</string>
    <string name="description_210">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. \n\nSTEP 2: FULLY EXTEND YOUR RIGHT ARM ACROSS YOUR BODY. THE ARM IS PARALLEL WITH THE FLOOR. POSITION YOUR LEFT ARM IN FRONT YOUR LEFT WRIST. USE YOUR LEFT ARM TO PULL YOUR RIGHT ARM CLOSER TO THE BODY. HOLD THIS POSITION FOR 15- 25 SECONDS. REPEAT WITH THE OTHER ARM.</string>
    <string name="description_211">MUSCLE TRICEPS BRACHII \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. POSITION ONE HAND ON THE CENTER OF YOUR UPPER BACK. YOUR ELBOW POINTS TOWARD THE CEILING. \n\nSTEP 2: USE YOUR OTHER HAND TO HOLD YOUR ELBOW. PULL ELBOW DOWN AND TOWARD YOUR HEAD. HOLD THIS POSITION FOR 15-25 SECONDS. REPEAT WITH OTHER SIDE.</string>
    <string name="description_240">MUSCLE GROUP: LATISSIMUS DORSI \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. POSITION YOUR HANDS ON YOUR HIPS. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE ONE ARM OVERHEAD AND BEND YOUR BODY TOWARD ONE SIDE. HOLD FOR 15-25 SECONDS. REPEAT WITH OTHER SIDE.</string>
    <string name="description_213">MUSCLE GROUP: LATISSIMUS DORSI \n\nSTEP 1: SQUAT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. POSITION YOUR HANDS ON YOUR HIPS. LOOK FORWARD \n\nSTEP 2: TWIST YOUR TORSO IN ONE DIRECTION UNTIL YOU FEEL A STRETCH. REPEAT WITH OTHER SIDE.</string>
    <string name="description_214">MUSCLE GROUP: HAMSTRINGS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH WIDER THAN FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. POSITION YOUR HANDS ON YOUR HIPS. \n\nSTEP 2: WITHOUT BENDING YOUR LEGS, REACH DOWN AND WRAP YOUR HANDS AROUND YOUR ANKLES. HOLD FOR 15-25 SECONDS.</string>
    <string name="description_215">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET CLOSE TOGETHER. REST YOUR HANDS AT YOUR SIDES. \n\nSTEP 2: BEND ONE KNEE BEHIND YOU. HOLD ONTO KNEE WITH YOUR HAND. PULL FOOT TOWARDS YOUR HAMSTRINGS. HOLD FOR 15-25 SECONDS. REPEAT WITH OTHER LEG.</string>
    <string name="description_216">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: SIT STRAIGHT WITH YOUR LEGS FULLY EXTENDED. BEND YOUR RIGHT KNEE POSITION YOUR RIGHT FOOT ON YOUR LEFT INNER THIGH. \n\nSTEP 2: TOUCH YOUR LEFT TOES WITH YOUR LEFT HAND. HOLD FOR 15-25 SECONDS. REPEAT WITH OTHER LEG.</string>
    <string name="description_217">MUSCLE GROUP: ADDUCTORS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET MORE THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. PLACE YOUR HANDS ON YOUR HIPS. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOUR BODY TOWARD ONE SIDE. YOUR OPPOSITE LEG IS STRAIGHTENED OUT. HOLD FOR 15-25 SECONDS. REPEAT WITH OTHER SIDE.</string>
    <string name="description_242">MUSCLE HAMSTRINGS \n\nSTEP 1: SIT DOWN WITH YOUR BACK STRAIGHT. FULLY EXTEND YOUR LEGS IN FRONT OF YOU. REST YOUR ARMS ON YOUR THIGHS. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOUR UPPER BODY TOWARD YOUR LEGS. HOLD THIS POSITION FOR 15-25 SECONDS.</string>
    <string name="description_219">MUSCLE HAMSTRINGS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE FLAT ON THE FLOOR. FULLY EXTEND YOUR LEGS. REST YOUR HANDS YOUR SIDE. \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT ONE LEG TOWARD YOUR CHEST. YOUR KNEE REMAINS BENT. POSITION YOUR HANDS ON YOUR THIGH. PULL YOUR LEG TOWARD YOUR UPPER BODY. HOLD THIS POSITION FOR 15-25 SECONDS. REPEAT WITH OTHER LEG.</string>
    <string name="description_244">MUSCLE: ADDUCTORS \n\nSTEP 1: SIT WITH THE SOLE OF YOUR AGAINST EACH OTHER. KEEP YOUR BACK STRAIGHT. POSITION HANDS ON YOUR ANKLES. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOUR UPPER BODY AND KNEES TOWARD FLOOR. HOLD FOR 15-25 SECONDS.</string>
    <string name="description_221">MUSCLE GROUP: LOWER BACK \n\nSTEP 1: KNEEL ON THE FLOOR WITH BACK STRAIGHT. \n\nSTEP 2: AS YOU STRAIGHTEN YOUR ARMS IN FRONT OF YOU, SIT DOWN SO THAT YOUR BEHIND TOUCHES YOUR FEET. KEEP YOUR BACK AND HEAD STRAIGHT.</string>
    <string name="description_222">MUSCLE GROUP: LOWER BACK \n\nSTEP 1: LIE PRONE ON FLOOR EXTENDED. POSITION YOUR HANDS NEXT TO YOUR CHEST WITH PALMS FACING DOWN. \n\nSTEP 2: USE YOUR ARMS TO LIFT YOUR BODY TOWARD THE CEILING. YOUR ARMS ARE FULLY EXTENDED. HOLD THIS POSITION FOR 15-25 SECONDS.</string>
    <string name="description_223">MUSCLE GROUP:QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND WITH BACK STRAIGHT. KEEP YOUR HANDS AT YOUR SIDE. HOP TO THE RIGHT SIDE. AT THE SAME AND BRING YOUR LEFT LEG BEHIND THE RIGHT. FRONT KNEE IS SLIGHTLY BENT. \n\nSTEP 2: HOP TO THE LEFT SIDE. AT THE SAME TIME, LOWER YOUR BODY AND BRING YOUR RIGHT LEG BEHIND THE OTHER. FRONT KNEE IS SLIGHTLY BENT</string>
    <string name="description_224">MUSCLE GROUP:QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD MEDICINE BALL IN FRONT OF YOU WITH ARMS FULLY EXTENDED. ADJUST FEET TO FACE SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. YOUR BACK IS STRAIGHT THROUGHOUT THE WHOLE MOVEMENT. STOP WHEN YOUR THIGHS ARE NEARLY PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. WHEN YOU RETURN THE STARTING POSITION, GENERATE ENERGY FROM YOUR LOWER BACK.</string>
    <string name="description_225">MUSCLE GROUP:QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD MEDICINE BALL IN FRONT OF YOU WITH ARMS FULLY EXTENDED. ADJUST FEET TO FACE SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. YOUR BACK IS STRAIGHT THROUGHOUT THE WHOLE MOVEMENT. STOP WHEN YOUR THIGHS ARE NEARLY PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. WHEN YOU RETURN THE STARTING POSITION, GENERATE ENERGY FROM YOUR LOWER BACK.</string>
    <string name="description_226">MUSCLE GROUP:PRCTORIALIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN CHEST FIRST WITH YOUR HANDS ON THE FLOOR. POSITION HANDS UNDER YOUR SHOULDERS. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE NARROWER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR HANDS AND TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. \n\nSTEP 3: TOUCH YOUR OPPOSITE SHOULDER AFTER EVERY TIME YOU COME UP. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_227">MUSCLE GROUP:QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART\n\nSTEP 2: SQUAT DOWN AND TOUCH THE FLOOR WITH YOUR HANDS.\n\nSTEP 3: JUMP BACKWARD TO A PUSHUP POSITION. ONLY YOUR HANDS AND TOES ARE TOUCHING THE GROUND\n\nSTEP 4: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARD YOUR FEET. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND.\n\nSTEP 5: FULL EXTEND YOUR ARMS TO GET BACK INTO PUSHUP POSITION.\n\nSTEP 6: JUMP FORWARD SO THAT YOUR FEET NEAR YOUR HANDS. REMAIN IN A SQUAT POSITION. JUMP UPWARD WITH YOUR ARMS FULLY EXTENDED. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_228">MUSCLE GROUP:QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. ADJUST FEET TO FACE SLIGHTLY OUTWARD.\n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. YOUR BACK SHOULD BE STRAIGHT THROUGHOUT THE WHOLE MOVEMENT. STOP WHEN YOUR THIGHS ARE PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. WHEN YOU RETURN THE STARTING POSITION, GENERATE ENERGY FROM YOUR LOWER BACK.</string>
    <string name="description_229">MUSCLE GROUP:PECTORALIS\n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN CHEST RST WITH YOUR HANDS ON THE FLOOR. POSITION HANDS NEXT TO YOUR LOWER CHEST. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. LIFT YOURSELF WITH YOUR ARMS SO THAT ONLY YOUR HANDS AND TOES ARE ON THE FLOOR. MAINTAIN A STRAIGHT BACK. HANDS POINT SLIGHTLY OUTWARD \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. AT THE SAME TIME, BRING ONE KNEE TOWARDS YOUR ELBOW. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND\n\nSTEP 3: RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.\n\nSTEP 4: LOWER YOURSELF UNTIL YOUR CHEST IS INCHES AWAY FROM THE FLOOR BY BENDING YOUR ELBOWS. THE ELBOWS SHOULD BEND TOWARDS YOUR FEET. AT THE SAME TIME, BRING YOUR OTHER KNEE TOWARDS YOUR ELBOW. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND.</string>
    <string name="description_230">MUSCLE GROUP:RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1. STANDING SO THAT YOUR FEET ARE SHOULDER-WIDTH APART, PLACE YOUR FINGERS BEHIND YOUR EARS\n\nSTEP 2. TOUCH YOUR LEFT ELBOW TO YOUR RIGHT KNEE AS YOU RAISE THE KNEE WHILE YOU REACHING YOUR LEFT POINT TOWARD YOUR RIGHT HIP.\n\nSTEP 3. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION AND REPEAT WITH THE OTHER SIDE. REPEAT THE TWO SEQUENCES REPEATEDLY.</string>
    <string name="description_231">MUSCLE GROUP:RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR. PLACE HANDS AT YOUR SIDES. EXTEND LEGS FULLY\n\nSTEP 2: RAISE LEGS TO A 30 DEGREE ANGLE. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND \n\nSTEP 3: RAISE LEGS TO A 60 DEGREE ANGLE. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND\n\nSTEP 4: RAISE LEGS TO A 90 DEGREE ANGLE. HOLD ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_232">MUSCULAR GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: BEGIN ON YOUR AND KNEES IN TABLE TOP POSE.\n\nSTEP 2: INHALE AND REACH YOUR TAILBONE UP AND TOWARDS THE CEILING, LETTING YOUR SPINE ARCH AND YOUR BELLY DROP TOWARDS THE FLOOR.\n\nSTEP 3: HOLD HERE FOR SEVERAL BREATHS.\n\nSTEP 4: TO COME OUT, EXHALE AND COME BACK TO NORMAL POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_233">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: POSITION LEGS STRAIGHT EXTENDED. WHILE KEEPING BACK STRAIGHT, PLACE FOREARMS ON THE FLOOR. YOUR FOREARMS ARE PERPENDICULAR WITH YOUR UPPER ARMS. HOLD FOR AS LONG AS YOU CAN.</string>
    <string name="description_13">MUSCLE GROUP: OBLIQUES \n\nSTEP 1: LIE ON YOUR SIDE. MAKE SURE ONE LEG IS ON TOP OF THE OTHER. POSITION THE FOREARM ON THE FLOOR PERPENDICULAR WITH YOUR BODY. \n\nSTEP 2: USE YOUR FOREARM TO LIFT YOUR UPPER BODY OF THE GROUND. THE OTHER ARM IS PLACED ON THE SIDE OF YOUR BODY. YOUR BODY SHOULD BE STRAIGHT. ONLY YOUR FOREARM AND THE SIDE OF YOUR FOOT SHOULD BE TOUCHING THE FLOOR. HOLD THIS POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_29">MUSCLE GROUP: OBLIQUES \n\nSTEP: 1: POSITION ONE FOREARM ON THE BENCH WITH YOUR FEET ON THE FLOOR. THE ENTIRE FOREARM SHOULD BE ON THE BENCH. MAKE SURE ONE LEG IS ON TOP OF THE OTHER. THE OTHER ARM IS PLACED ON THE SIDE OF YOUR BODY. \n\nSTEP 2: KEEP YOUR BODY STRAIGHT. ONLY YOUR FOREARM SHOULD BE TOUCHING THE BENCH AND ONLY THE SIDE OF YOUR FOOT SHOULD BE TOUCHING THE FLOOR. HOLD THIS POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_10">MUSCLE GROUP: OBLIQUES \n\nSTEP 1: LAI DOWN ON THE FLOOR, BEND YOUR LEGS AND PUT YOUR FEET ON THE GROUND. MOVE YOUR HANDS BEHIND YOUR EARS AND PUT YOUR ELBOWS OUT. CURVE YOUR RIGHT LEG UP AND REST YOUR FOOT ON YOUR LEFT KNEE. \n\nSTEP 2: CRUNCH FORWARDS AND LIFT IT SIDEWAYS AND TRY TO TOUCH YOUR LEFT ELBOW TO YOUR RIGHT KNEE. THAN CRUNCH BACKWARDS, NOW SWAP AND CRUNCH FORWARD AND LIFT IT SIDEWAYS AND TRY TO TOUCH YOUR RIGHT ELBOW TO YOUR LEFT KNEE. REPEAT THIS.</string>
    <string name="description_14">MUSCLE NAME: OBLIQUES \n\nSTEP 1: LIE ON YOUR SIDE WITH YOUR BODY IN A STRAIGHT LINE AND YOUR ARMS CROSSED AGAINST YOUR CHEST. \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT YOUR LEGS OFF THE FLOOR, MAKING SURE TO KEEP THEM TIGHTLY BOUND CONTRACTING, EVEN THOUGHT THERE ISN\'T TOO MUCH MOTION INVOLVED. \n\nSTEP 3: PAUSE, THEN SLOWLY RETURN TO THE STARTING POSITION. REPEAT AS MANY TIMES AS NEEDED THEN SWITCH SIDES.</string>
    <string name="description_17">MUSCLE GROUSZECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR WITH YOUR HANDS ASIDE, AND YOUR FEET STRAIGHT. \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT ONE LEG, BEND IT TO 90 DEGREES AND LAY IT OVER THE OTHER ONE, THAT STAYS STRAIGHT. \n\nSTEP 3: MAINTAINING THIS POSITION START THE EXERCISE BY LIFTING THE STRAIGHT LEG UP. \n\nSTEP 4: REPEAT THIS POSITION AS NECESSARY. SWITCH LEGS AND REPEAT.</string>
    <string name="description_51">MUSCLE GROUP: RECTUS ABDOMINIS \n\nSTEP 1: KEEP YOUR LEGS DOWN AND PLACE YOUR HANDS ON THE FLOOR. RAISE YOUR RIGHT ARM AND LEFT LEG UP INTO THE AIR. \n\nSTEP 2: BRING YOUR ARM AND LEG OUTWARD. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_61">MUSCLE GROUP: LATISSIMUS DORSI \n\nSTEP 1: KNEEL WITH ONE LEG ON A FLAT BENCH AND PLACE ONE HAND ON THE BENCH FOR SUPPORT. PLACE OTHER LEG ON THE FLOOR AND HOLD DUMBBELL WITH A NEUTRAL GRIP. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE THE DUMBBELL VERTICALLY TOWARDS YOUR CHEST. REFRAIN FROM FLARING YOUR ELBOW OUT. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_70">MUSCLE GROUP: BICEBS BRACHII \n\nSTEP 1: SID DOWN ON THE BENCH. KEEP BACK BENT AND STRAIGHT. HOLD ONE DUMBBELL WITH UNDERHAND GRIP. POSITION ELBOW AT THE INNER THIGH. \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT DUMBBELL UP WHILE KEEPING YOUR UPPER ARM IN PLACE. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_151">MUSCLE NAME: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: PLACE BARBELL ON THE BACK OF YOUR SHOULDERS. HOLD BARBELL WITH OVERHAND GRIP. DISTANCE BETWEEN YOUR HANDS SHOULD BE WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. STAND STRAIGHT WITH ONE FOOT FORWARD AND ONE FOOT BEHIND. REST THE BACK FOOT ON A BENCH. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR FRONT KNEE. STOP WHEN YOUR FRONT THIGH IS PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_122">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD YOUR ARMS IN THE FRONT OF YOUR CHEST. \n\nSTEP 2: WHILE KEEPING YOUR BACK STRAIGHT, STEP TO YOUR SIDE WITH ONE FOOT AND LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. THE BACK FOOT PIVOTS BUT STAYS IN POSITION. STOP WHEN YOUR FRONT THIGH IS PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_138">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT. LIFT LEFT LEG BEHIND YOU. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEE. YOUR BACK SHOULD BE STRAIGHT THROUGHOUT THE WHOLE MOVEMENT. STOP WHEN YOUR THIGH IS NEARLY PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. WHEN YOU RETURN THE STARTING POSITION, GENERATE ENERGY FROM YOUR LOWER BACK.</string>
    <string name="description_146">MUSCLE GROUP: GLUTES \n\nSTEP 1. STAND HOLDING DUMBBELLS IN FRONT OF YOUR THIGHS, PALMS TURNED TOWARD YOUR BODY. YOUR FEET SHOULD BE SHOULDER-WIDTH APART, TOES POINTED FORWARD. \n\nSTEP 2. LIFT YOUR RIGHT FOOT UP BEHIND YOU, A FEW INCHES OFF THE FLOOR, WITH YOUR RIGHT THIGH PERPENDICULAR TO THE FLOOR. PUSH YOUR HIPS BACK AND ALLOW YOUR TORSO TO BEND FORWARD, WHILE KEEPING YOUR ABS TIGHT AND BACK FLAT. YOUR LEFT KNEE SHOULD BENT SIGHTLY. \n\nSTEP 3. BEND FORWARD AS FAR AS YOU CAN WHILE KEEPING YOUR LOWER BACK FLAT. RETURN TO THE STARTING POSITION. REPEAT WITH THE OTHER LEG.</string>
    <string name="description_148">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: HOLD THE DUMBBELLS AT YOUR SIDES WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. STAND STRAIGHT WITH ONE FOOT FORWARD AND ONE FOOT BEHIND. REST THE BACK FOOT ON A BENCH. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR FRONT KNEE. STOP WHEN YOUR FRONT THIGH IS PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_114">MUSCLE GROUP: GLUTES \n\nSTEP 1. LIE FLAT ON THE FLOOR OR MAT WITH ARLÉ LEG EXTENDED STRAIGHT AND THE OTHER LEG BENT WITH THE FOOT FLAT ON THE FLOOR. PLACE YOUR ARMS DOWN ON THE MAT, ON THE SIDE OF YOUR HIPS. \n\nSTEP 2. RAISE YOUR LOWER BACK OFF THE FLOOR WHILE KEEPING YOUR EXTENDED LEG STRAIGHT. HOLD THEN RETURN TO YOUR ORIGINAL POSITION AFTER A FEW REPETITIONS, SWITCH LEGS AND REPEAT WITH THE OTHER SIDE.</string>
    <string name="description_237">MUSCLE GROUP: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD DUMBBELLS AT YOUR SIDES WITH NEUTRAL GRIP. \n\nSTEP 2: WHILE KEEPING YOUR BACK STRAIGHT, STEP TO YOUR SIDE WITH ONE FOOT AND LOWER YOURSELF BY BENDING YOUR KNEES. THE BACK FOOT STAYS IN POSITION. STOP WHEN YOUR FRONT THIGH IS PARALLEL WITH THE GROUND HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_175">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1. HOLD A WEIGHT PLATE USING BOTH AANDS AT THE LEVEL OF YOUR THIGHS. KEEP YOUR ARMS STRAIGHT, AND STAND FULLY UPRIGHT. \n\nSTEP 2. RAISE THE PLATE IN AN TO THE FRONT AND OVER YOUR SHOULDER TWISTING YOUR UPPER BODY TO THAT SIDE. \n\nSTEP 3. RETURN TO THE STARTING POSITION AND REPEAT THE MOTION BUT TARGET THE OTHER SIDE OF THE BODY.</string>
    <string name="description_168">MUSCLE NAME: QUADRICEPS \n\nSTEP 1. START IN A PUSHUP POSITION. KEEPING YOUR ARMS STRAIGHT AND YOUR CORE ENGAGED \n\nSTEP 2. SHIFT YOUR WEIGHT ONTO YOUR LEFT ARM, ROTATE YOUR TORSO TO THE RIGHT, AND RAISE YOUR RIGHT ARM TOWARD THE CEILING SO THAT YOUR BODY FORMS A T. \n\nSTEP 3. HOLD FOR THREE SECONDS, THEN RETURN TO START AND REPEAT ON THE OTHER SIDE. THAT\'S ONE REP.</string>
    <string name="description_182">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. HOLD DUMBBELL WITH OVERHAND GRIP. POSITION THE DUMBBELL NEXT TO YOUR HEAD. \n\nSTEP 2: BEND KNEES SLIGHTLY. \n\nSTEP 3: JUMP AND PUSH THE DUMBBELL UP. RAISE DUMBBELL OVERHEAD WITH ARMS FULLY EXTENDED. LAND WITH ONE FOOT FORWARD AND ONE FOOT BEHIND. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_239">MUSCLE GROUP: DELTOIDS \n\nSTEP 1: BEGIN BY SQUATTING LOWER OVER A DUMBBELL. MAINTAIN A LOCKED AND RIGID LOWER BACK AND HAVE YOUR FEET PLACED A SHOULDER WIDTH APART. \n\nSTEP 2. GRASP THE DUMBBELL AND TIGHTEN THE ABDOMINAL MUSCLES. IN A RAPID AND US MOTION, LIFT THE DUMBBELL UPWARD UNTIL YOUR ARM IS STRAIGHT AND LOOKED, AS ILLUSTRATED. THE DUMBBELL SHOULD TRAVEL CLOSE TO THE BODY AND NOT SWING OUT OR AWAY. \n\nSTEP 3. BRIEFLY HOLD IT ABOVE YOUR HEAD, THEN BRING IT DOWN TO THE STARTING POSITION.</string>
    <string name="description_205">MUSCLE GROUP: TRICEPS BRACHII \n\nSTEP 1. LIE ON A BENCH WITH YOUR KNEES BENT FARID FEET FLAT ON THE FLOOR. HOLD A FAIRLY LIGHT DUMBBELL IN YOUR LEFT HAND AND STRAIGHTEN THE ARM SO THAT THE WEIGHT IS ABOVE YOUR SHOULDER. USE YOUR RIGHT HAND TO REACH ACROSS YOUR CHEST AND UP THE UPPER PART OF YOUR LEFT ARM TO HELP STABILIZE IT. \n\nSTEP 2. TURN THE WEIGHT SO THAT YOUR PALM FACES IN. WITHOUT MOVING YOUR UPPER ARM BEND YOUR ELBOW AND SLOWLY LOWER THE DUMBBELL UNTIL IT REACHES THE SIDE OF YOUR HEAD. \n\nSTEP 3. SLOWLY PRESS THE WEIGHT BACK UP ABOVE YOU. FINISH THE SET, THEN SWITCH POSITIONS TO WORK YOUR RIGHT ARM.</string>
    <string name="description_201">MUSCLE GROUP: TRICEPS BRACHII \n\nSTEP 1. STAND STRAIGHT UPRIGHT WITH YOUR FEET SHOULDER-WIDTH APART, HOLDING A LIGHT DUMBBELL IN YOUR LEFT HAND. \n\nSTEP 2. PRESS THE DUMBBELL OVER YOUR HEAD SO THAT YOUR LEFT ARM IS STRAIGHT PALM POINTING OUT TO THE SIDE. REACH YOUR RIGHT ARM ACROSS YOUR FACE AND CUP YOUR LEFT ELBOW WITH YOUR RIGHT HAND THIS WILL HELP KEEP YOUR UPPER ARM STABLE AS YOU PERFORM THE EXERCISE. \n\nSTEP 3. WITHOUT MOVING YOUR UPPER ARM, SLOWLY BEND YOUR LEFT ELBOW AND LOWER THE DUMBBELL BEHIND YOUR HEAD AS FAR AS POSSIBLE \n\nSTEP 4. EXTEND THE DUMBBELL BACK OVERHEAD UNTIL YOUR LEFT ARM IS STRAIGHT AND REPEAT FOR ONE SET. THEN PLACE THE DUMBBELL IN YOUR RIGHT HAND AND REPEAT THE EXERCISE WITH YOUR RIGHT ARM.</string>
    <string name="description_212">MUSCLE TRICEPS BRACHII \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. POSITION ONE HAND ON THE CENTER OF YOUR UPPER BACK. YOUR ELBOW POINTS TOWARD THE CEILING. \n\nSTEP 2: USE YOUR OTHER HAND TO HOLD YOUR ELBOW. PULL ELBOW DOWN AND TOWARD YOUR HEAD. HOLD THIS POSITION FOR 15-25 SECONDS. REPEAT WITH OTHER SIDE.</string>
    <string name="description_241">MUSCLE GROUP: LATISSIMUS DORSI \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. POSITION YOUR HANDS ON YOUR HIPS. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE ONE ARM OVERHEAD AND BEND YOUR BODY TOWARD ONE SIDE. HOLD FOR 15-25 SECONDS. REPEAT WITH OTHER SIDE.</string>
    <string name="description_218">MUSCLE GROUP: ADDUCTORS \n\nSTEP 1: STAND STRAIGHT WITH FEET MORE THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART. PLACE YOUR HANDS ON YOUR HIPS. \n\nSTEP 2: LOWER YOUR BODY TOWARD ONE SIDE. YOUR OPPOSITE LEG IS STRAIGHTENED OUT. HOLD FOR 15-25 SECONDS. REPEAT WITH OTHER SIDE.</string>
    <string name="description_220">MUSCLE HAMSTRINGS \n\nSTEP 1: LIE FLAT ON THE FLOOR. FULLY EXTEND YOUR LEGS. REST YOUR HANDS YOUR SIDE. \n\nSTEP 2: LIFT ONE LEG TOWARD YOUR CHEST. YOUR KNEE REMAINS BENT. POSITION YOUR HANDS ON YOUR THIGH. PULL YOUR LEG TOWARD YOUR UPPER BODY. HOLD THIS POSITION FOR 15-25 SECONDS. REPEAT WITH OTHER LEG.</string>
    <string name="description_261">MUSCLE: RECTUS ABDOMINIS\n\nSTEP 1: LIE DOWN ON THE FLOOR. POSITION YOUR HANDS AND LEGS ON THE FLOOR. \n\nSTEP 2: RAISE YOUR UPPER BODY UPWARD. HOLD FOR ONE SECOND. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION.</string>
<!--    <string name="round">Round</string>-->
<!--    <string name="reset">Reset</string>-->
<!--    <string name="intervals">Intervals</string>-->
<!--    <string name="settings">Settings</string>-->
<!--    <string name="current_settings">Current settings</string>-->
<!--    <string name="my_workouts">My workouts</string>-->
<!--    <string name="work_time">Work time</string>-->
<!--    <string name="rest_time">Rest time</string>-->
<!--    <string name="rounds">Rounds</string>-->
<!--    <string name="done">Done</string>-->
<!--    <string name="done_w">Done</string>-->
<!--    <string name="min">min</string>-->
<!--    <string name="sec">sec</string>-->
<!--    <string name="seconds">seconds</string>-->
<!--    <string name="repetitions">repetitions</string>-->
<!--    <string name="edit">Edit</string>-->
<!--    <string name="start">Start</string>-->
<!--    <string name="resume">Resume</string>-->
<!--    <string name="pause">Pause</string>-->
<!--    <string name="title_7_minutes">7 minutes</string>-->
<!--    <string name="premium">Premium</string>-->
<!--    <string name="workouts_category_description_header">20 workouts and no ads</string>-->
<!--    <string name="workouts_category_description_footer">Build-in workouts player focused on home training, fat burning, build muscle and getting lean abs</string>-->
<!--    <string name="upgrade_now">Upgrade now</string>-->
<!--    <string name="kcal">kcal</string>-->
<!--    <string name="start_workout">Start workout</string>-->
<!--    <string name="quick_workout">Quick workout</string>-->
<!--    <string name="skip">Skip</string>-->
<!--    <string name="workout_done">Workout done, Great job</string>-->
<!--    <string name="next_exercise">Next exercise</string>-->
<!--    <string name="rest_next_exercise">Next exercise:</string>-->
<!--    <string name="rest_last_exercise">Last exercise:</string>-->
<!--    <string name="workout">Workout</string>-->
<!--    <string name="prepare">Prepare</string>-->
<!--    <string name="go">Go</string>-->
<!--    <string name="halfway">Half Way There</string>-->
<!--    <string name="more_sec">more seconds</string>-->
<!--    <string name="pausing_workout">Pausing workout</string>-->
<!--    <string name="resuming_workout">Resuming workout</string>-->

<!--    <string name="restore">Restore</string>-->
<!--    <string name="extra_plan_workouts">Extra plan workouts</string>-->
<!---->
<!--    <string name="cardio">CARDIO</string>-->
    <string name="cardio_title">RUN • SPIN • SWIM • CYCLE</string>
<!--    <string name="cardio_description">20-40 MIN OF CARDIOVASCULAR ACTIVITY IS NECESSARY TO KEEP THE METABOLISM ROARING AND HELP YOU BURN SOME EXTRA CALORIES THAT WILL LEAD TO FAT LOSS. \n\n I WOULD RECOMMEND DOING YOUR CARDIO FIRST THING IN THE MORNING, BEFORE BREAKFAST. THIS WAY IT IS OUT OF THE WAY, AND IT WILL REALLY BOOST YOUR ENERGY FOR A GOOD PORTION OF THE DAY TO FOLLOW. IT IS A LITTLE TOUGH IN THE BEGINNING, BUT AFTER A WEEK, YOU WILL FEEL SO GOOD DOING IT, YOU WILL BE LOCKED IN A ROUTINE. \n\n  IF THERE IS NO WAY YOU CAN DO IT FIRST THING IN THE MORNING, I WOULD DO IT RIGHT AFTER YOU TRAIN WITH WEIGHTS OR AT NIGHT AFTER YOUR LAST MEAL. BRING A HEADSET WITH YOUR FAVORITE MUSIC TO HELP THE TIME GO FASTER.</string>-->

    <string name="active_rest_day_title">ACTIVE REST DAY • YOGA • PILATES</string>
    <string name="active_rest_day_description">  CONSISTENCY IN EXERCISE IS THE KEY TO REAL RESULTS AND REAL HEALTH BENEFITS. AND THE MORE CONSISTENTLY YOU ARE EXERCISE, THE FASTER YOU WILL SEE TANGIBLE RESULTS. \n\n THE PROGRESS MEANS MORE YOU EXERCISE MORE POWERFUL THE EFFECT ON THE BODY. ITS A BALANCE OVER TIME THAT HELPS YOU MAINTAIN A HEALTH WEIGHT. ENERGY OUT MUST EQUAL TO OR GREATER THAN ENERGY IN.</string>
<!--    <string name="sets">sets</string>-->

<!--    <string name="create_custom_workout_title">To create new workout \n press +</string>-->
<!--    <string name="enter_workout_name">Enter workout name:</string>-->
<!--    <string name="search_for_exercise">Search for exercise</string>-->
<!--    <string name="ok">OK</string>-->
<!--    <string name="selected_exercise">Selected exercise</string>-->
<!--    <string name="how_many_minutes">How many minutes?</string>-->
<!--    <string name="choose_a_custom_length">Choose a custom length</string>-->
<!--    <string name="begin_workout">Begin workout</string>-->
<!--    <string name="set_custom_interval">Set custom interval</string>-->
<!--    <string name="prepare_workout">Prepare workout</string>-->
<!--    <string name="try_a_new_timing_variation">Try a new timing variation</string>-->
<!--    <string name="hit_choice">Hit (high intensity interval training)</string>-->
<!--    <string name="hit_choice_description">30 seconds of exercise, 15 seconds of rest</string>-->
<!--    <string name="tabata_choice">Tabata</string>-->
<!--    <string name="tabata_description">20 seconds of exercise, 10 seconds of rest</string>-->

<!--    <string name="exercise_length_key">Exercise length(sec):</string>-->
<!--    <string name="preview_time_interval_key">Preview time interval(sec):</string>-->
<!--    <string name="preview_key">Preview:</string>-->
<!--    <string name="length_of_rest_break">Length of rest break(sec):</string>-->
<!--    <string name="rest_time_key">Rest time:</string>-->
<!--    <string name="delete">Delete</string>-->
<!--    <string name="undo">Undo</string>-->
<!--    <string name="edit_custom_workout">Edit custom workout</string>-->
<!--    <string name="add_or_remove_exercise">Add or Remove Exercise</string>-->
<!--    <string name="rename_workout">Rename Workout</string>-->
<!--    <string name="change_exercise_order">Change Exercise Order</string>-->
<!--    <string name="new_workout_name">New Workout Name</string>-->

<!--    <string name="contact_v">Stay connected with VGFIT</string>-->
<!--    <string name="vg_details" translatable="false">www.vgfit.com</string>-->
<!--    <string name="tweet">Share app on Twitter</string>-->
<!--    <string name="sharef">Share app on Facebook</string>-->
<!--    <string name="rate_us">Rate us</string>-->
<!--    <string name="send_feed">Send feedback</string>-->
<!--    <string name="tell_friend">Tell a Friend</string>-->
<!--    <string name="other_apps">Our other apps</string>-->
<!--    <string name="reminder">Reminder</string>-->
<!--    <string name="daily_reminder">Daily reminder</string>-->
<!--    <string name="frequency_days">Frequency(days)</string>-->
<!--    <string name="after_days">After %1$d of inactivity</string>-->
<!--    <string name="time_to_workout">It\'s time to workout!</string>-->
<!--    <string name="day">day</string>-->

    <string name="superset_1">QUICK HIIT</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_1">MAT • DUMBBELLS</string>
    <string name="superset_2">FULL INTENSITY</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_2">EXERCISE MAT</string>
    <string name="superset_3">CIRCUIT BURNER</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_3">MAT • DUMBBELLS • BENCH</string>
    <string name="superset_4">BOOT CAMP</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_4">MAT • DUMBBELLS • BENCH</string>
    <string name="superset_5">CORE STRENGTH</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_5">MAT</string>
    <string name="superset_6">TOTAL BODY IMPACT</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_6">MAT • DUMBBELLS • BENCH</string>
    <string name="superset_7">POWER UP</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_7">MAT • DUMBBELLS</string>
    <string name="superset_8">CORE SCULPT</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_8">MAT</string>
    <string name="superset_9">BODY FLEXOR</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_9">MAT • DUMBBELLS • BENCH</string>
    <string name="superset_10">LOWER BODY</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_10">MAT • DUMBBELLS • BENCH</string>
    <string name="superset_11">FULL BODY WORKOUT</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_11">MAT • BENCH</string>
    <string name="superset_12">INTENSE INTERVAL</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_12">MAT • CHAIR</string>
    <string name="superset_13">TOTAL IMPACT</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_13">MAT • BENCH</string>
    <string name="superset_14">FAST CARDIO</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_14">MAT • BENCH</string>
    <string name="superset_15">ABS BURNER</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_15">MAT • BENCH</string>
    <string name="superset_16">CIRCUIT BREAKER</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_16" translatable="false">NONE</string>
    <string name="superset_17">ABS &amp; ARMS</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_17">MAT • BENCH</string>
    <string name="superset_18">TABATA WORKOUT</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_18" translatable="false">NONE</string>
    <string name="superset_19">THE BALANCE OF POWER</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_19">MAT • DUMBBELLS</string>
    <string name="superset_20">CORE CONTROL</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_20">MAT • DUMBBELLS</string>
    <string name="superset_21">DYNAMIC CIRCUIT</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_21">MAT • DUMBBELLS</string>
    <string name="superset_22">FOCUS ON ABS</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_22">MAT • DUMBBELLS</string>
    <string name="superset_23">GET POWER</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_23">MAT • DUMBBELLS • BENCH</string>
    <string name="superset_24">FULL BODY FITNESS</string>
    <string name="superset_equipment_24">MAT • DUMBBELLS</string>

    <string name="focus">FOCUS</string>
    <string name="equipment">EQUIPMENT</string>
    <string name="seven_days_plan">7 DAYS PLAN</string>

    <string name="plan_focus_1">BURNING FAT•MUSCULAR ENDURANCE•DEVELOP STRENGTH • CORE STRENGTH•FULL BODY STRENGTH &amp; POWER</string>
    <string name="plan_focus_2">BUILDING LEAN MUSCLE • CHEST • ARMS•SHOULDERS • CORE LOWER BODY STRENGTH FULL BODY WORKOUT • POWER DEVELOPMENT</string>
    <string name="plan_focus_3">BURNING FAT • CORE STRENGTH • CIRCUIT TRAINING • LOWER BODY ENDURANCE</string>

    <string name="plan_equipment_1">MAT • BENCH•DUMBBELLS • BARBELL</string>
    <string name="plan_equipment_2">MAT • BENCH•DUMBBELLS • BARBELL</string>
    <string name="plan_equipment_3">EXERCISE MAT</string>

    <string name="plan_seven_days_plan_1">MODERATE AND HIGH INTENSITY • BEGINNER &amp; ADVANCED LEVEL</string>
    <string name="plan_seven_days_plan_2">MODERATE AND HIGH INTENSITY • BEGINNER &amp; ADVANCED LEVEL</string>
    <string name="plan_seven_days_plan_3">MODERATE AND HIGH INTENSITY • BEGINNER &amp; ADVANCED LEVEL</string>

    <string name="unlock_plan">UNLOCK PLAN</string>

    <string name="extra_muscle_group_1">CHEST | ARMS | ABS</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_2">CARDIO</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_3">BACK | ARMS | ABS</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_4">HIIT WORKOUT</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_5">SHOULDERS | TRICEPS</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_6">CARDIO</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_7">ACTIVE REST DAY</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_8">CHEST | TRICEPS </string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_9">BACK | BICEPS</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_10">CARDIO</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_11">LEGS | CALVES</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_12">SHOULDERS | TRAPS</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_13">CARDIO</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_14">ACTIVE REST DAY</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_15">ABS ROUTINE</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_16">CARDIO</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_17">ABS ROUTINE</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_18">CARDIO</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_19">ABS ROUTINE</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_20">CARDIO</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_21">ACTIVE REST DAY</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_22">HIIT WORKOUT</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_23">LEGS | CALVES</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_24">CHEST | ARMS | ABS</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_25">CHEST | ARMS | ABS</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_26">BACK | ARMS | ABS</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_27">HIIT WORKOUT</string>
    <string name="extra_muscle_group_28">ACTIVE REST DAY</string>

    <string name="extra_equipment_1">MAT •  BENCH</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_2" translatable="false">NONE</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_3">MAT •  BARBELL •  DUMBBELLS</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_4" translatable="false">NONE</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_5">MAT •  DUMBBELLS</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_6" translatable="false">NONE</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_7" translatable="false">NONE</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_8">BENCH •  BARBELLS •  DUMBBELLS</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_9">BARBELL •  DUMBBELLS</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_10" translatable="false">NONE</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_11">BARBELL</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_12">BENCH •  BARBELLS •  DUMBBELLS</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_13" translatable="false">NONE</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_14" translatable="false">NONE</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_15" translatable="false">NONE</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_16" translatable="false">NONE</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_17" translatable="false">NONE</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_18" translatable="false">NONE</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_19" translatable="false">NONE</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_20" translatable="false">NONE</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_21" translatable="false">NONE</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_22">BENCH •  BARBELLS •  DUMBBELLS</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_23">BENCH •  BARBELLS •  DUMBBELLS</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_24">BENCH •  BARBELLS •  DUMBBELLS</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_25">MAT •  BARBELL •  DUMBBELLS</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_26">MAT •  BARBELL •  DUMBBELLS</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_27">MAT •  BENCH</string>
    <string name="extra_equipment_28" translatable="false">NONE</string>

    <string name="cardio_description">20-40 MIN OF CARDIOVASCULAR ACTIVITY IS NECESSARY TO KEEP THE METABOLISM ROARING AND HELP YOU BURN SOME EXTRA CALORIES THAT WILL LEAD TO FAT LOSS. \n\n I WOULD RECOMMEND DOING YOUR CARDIO FIRST THING IN THE MORNING, BEFORE BREAKFAST. THIS WAY IT IS OUT OF THE WAY, AND IT WILL REALLY BOOST YOUR ENERGY FOR A GOOD PORTION OF THE DAY TO FOLLOW. IT IS A LITTLE TOUGH IN THE BEGINNING, BUT AFTER A WEEK, YOU WILL FEEL SO GOOD DOING IT, YOU WILL BE LOCKED IN A ROUTINE. \n\n  IF THERE IS NO WAY YOU CAN DO IT FIRST THING IN THE MORNING, I WOULD DO IT RIGHT AFTER YOU TRAIN WITH WEIGHTS OR AT NIGHT AFTER YOUR LAST MEAL. BRING A HEADSET WITH YOUR FAVORITE MUSIC TO HELP THE TIME GO FASTER.</string>
</resources>